<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <title>Bibarud</title>
    <link href="https://www.bibarud.com/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://www.bibarud.com" />
    <updated>2021-07-09T02:13:36+05:30</updated>
    <author>
        <name>Uddipan Barman</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://www.bibarud.com</id>

    <entry>
        <title>Fix for key mapping in Gameloop 2021</title>
        <author>
            <name>Uddipan Barman</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://www.bibarud.com/fix-for-key-mapping-in-gameloop-2021/"/>
        <id>https://www.bibarud.com/fix-for-key-mapping-in-gameloop-2021/</id>
            <category term="Explained"/>

        <updated>2021-07-09T02:13:36+05:30</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://www.bibarud.com/media/posts/18/name-5.jpeg" alt="Fix for key mapping in Gameloop 2021" />
                     Do you know what Gameloop is? I'm confident you have. If&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://www.bibarud.com/media/posts/18/name-5.jpeg" alt="Fix for key mapping in Gameloop 2021" />
                <div class="post__toc">
<h3>Table of Contents</h3>
<ul>
<li><a href="#mcetoc_1fa3t1s5k4c">What exactly is Gameloop?</a></li>
<li><a href="#mcetoc_1fa3t1s5k4d">Fix for the key mapping in Gameloop</a>
<ul>
<li><a href="#mcetoc_1fa3t1s5k4e">The steps to resolving this problem, according to them, are as follows:</a></li>
</ul>
</li>
<li><a href="#mcetoc_1fa3t1s5k4f">Conclusion</a></li>
</ul>
</div>
<p data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="126">Do you know what Gameloop is? I'm confident you have. If you haven't already, check out Tencent Gaming Buddy. Isn't this all too familiar? Gameloop, formerly known as Tencent Gaming Buddy, is now one of the most popular Android emulators. Today, we'll discuss the Gameloop key mapping fix for the year 2021.</p>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="127">Sure, Gameloop may lag behind other emulators (Genymotion, Virtual Box, and so on) in some areas, but you can rely on it for your gaming needs. It was made just for the purpose of playing Android games, and only that.</p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1fa3t1s5k4c" class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="128">What exactly is Gameloop?</h2>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="129">Gameloop is the same as Tencent Gaming Buddy, as I previously stated. It's a popular Tencent programme for playing Android games on desktops, namely Player Unknown Battlegrounds Mobile, or PUBG Mobile for short. This is a huge benefit because it allows computer gamers who don't have enough money or don't want to buy PUBG to play PUBG Mobile through this software.</p>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="130">The software includes buttons and settings for the majority of popular Android games, including PUBG Mobile. You don't even have to map them yourself because the procedure is completely automated and smooth.</p>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="131">You may, however, be perplexed. Why don't we try out some other Android emulators? You certainly could, but you wouldn't be able to play it as smoothly or readily. The majority of Android emulators are designed to accommodate as many functions as possible, which can make them slow. When playing a difficult game like PUBG Mobile, this delay increases.</p>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="132">To play the game, you must also map each key. However, Gameloop comes with these keys pre-mapped, so you can jump right in! However, there is a current problem that prevents users from using the F, G, and H keys. Let's have a look at what causes it and what we can do about it.</p>
<figure class="post__image"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://s.gameloop.fun/gameassistant/web/0b6deeae97ae8a8cfbfb1fb713ee294e.jpeg" data-is-external-image="true"  alt="Fix for key mapping in Gameloop 2021" width="702" height="410"></figure>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1fa3t1s5k4d" class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="133">Fix for the key mapping in Gameloop</h2>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="134">After some investigation and numerous tests, I discovered that this is a probable Gameloop and PUBG Mobile malfunction. However, after some time, a straight solution from the Gameloop Discord server was discovered.</p>
<h3 id="mcetoc_1fa3t1s5k4e" class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="135">The steps to resolving this problem, according to them, are as follows:</h3>
<ul>
<li class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="136"><strong>Step 1:</strong> To begin, launch Gameloop and launch PUBG Mobile.</li>
<li class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="137"><strong>Step 2:</strong> Go to Settings &gt; Controls &gt; Customize from there.</li>
</ul>
<p>Remember that you should only use the customise tab for one movement at a time, not for driving.</p>
<ul>
<li class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="139"><strong>Step 3:</strong> Select Reset and Save from the menu. The Customisations option will thereafter be closed.</li>
<li class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="140"><strong>Step 4:</strong> After you've completed the previous steps, press F11.</li>
</ul>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="141">As a result, the game will depart full screen mode and run in window mode.</p>
<ul>
<li class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="142"><strong>Step 5:</strong> On the right side of Gameloop's panel, locate and select the Keyboard option.</li>
<li class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="143"><strong>Step 6:</strong> All of the assigned keys will now be accessible.</li>
</ul>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="144">Ensure that the display resolution and key mapping mode are both the same.</p>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="145">If your resolution is 1080p, for example, your mode should be Smart 1080.</p>
<ul>
<li class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="146"><strong>Step 7:</strong> Save after pressing Reset.</li>
<li class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="147"><strong>Step 8:</strong> Go to the top right and select Settings, then Clean Cache twice.</li>
</ul>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="148">As indicated in Gameloop's official repair, we're cleaning it twice just to be safe.</p>
<ul>
<li class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="149"><strong>Step 9:</strong> Launch PUBG Mobile after restarting Gameloop.</li>
<li class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="150"><strong>Step 10:</strong> When prompted, pick the High Resolution Texture pack.</li>
</ul>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="151">The repair will fail if you choose a Low-Resolution texture pack.</p>
<ul>
<li class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="152"><strong>Step 11:</strong> Go back to the PUBG Mobile settings, then controls and customisations, and execute another reset.</li>
</ul>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="153">This method should simply resolve your issue, allowing you to continue playing the game without interruption.</p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1fa3t1s5k4f" class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="154">Conclusion</h2>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="155" data-from-init="true">The accompanying post covered many approaches to resolving Gameloop's key mapping issues. I hope you found the information in this post useful. Check out <a href="https://www.gameloop.com/" title="Gameloop" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Gameloop </a>if you don't already have it.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>What does the phrase &quot;no couriers nearby&quot; on Uber Eats mean? (2021)</title>
        <author>
            <name>Uddipan Barman</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://www.bibarud.com/what-does-the-phrase-no-couriers-nearby-on-uber-eats-mean/"/>
        <id>https://www.bibarud.com/what-does-the-phrase-no-couriers-nearby-on-uber-eats-mean/</id>
            <category term="Explained"/>

        <updated>2021-07-06T00:34:13+05:30</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://www.bibarud.com/media/posts/17/name-4.jpeg" alt="no couriers nearby on Uber Eats mean" />
                     Other options for resolving the Uber Eats no courier nearby issue&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://www.bibarud.com/media/posts/17/name-4.jpeg" alt="no couriers nearby on Uber Eats mean" />
                <div class="post__toc">
<h3>Table of Contents</h3>
<ul>
<li><a href="#mcetoc_1f9s05mqfe3">Uber eats is a fantastic service with numerous advantages, including the following:</a>
<ul>
<li><a href="#mcetoc_1f9s05mqfe4">Ordering is a straightforward process.</a></li>
<li><a href="#mcetoc_1f9s05mqfe5">You can choose between Pickup and delivery options.</a></li>
<li><a href="#mcetoc_1f9s05mqfe6">Methods of Making Simple Payments</a></li>
<li><a href="#mcetoc_1f9s05mqfe7">You can keep track of your meal orders in real-time.</a></li>
<li><a href="#mcetoc_1f9s05mqfe8">Numerous well-known restaurants, including:</a></li>
</ul>
</li>
<li><a href="#mcetoc_1f9s05mqfe9">But what does the fact that there are no Uber Eats couriers nearby mean? And how does one go about fixing it?</a></li>
<li><a href="#mcetoc_1f9s05mqfea">How to resolve the Uber Eats issue of no nearby courier.</a>
<ul>
<li><a href="#mcetoc_1f9s05mqfeb">The following are the most effective methods of resolving this problem:</a></li>
</ul>
</li>
<li><a href="#mcetoc_1f9s0c9f2es">Other options for resolving the Uber Eats no courier nearby issue include:</a></li>
<li><a href="#mcetoc_1f9s05mqfed">Is it possible to cancel your Uber Eats order if it takes an excessive amount of time?</a></li>
<li><a href="#mcetoc_1f9s05mqfee">Is it possible for Uber Eats to refund the cancellation fee?</a></li>
</ul>
</div>
<p class="dropcap"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Food delivery has risen to prominence in several countries in recent years. Even though it was already widely used previous to Covid 19, the lockdown caused by Covid 19 significantly boosted the priority of these jobs by orders of magnitude. Uber Eats is an example of a service that seeks to provide food delivery to customers in their local area.</span></p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1f9s05mqfe3"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Uber eats is a fantastic service with numerous advantages, including the following:</span></h2>
<h3 id="mcetoc_1f9s05mqfe4"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Ordering is a straightforward process.</span></h3>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">You may select your meal order from any menu with a few touches and add it to your basket. That's all there is to it.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">As soon as you can, place an order for food to be delivered by delivery persons.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Alternatively, you can place your meal order in advance and have a delivery person pick it up later. It's entirely up to you!</span></p>
<h3 id="mcetoc_1f9s05mqfe5"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">You can choose between Pickup and delivery options.</span></h3>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Instead of ordering food for delivery, you can now order food ahead of time for pick up. Pickup is selected, food items are added to your cart, and you proceed to the restaurant to get your food. Alternatively, you can choose the new no-contact delivery option, which will have your order left at your door.</span></p>
<h3 id="mcetoc_1f9s05mqfe6"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Methods of Making Simple Payments</span></h3>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Pay with a credit card or Uber Cash to get paid promptly. It's simple to switch out a card.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">To receive a discount on your food order, enter an Uber Eats promo code at checkout.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">In the app, you may effortlessly leave a tip. There is no requirement for cash for tipping.</span></p>
<h3 id="mcetoc_1f9s05mqfe7"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">You can keep track of your meal orders in real-time.</span></h3>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Follow the progress of your food order on a map as it makes its way to you.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">See what the expected delivery time to your location will be.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">You will be contacted when your order has arrived.</span></p>
<h3 id="mcetoc_1f9s05mqfe8"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Numerous well-known restaurants, including:</span></h3>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> McDonald's, Subway, Popeyes Louisiana Kitchen, Starbucks, Five Guys, Panda Express, Denny's, Jersey Mike's Subs, T.G.I. Friday's, Hooters, Sonic, Red Lobster, and many more are located here. Among the restaurants are Firehouse Subs, Moe's Southwest Grill, BurgerFi, Tropical Smoothie Cafe, Boston Market, Qdoba, Steak' n Shake, The Halal Guys, Anthony's Coal Fired Pizza, Tijuana Flats, Church's Chicken, White Castle, McAlister's Deli, Jack in the Box, On The Border, Fatburger, Romano's Macaroni Grill, Famous Dave's B.B.Q.,</span></p>
<div class="gallery-wrapper"><div class="gallery"  data-is-empty="false" data-columns="3">
<figure class="gallery__item"><a href="https://www.bibarud.com/media/posts/17/gallery/unnamed-33.webp" data-size="374x664"><img loading="lazy" src="https://www.bibarud.com/media/posts/17/gallery/unnamed-33-thumbnail.webp" alt="no couriers nearby on Uber Eats mean" width="374" height="664"></a></figure>
<figure class="gallery__item"><a href="https://www.bibarud.com/media/posts/17/gallery/unnamed-32.webp" data-size="374x664"><img loading="lazy" src="https://www.bibarud.com/media/posts/17/gallery/unnamed-32-thumbnail.webp" alt="no couriers nearby on Uber Eats mean" width="374" height="664"></a></figure>
<figure class="gallery__item"><a href="https://www.bibarud.com/media/posts/17/gallery/unnamed-31.webp" data-size="374x664"><img loading="lazy" src="https://www.bibarud.com/media/posts/17/gallery/unnamed-31-thumbnail.webp" alt="no couriers nearby on Uber Eats mean" width="374" height="664"></a></figure>
</div></div>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1f9s05mqfe9"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">But what does the fact that there are no Uber Eats couriers nearby mean? And how does one go about fixing it?</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">If you've recently placed an Uber Eats order or scheduled one but received the phrase 'no couriers nearby,' you've probably experienced a frustrating situation that could have been avoided. The problem with this is that Uber does not always identify a suitable courier to deliver your food, which can be frustrating. As a result, you are receiving this error message.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">I believe you are already familiar with the term "courier." Couriers are persons who Uber Eats have employed to bring your meal from a restaurant to you.</span></p>
<p><strong>Also Read:</strong> <a href="https://www.bibarud.com/windows-11-details/">Windows 11: When it will be released, how much it will cost, and everything you need to know.</a></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Additionally, there is an additional cause for it. If the app has been experiencing glitches for any reason, your Uber Eats may display the same message to you, given that you were stranded at your location while the app experienced a fault. In either case, we are prepared to provide a solution for either of these eventualities.</span></p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1f9s05mqfea"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">How to resolve the Uber Eats issue of no nearby courier.</span></h2>
<h3 id="mcetoc_1f9s05mqfeb"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The following are the most effective methods of resolving this problem:</span></h3>
<p id="mcetoc_1f9s080jjej"><strong><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Move the delivery location of your food order:</span></strong><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">If you are still unable to locate a courier after waiting, you can change the delivery location to a more commonplace one. These problems are frequently seen in rural areas. If you are going to a friend's house who lives in the city, for example, you might want to consider ordering the food to be delivered to them instead.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">A restaurant may be located in an area where delivery drivers are in short supply. If your order cannot be delivered, consider a different restaurant that serves the same meal but is more well-known in the community. In this manner, there will almost certainly be a courier nearby who would be willing to bring your food.</span></p>
<p id="mcetoc_1f9s080jjek"><strong><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Pickup from restaurant:</span></strong><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> </span></p>
<p id="mcetoc_1f9s0c9f2er">Assume that most delivery drivers are either busy or on vacation, resulting in a scarcity of food delivery personnel. If this is the case, the best course of action would be to order the food for Pickup and pick it up from the restaurant yourself. You would escape all large crowds in this manner and would be able to dine comfortably in your own home at the time of your choosing.</p>
<div class="gallery-wrapper"><div class="gallery"  data-is-empty="false" data-columns="3">
<figure class="gallery__item"><a href="https://www.bibarud.com/media/posts/17/gallery/unnamed-36.webp" data-size="374x664"><img loading="lazy" src="https://www.bibarud.com/media/posts/17/gallery/unnamed-36-thumbnail.webp" alt="no couriers nearby on Uber Eats mean" width="374" height="664"></a></figure>
<figure class="gallery__item"><a href="https://www.bibarud.com/media/posts/17/gallery/unnamed-35.webp" data-size="374x664"><img loading="lazy" src="https://www.bibarud.com/media/posts/17/gallery/unnamed-35-thumbnail.webp" alt="no couriers nearby on Uber Eats mean" width="374" height="664"></a></figure>
<figure class="gallery__item"><a href="https://www.bibarud.com/media/posts/17/gallery/unnamed-34.webp" data-size="374x664"><img loading="lazy" src="https://www.bibarud.com/media/posts/17/gallery/unnamed-34-thumbnail.webp" alt="no couriers nearby on Uber Eats mean" width="374" height="664"></a></figure>
</div></div>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1f9s0c9f2es"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Other options for resolving the Uber Eats no courier nearby issue include:</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Rebooting your phone, cleaning its data and cache, and reinstalling the app are all options you could attempt in addition to the above. Always make sure that the app on your Android smartphone is up to date with the most recent version available to you. If your application is not kept up to date, it may begin to display unexpected errors like these.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">This is primarily because the app is out of date and cannot correctly sync with the servers. Furthermore, updating an app ensures that you receive the most up-to-date user interface designs, security, and any other features that the company is currently offering.</span></p>
<p><strong>Also Read: </strong><a href="https://www.bibarud.com/is-there-still-potential-to-earn-money-from-the-internet/">Is there still potential to earn money from the internet in 2021?</a><strong><br></strong></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">It might be beneficial if you also thought about utilising a down detector. According to your geographic location, this excellent website can track down and inform you of which websites and services are unavailable. If all else fails, consider going to the website and contacting customer service about the problem you're experiencing. They are extremely friendly and helpful, and they will go above and above to assist you.</span></p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1f9s05mqfed"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Is it possible to cancel your Uber Eats order if it takes an excessive amount of time?</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Yes, you have the option to cancel your Uber Eats order if your food delivery takes an excessive amount of time. If fewer couriers are available, your order may be picked up from the restaurant somewhat later than expected. This may alter your attitude toward the food or the order.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">If you are dissatisfied with your order or arrive much later than expected, you can cancel it by going to the Order Summary page. You may be asked for specific reasons for cancelling the order, but this will not prohibit you from doing so.</span></p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1f9s05mqfee"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Is it possible for Uber Eats to refund the cancellation fee?</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Your request for order cancellation and refund will be considered authentic or invalid, depending on its legitimacy. Consider the following scenario: you cancel your order after 30 minutes, even though the estimated delivery time was between 30-45 minutes. Even though 30 minutes is an extended period, it is still less than the estimated time.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">It is unlikely that Uber Eats would reimburse your cancellation fee if you were already aware of the situation and then changed your mind. Unless the delivery timeframe is acceptable to you, there is no need to order with us. If the food arrives much later than expected, you have the option to cancel the order and receive a refund. In the best-case scenario, the company would issue you a full refund, a complimentary lunch, or most likely a promo voucher for the same amount of money.</span></p>
<hr>
<p> </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>The danger of a single story summary in 350 words</title>
        <author>
            <name>Uddipan Barman</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://www.bibarud.com/the-danger-of-a-single-story-summary-in-350-words/"/>
        <id>https://www.bibarud.com/the-danger-of-a-single-story-summary-in-350-words/</id>
            <category term="Summary"/>

        <updated>2021-07-05T01:27:12+05:30</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://www.bibarud.com/media/posts/16/name-3.jpeg" alt="The danger of a single story summary in 350 words" />
                    The TED Talk by Chimamanda Ngozi Adichie in July 2009 focuses on&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://www.bibarud.com/media/posts/16/name-3.jpeg" alt="The danger of a single story summary in 350 words" />
                <p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="10">The TED Talk by Chimamanda Ngozi Adichie in July 2009 focuses on the dangers of the "single storey" and locates the origin of these stories. Adichie thinks that single stories start from basic misconceptions or a lack of awareness of others, but these stories may also be used maliciously to discriminate against other communities (Adichie). Even as children, people are impressionable and vulnerable to individual stories (Adichie 01:43). Adichie states that the media and literature readily available to the public tell only one story, leading to stereotypes and generalisations.</p>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="11">"In particular, she explains why generalisations are made." Coupled with the idea that everyone from Africa comes from a poor, suffering background, her college roommate had a "default posture" of "well-meaning sympathy" towards her (04:49). Adichie also obviously blames herself for falling prey to the "one tale" craze, much like others. Because of the extensive media emphasis on Mexican immigration, she has absorbed the idea that all Mexicans are immigrants (Adichie 08:53). However, just one storey can not characterise a whole group of individuals.</p>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="12">Political and cultural powers have an impact on storytelling as well.Story-spreading power holds ideas over time as well. "Managing 'how stories are told, who tells them, when they're told, and how many stories are told' can be exploited for malintent" (09:25). Adichie's journey to Mexico is a good representation of how power is often utilised to mislead people about others. And, moreover, important western stories have contributed to the marginalisation of people like Adichie, as foreigners are not part of their experiences. Adichie uses the first story she wrote to portray people of all races enjoying playing in the snow (Adichie 00:39). "When she came across African writers, that freed her from having a singular story of what books are and from being another victim of biased literature" (02:36).</p>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="13">To give an overall summary, Adichie simply says that "you portray people as one thing, as only one thing, and that is what they eventually become" (09:25). Her conclusion asserts that propagating a variety of stories against promoting one narrative is vital. She maintains that rejecting single-story phenomena is necessary to perceive humans as more than just an incomplete idea. (Adichie 18:17).</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Dust of Snow: English Class 10 NCERT (First Flight) Summary, Question &amp; Answers</title>
        <author>
            <name>Uddipan Barman</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://www.bibarud.com/dust-of-snow-english-summary-question-and-answers/"/>
        <id>https://www.bibarud.com/dust-of-snow-english-summary-question-and-answers/</id>
            <category term="Summary"/>

        <updated>2021-07-06T00:35:08+05:30</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://www.bibarud.com/media/posts/15/name-1.jpeg" alt="" />
                     Dust of Snow Summary When a crow moved near a hemlock,&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://www.bibarud.com/media/posts/15/name-1.jpeg" alt="" />
                <div class="post__toc">
<h3>Table of Contents</h3>
<ul>
<li><a href="#mcetoc_1f9a6g0pg4g">Dust of Snow Summary</a></li>
<li><a href="#mcetoc_1f9a6g0pg4h">Dust of Snow Question &amp; Answers</a></li>
</ul>
</div>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1f9a6g0pg4g">Dust of Snow Summary</h2>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="8">When a crow moved near a hemlock, it powdered the poet with snow. He realised he was having a horrible day. The poet's mood shifts from bitter to delight when he touches the snow, which is cold and velvety to the touch. People of all ages and backgrounds can benefit from being outside in nature, despite its unpredictable nature. Other trees, such as oak, maple, or pine, were not preferred by Robert Frost. When it comes to poison and toxicity, hemlocks are often associated with them.</p>
<p data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="8"><strong>Also Read</strong>: <a href="https://www.bibarud.com/the-danger-of-a-single-story-summary-in-350-words/">The danger of a single story summary in 350 words</a></p>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="9">It is the message of this poetry that there are no trivial things in life. Our lives can be transformed by even the most simple events. It also demonstrates how, by viewing things in a positive light, we may influence the outcome of our lives. Do not doubt those small acts of kindness we perform on a daily basis, and how they can brighten someone's day and even influence their future.</p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1f9a6g0pg4h" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="9">Dust of Snow Question &amp; Answers</h2>
<p><strong>Q1. What exactly is "snow dust"?What does the poet say has changed his mood? How has the poet’s mood changed? </strong></p>
<p><strong>Ans</strong>: "Snow dust" is made up of snowflakes. For the poet, the particles were "dust." The poet was angry as particles of snow landed on him. Instantly, the poet's attitude to his own mind was altered, and his day improved.</p>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="12"><strong>Q 2. How does Frost present nature in this poem? The following questions may help you to think of an answer.</strong></p>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="13"><strong>(i) What are the birds that are usually named in poems? Do you think the crow is often mentioned in poems? What images come to your mind when you think of a crow?</strong></p>
<p data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="13"><strong>Ans</strong>: The birds mentioned above can be found in a lot of the poetry.Crows are generally viewed as signs of doom and fear. They are often used for criticism.</p>
<p data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="13"><strong>(ii) Again, what is "a hemlock tree"? Why doesn’t the poet write about a more ‘beautiful’ tree, such as a maple, or an oak, or a pine?</strong></p>
<p data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="13"><strong>Ans</strong>: Trees are viewed as great creatures that teach wisdom, as they are too old. The absorbance of all negative energy is connected to the emission of oxygen. But certain trees are poisonous, like the hemlock tree. To evoke a sorrowful atmosphere, the poet avoids mentioning more lovely trees such as maple, oak, or pine. He refers to the hemlock tree, which is deadly, as being "poisonous".</p>
<p data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="13"><strong>(iii) What do the ‘crow’ and ‘hemlock’ represent — joy or sorrow? What does the dust of snow that the crow shakes off a hemlock tree stand for?</strong></p>
<p data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="13"><strong>Ans</strong>: The crow and the hemlock tree symbolise sorrow. Frost employed both crows and the hemlock tree to bring about positivity and vigour to his day. By excluding such birds and trees, the poet has endeavoured to shatter our beliefs about various types of natural agents. He has tried to convince us that we view the world as we like it to be. When a crow flies into a hemlock tree, everyone benefits. The snow dust stands for gladness.</p>
<p data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="9"> </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>A Thing of Beauty Summary in 250 Words Class 12 English 2021</title>
        <author>
            <name>Uddipan Barman</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://www.bibarud.com/a-thing-of-beauty-summary/"/>
        <id>https://www.bibarud.com/a-thing-of-beauty-summary/</id>
            <category term="Summary"/>

        <updated>2021-07-06T00:34:23+05:30</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://www.bibarud.com/media/posts/14/A-Thing-of-Beauty-Summary.jpg" alt="" />
                    The legendary poet John Keats wrote the poem A Thing of Beauty.
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://www.bibarud.com/media/posts/14/A-Thing-of-Beauty-Summary.jpg" alt="" />
                <p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="4">The legendary poet John Keats wrote the poem A Thing of Beauty. According to the poet's explanation in the poem, lovely things provide enormous joy and delight. The poet also speaks about God's numerous creations, all of which we should be able to appreciate. This is due to the fact that these wonderful things give us a plethora of reasons to be joyful. Beauty, according to the poet, is a celestial tonic and an everlasting spring of nectar that never runs dry.</p>
<p data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="4"><strong>Also Read</strong>: <a href="https://www.bibarud.com/the-portrait-of-a-lady-summary-hornbill/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">The Portrait of a Lady Summary (Hornbill)</a></p>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="5">A Thing of Beauty teaches us about the importance of beautiful things that are all around us and the importance of cherishing those things. There are a variety of species in our environment that help to keep our world alive. The forests are abundant with beautiful musk rose blossoms, and the running streams of water give a refreshing breeze throughout the hot summer months. It is also important to remember the wonderful and inspiring stories of the courageous troops who served our country. These valiant soldiers risk their lives and make the ultimate sacrifice to protect others.</p>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="true" data-paragraphid="6">Seeing such lovely things serves as an encouragement for all of us to keep living our lives. They make life worth living. Life would be really difficult if we did not have access to these wonderful things.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Windows 11: When it will be released, how much it will cost, and everything you need to know.</title>
        <author>
            <name>Uddipan Barman</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://www.bibarud.com/windows-11-details/"/>
        <id>https://www.bibarud.com/windows-11-details/</id>
            <category term="Tech"/>

        <updated>2021-06-28T22:18:01+05:30</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://www.bibarud.com/media/posts/13/Windows-11.jpg" alt="Windows 11" />
                     Windows has always existed to serve as a platform for the&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://www.bibarud.com/media/posts/13/Windows-11.jpg" alt="Windows 11" />
                <div class="post__toc">
<h3>Table of Contents</h3>
<ul>
<li><a href="#mcetoc_1f99oacrd1f">The Microsoft Store has been redesigned for Windows 11.</a></li>
<li><a href="#mcetoc_1f99oacrd1g">Windows 11 updates will be smaller and more efficient than previous versions of Windows.</a></li>
<li><a href="#mcetoc_1f99oacrd1h">The process of upgrading to Windows 11</a>
<ul>
<li><a href="#mcetoc_1f99oacrd1i">Requirements for Windows 11</a></li>
</ul>
</li>
<li><a href="#mcetoc_1f99oacrd1j">Is it possible that Windows 11 will be made available for free?</a></li>
<li><a href="#mcetoc_1f99oacrd1k">Conclusion</a></li>
</ul>
</div>
<p data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="28">Windows has always existed to serve as a platform for the advancement of technology around the world. It has served as the backbone of big corporations, and it is where scrappy startups have grown into household names. Windows was the platform on which the web was born and grew up. For many of us, it was the location where we wrote our first emails, played our first PC games, and wrote our very first line of computer code. Windows is the platform on which people create, interact, learn, and achieve their goals - a platform on which more than a billion people rely today.</p>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="30">In his keynote address, Microsoft CEO Satya Nadella stated that Windows 11 is an open platform that allows developers to do whatever they want with their apps. Specifically, Nadella is referring to third-party payment systems that will help developers grow their companies with Windows 11. One of their primary attractions is the fact that there is no commission on transactions made through their payment system — something that Apple strongly opposes and feels renders the platform more vulnerable to spyware and viruses.</p>
<figure class="post__image"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://www.bibarud.com/media/posts/13/MicrosoftTeams-image-1-1024x683-min.png" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" srcset="https://www.bibarud.com/media/posts/13/responsive/MicrosoftTeams-image-1-1024x683-min-xs.png 300w ,https://www.bibarud.com/media/posts/13/responsive/MicrosoftTeams-image-1-1024x683-min-sm.png 480w ,https://www.bibarud.com/media/posts/13/responsive/MicrosoftTeams-image-1-1024x683-min-md.png 768w ,https://www.bibarud.com/media/posts/13/responsive/MicrosoftTeams-image-1-1024x683-min-lg.png 1024w"  alt="" width="1024" height="683"></figure>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1f99oacrd1f" class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="31">The Microsoft Store has been redesigned for Windows 11.</h2>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="32">A new app store is being developed by Microsoft as part of the Windows 11 operating system, which is one of the most significant revelations thus far. The new Microsoft Store app has a more fluid user interface that matches the rest of Windows 11, but that isn't the most notable improvement. Several policies governing which programmes can be found on the Microsoft Storefront are being revised by the company.</p>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="33">App developers can now submit unpackaged Win32 applications in either.exe or MSI format to the Microsoft Store as a result of the new Microsoft Store.Microsoft does not take a portion of the revenue generated by developers that utilise their own content delivery networks and their own commerce platforms, according to the company. This will make it possible for nearly any software running on the Windows platform to be featured and discovered in the Microsoft Store by end users in the future.</p>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="34">In order to demonstrate to the world that it is serious about the new Microsoft Store initiative, Microsoft says it is adding its own apps, such as Teams, Office, and Visual Studio, to the new Microsoft Store. The company says it hopes that other app developers, such as Mozilla and Adobe, will follow its lead.</p>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="35">Also revealed today by Microsoft is the support for Android apps such as TikTok on Windows 11 and the new Microsoft Store!</p>
<figure class="post__image"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://www.bibarud.com/media/posts/13/WIN_Widgets_Light-Theme_16x9_en-US-1-1024x576-min.png" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" srcset="https://www.bibarud.com/media/posts/13/responsive/WIN_Widgets_Light-Theme_16x9_en-US-1-1024x576-min-xs.png 300w ,https://www.bibarud.com/media/posts/13/responsive/WIN_Widgets_Light-Theme_16x9_en-US-1-1024x576-min-sm.png 480w ,https://www.bibarud.com/media/posts/13/responsive/WIN_Widgets_Light-Theme_16x9_en-US-1-1024x576-min-md.png 768w ,https://www.bibarud.com/media/posts/13/responsive/WIN_Widgets_Light-Theme_16x9_en-US-1-1024x576-min-lg.png 1024w"  alt="" width="1024" height="576"></figure>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1f99oacrd1g" class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="36">Windows 11 updates will be smaller and more efficient than previous versions of Windows.</h2>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="37">In addition, Microsoft promises that Windows 11 provides a 40 percent performance gain and that Windows updates will be lower in size and will continue to run in the background. In other words, you can carry on with your work while the computer is being updated in the background.</p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1f99oacrd1h" class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="38">The process of upgrading to Windows 11</h2>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="39">If you want to upgrade to Windows 11 after it becomes available, you must first go into the settings of your PC or laptop that is running Windows 10. Navigate to Update &amp; Security, and then click on Windows Update to complete the process. By clicking on this button, you will be able to see if there have been any updates. If a feature update to Windows 11 is available, you will notice an update that says "Feature update to Windows 11." Select Download and install from the drop-down menu.</p>
<h3 id="mcetoc_1f99oacrd1i" class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="40">Requirements for Windows 11</h3>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="41">Windows 11 is a high-end operating system, similar to Apple's macOS in terms of features. The fact that it works with a wide range of hardware is what sets it apart from macOS. There are numerous original equipment manufacturers (OEMs) that ship Windows on their PCs, laptops, convertibles, and other devices. And it is for this reason that Microsoft must have a set of requirements in order for its operating system to deliver on its claims.</p>
<figure class="post__image"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://www.bibarud.com/media/posts/13/WIN_Teams_Integration_16x9_en-US-1-1024x576-min.png" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" srcset="https://www.bibarud.com/media/posts/13/responsive/WIN_Teams_Integration_16x9_en-US-1-1024x576-min-xs.png 300w ,https://www.bibarud.com/media/posts/13/responsive/WIN_Teams_Integration_16x9_en-US-1-1024x576-min-sm.png 480w ,https://www.bibarud.com/media/posts/13/responsive/WIN_Teams_Integration_16x9_en-US-1-1024x576-min-md.png 768w ,https://www.bibarud.com/media/posts/13/responsive/WIN_Teams_Integration_16x9_en-US-1-1024x576-min-lg.png 1024w"  alt="" width="1024" height="576"></figure>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="42">The following are the minimum system requirements for Windows 11:</p>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="43"><strong>Processor </strong>-You must have a processor or System on a Chip (SoC) with a clock speed of at least 1GHz, two cores, and a 64-bit architecture in order to run the programme. This includes, among other things, virtually all of Intel's Core, Pentium, and Evo chipsets, as well as AMD's Ryzen chipsets.</p>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="44"><strong>Ram-</strong>The amount of RAM available on your computer should be at least 4GB in order to run Windows 11. If your old computer only has 2GB of RAM, you will be unable to install Windows 11, and you will be forced to either purchase a new computer or physically upgrade the RAM on your existing computer.</p>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="45"><strong>Storage </strong>- A minimum of 64GB of available storage space is required for your PC. I believe it is a rather minor need, so most old PCs and laptops should be able to meet it.</p>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="46"><strong>System firmware</strong> - Your PC must be equipped with UEFI and Secure Boot in order to run Windows 11. Although identical to BIOS in appearance, UEFI serves an important function in the connection of a computer's firmware to its operating system. In computing, Secure Boot is a collection of programmes that determines whether or not your operating system is secure when it is running on a computer.</p>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="47"><strong>Graphics card</strong> - Windows 11, Microsoft recommends DirectX 12 compliant graphics cards that are also equipped with WDDM 2.x. Nearly all graphics cards from Intel, Nvidia, and AMD that have recently been released support DirectX 12, but you should double-check whether your PC is equipped with a compatible graphics card. Don't be concerned; you won't have to do anything to achieve this, and I'll explain more about it later.</p>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="48"><strong>Display </strong>-Your computer's screen must be at least 9 inches in size and have a high definition (720p) resolution. Most laptops have screens that are either 14-inch or 15.6-inch in size, and monitors are available in a variety of sizes that are all larger than 9-inch, so the display on your old PC should not be a problem.</p>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="49"><strong>Internet access</strong> -In addition to downloading Windows 11 onto your computer, you will want access to the internet in order to activate it. Only Windows 10 customers who have purchased a legitimate copy of the operating system are eligible to download Windows 11.</p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1f99oacrd1j" class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="50">Is it possible that Windows 11 will be made available for free?</h2>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="51">Windows 11 will be available for free download as well, but only to those who already have a valid copy of Windows 10 installed on their machines. Microsoft has stated that the distribution will begin somewhere in November and will continue through the end of the decade. It's possible to test Windows 11 beta versions until the final version is published if you join the Windows Insider Program, but this will need you to wait for a long time.</p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1f99oacrd1k" class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="52">Conclusion</h2>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="53">Windows is more than simply an operating system; it's a fabric that is woven into our daily lives and our professional lives as well. There, we meet new people and study as well as work and play. It's a great place to be. It has grown known to us and has been modified to our needs over time. It's an exciting time for Windows users right now because the operating system has to be optimised on a general level.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>The Portrait of a Lady Summary (Hornbill)</title>
        <author>
            <name>Uddipan Barman</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://www.bibarud.com/the-portrait-of-a-lady-summary-hornbill/"/>
        <id>https://www.bibarud.com/the-portrait-of-a-lady-summary-hornbill/</id>
            <category term="Summary"/>

        <updated>2021-06-28T02:54:46+05:30</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://www.bibarud.com/media/posts/12/Crello-Free-Graphic-Design-Software-Simple-Online-Photo-Editor.png" alt="The Portrait of a Lady Summary (Hornbill)" />
                    The Author Says: In the two decades that I had known my&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://www.bibarud.com/media/posts/12/Crello-Free-Graphic-Design-Software-Simple-Online-Photo-Editor.png" alt="The Portrait of a Lady Summary (Hornbill)" />
                <h2 data-changed="true" data-paragraphid="33">The Author Says:</h2>
<p class="dropcap" data-changed="true" data-paragraphid="33">In the two decades that I had known my grandmother, she had developed prominent wrinkles and a frailer figure. Many stated she had once been young and lovely, and there was no question that she had even had a spouse, but those claims were difficult to accept. My grandfather's photo was prominently displayed over the fireplace in the drawing room. He was wearing a large turban and loose-fitting clothing, and he was several decades older than he looked. He seemed as if he could only have as many grandkids as there were grains of sand on the beach.</p>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="true" data-paragraphid="34">I had nearly thrown up when I thought about my grandmother being young and attractive. "I got my own room one day, and it was one of the best things that had happened to me." Their bond was torn apart as their friendship shattered." The quote from The Annals of Sanness goes like this: "I would try to pass on to her English words and ideas about western science and learning, including the law of gravity, Archimedes' Principle, and the globe being round. After feeding the sparrows, she had a well-deserved rest in the afternoon. As she sat in the veranda, she would give out handfuls of nuts to the birds. She used to consider the twenty minutes from five to seven p.m. as the happiest part of her day. A significant change in her personality occurred through the evening.</p>
<p data-changed="true" data-paragraphid="34"><strong>Also Read: </strong><a href="https://www.bibarud.com/a-thing-of-beauty-summary/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">A Thing of Beauty Summary</a></p>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="true" data-paragraphid="35">She had not prayed. The next morning she was stricken with illness. She lay in bed quietly praying and telling her beads. She told us that her death was approaching even before we could stop her. She stated she wasn't going to waste any more time talking to us because she hadn't prayed just a few hours before the end of her last chapter of life.</p>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="true" data-paragraphid="36">Suspect's lips froze, and the rosary slipped from her lifeless fingers. We realised she was gone when a peaceful pallor came across her face. Thousands of sparrows sat on the verandah and in her room, straight up to where she lay dead and rigid draped in a scarlet shroud.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Grounding for the Metaphysics of Morals Summary (All Chapters)</title>
        <author>
            <name>Uddipan Barman</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://www.bibarud.com/grounding-for-the-metaphysics-of-morals-summary-all-chapters/"/>
        <id>https://www.bibarud.com/grounding-for-the-metaphysics-of-morals-summary-all-chapters/</id>
            <category term="Summary"/>

        <updated>2021-06-04T01:26:13+05:30</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://www.bibarud.com/media/posts/10/Blog-Banner-560x315-px-Custom-dimensions.jpeg" alt="Grounding for the Metaphysics of Morals Summary (All Chapters)" />
                     Key Points A good majority of our core views about the&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://www.bibarud.com/media/posts/10/Blog-Banner-560x315-px-Custom-dimensions.jpeg" alt="Grounding for the Metaphysics of Morals Summary (All Chapters)" />
                <div class="post__toc">
<h3>Table of Contents</h3>
<ul>
<li><a href="#mcetoc_1f78ga7p0i0">Key Points</a></li>
<li><a href="#mcetoc_1f78ga7p0i1">Preface</a></li>
<li><a href="#mcetoc_1f78ga7p0i2">Chapter 1</a></li>
<li><a href="#mcetoc_1f78ga7p0i3">Chapter 2</a>
<ul>
<li><a href="#mcetoc_1f78ga7p0i4">Part 1</a></li>
<li><a href="#mcetoc_1f78ga7p0i5">Part 2</a></li>
</ul>
</li>
<li><a href="#mcetoc_1f78ga7p0i6">Chapter 3</a></li>
</ul>
</div>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1f78ga7p0i0">Key Points</h2>
<ul>
<li class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="9">A good majority of our core views about the universe are previous notions that we possess a priori in the Critique of Pure Reason, which Kant referred to as a 'philosophical precept.'</li>
<li class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="10">Kant said: One of the most important arguments in Kant's Metaphysics of Morals is on the subject of theft.</li>
<li class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="11">It is a paradox in a culture where property rights exist when one steals, as one expects others to recognise one's ownership of the property they took.</li>
<li class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="12">We can not count on the concept of free will to tell us what is right and wrong. Moral behaviour is within everyone's grasp of reason, not only humanity's, and hence we must rely on rationality to decide what is moral.</li>
<li class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="13">The need for unconditional validity, which evolved as a result of this, resulted in the introduction of the moral law and the Categorical Imperative, because freedom will inevitably be accompanied by freedom.</li>
</ul>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1f78ga7p0i1">Preface</h2>
<p class="root-block-node dropcap" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="10">In the Critique of Pure Reason, Kant claimed that a great number of our basic beliefs about the world are previous concepts that we possess a priori. In this work, Kant presents an argument on moral philosophy along similar lines. In this instance, he outlines basic concepts of moral thought that occur to us even when they aren't relevant to the circumstances. In other words, Kant believes that if you want to understand morality, you must begin with "pure," a priori ideas of reason.As far as Kant is concerned, moral thoughts may be universally legitimate only if they are grounded on a prior concept of cognition.</p>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="11">The Preface to this book was published by Oxford University Press, which is priced at $19.99. According to Kant, we should not take human nature into consideration when we determine morality. Some critics of Kant have contested his claim to present a comprehensive moral philosophy that is founded solely on rational thinking. According to Kant, a morality founded on rational thinking will be embraced by everyone; it will be better than one supported by one particular group of people. Some philosophers contend that we do not act on our values because we can not understand morality in its entirety; yet, researchers who study ethics report that we use intuition instead of analysis to discern what moral courses of action are.</p>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="12">It is simply because what makes sense to us is mostly derived from beliefs and misconceptions we learn from our parents and our local communities. Kant only only presents one instance of a moral principle with universal validity; this is to say that grounding the Metaphysics of Morals is the only instance of this. Additional examples and definitions of moral concepts will be provided in the subsequent chapters. There are two terms in German that both mean "man" — one is for man in the sense of a male adult, while the other is for man in the generic sense.</p>
<hr>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1f78ga7p0i2">Chapter 1</h2>
<p class="root-block-node dropcap" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="3">Good will is one of the only things in the world that is completely unambiguous, according to Kant. Promising something that can not be kept is an example of an activity that violates this moral norm, he explains. Regardless of whether they are uneducated or unskilled, everyone exhibits this ability to follow the moral rules in their daily life, he notes. While Hegel stated that Kant's philosophy was too abstract to be of value, the Austrian philosopher and 19th-century classicist Hegel also maintained that our thinking is organised by the ideas, institutions, and traditions of the community in which we live. He also disagreed with Kant's view, which holds that you can't know whether or not someone's behaviour will appear self-contradictory until you know something about their society.</p>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="4">Kant: One of the major arguments in Kant's Metaphysics of Morals is about theft. In a society where there are property rights, it is paradoxical to steal because you expect others to accept your ownership of what you have stolen. On the other hand, we can only envisage a new family structure in which affairs would not be regarded as unethical. To begin with, morality is not something for automatons living a life of pure rational thought. The ability to overlook personal desires in order to support and maintain communal values is of relevance to human beings, who are called upon to compromise their personal interests in various circumstances. Kant's critics, however, have instead said that while Hegel is correct in believing that social institutions play a crucial part in influencing our beliefs, he neglects to recognise how entrenched established norms, values, and beliefs can be. The notions of instinct and self-preservation had been accepted by the scientific community even before Darwin presented his thesis.</p>
<hr>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1f78ga7p0i3" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="4">Chapter 2</h2>
<h3 id="mcetoc_1f78ga7p0i4" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="4">Part 1</h3>
<p class="root-block-node dropcap" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="5">It is nearly rare to identify any instances of people carrying out their tasks just out of a sense of responsibility. Nearly everything we see may be explained by some motivation other than doing the right thing because it is the right thing to do. This idea that people behave as they do for no other reason than a need for self-preservation may be accurate at first glance, but we can not ever be sure whether there is some hidden motivation influencing their actions. It is critical to have a more complete knowledge of a priori moral conceptions, especially when competing goals and motivations attempt to weaken our moral sense. All categorical imperatives incorporate only intrinsic and universal factors, such as universal validity, and do not take into consideration any situational factors. As a result, the only viable categorical imperative is that actions must follow a requirement of universal validity.</p>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="6">People who routinely disregard their duties in each and every circumstance, such as when they accept the objective validity of the law and then seek an exception to it, are involved in a contradictory state of affairs; accepting the objective validity of the law, they desire an exception to it. To conclude the discussion in chapter 2, Kant mentions his ongoing work and asserts that an enhanced comprehension of principles of morality might further bolster our moral instincts. The standard view, as argued in the Critique of Pure Reason, is that it would be impossible for us to deduce our concept of cause from our observations of the world. For Kant, causality is an a priori concept. He refers to it as a thought that comes to us as a result of mental processing that happens prior to our thinking about it. In a similar vein, we must emphasise that while causation is too fundamental an idea to be derived from experience, our moral beliefs are much more foundational.</p>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="7">In reference to concrete examples from our personal experiences However, this doesn't mean that a lack of moral motivation or pure moral acts doesn't exist, just like the notion of a lack of moral motivation or pure moral deeds. The chapter's objective is to clarify and improve our knowledge of the absolute moral requirements that the law lays on us. Insofar as one accepts Kant's theory of ethical demands, one must accept "categorical imperatives" as his definition of moral law. In order for an a priori imperative to be valid, it must be independent of any circumstantial reasons. The categorical imperative can neither dictate that you should or must do something in a certain situation nor tell you not to do it.</p>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="8">Consequently, your activity is not applicable to everyone; it is partial and hypocritical, according to Kant. The categorical imperative is substantially the same as what we discussed in Chapter 1 of moral law. When it comes to each case, each person is obligated to decide on the path of action that appears most credible. The categorical imperative is an interesting philosophical experiment that attempts to base moral judgments on the assertion that contradiction is illogical. Despite this, Kant's formula does not seem to describe the complexity of moral concerns quite well.</p>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="9">The second part of Chapter 2 is concerned with Kant's second formulation of the categorical imperative, and in it, he restates his value-theoretic account of it, with a focus on the intrinsic worth of every single unique human being. He argues that although the notions of God, free will, and immortality are natural notions of reason, they are not tangible objects of sensory experience. Kant's observation that our conception of God originates in our notion of moral perfection is more evidence of his views on religion. Kant: We can only have a concept of moral perfection, and so a thought of God, if we already have a concept of moral perfection. These concepts were perceived as controversial by many of Kant's contemporaries. It was decreed by the Prussian government that no more writings on religious topics would be published.</p>
<h3 id="mcetoc_1f78ga7p0i5" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="9">Part 2</h3>
<p class="root-block-node dropcap" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="5">Such entities have agency, and they may make decisions about their goals and the methods they will use to achieve them. Merely hypothetical imperatives will always be the basis for ending desires that are founded on physical necessities or wants. While the categorical imperative may be founded on anything that is an "end in itself" — something that serves just itself and not another goal, want, or want — there may be other possible reasons for its existence, such as providing security and confidence to its creator. To understand the context of an action is essential for rational decision-making, and to pursue aims, rational individuals must think of themselves as means and as ends as well. When rational humans engage in something purely for the sake of obligation, they must relinquish all personal interests and incentives, other than obligation. A basic principle of morality is to only act in accordance with those principles and motivations that are conducive to establishing a kingdom of goals.</p>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="6">Compassion is required to steer our intent toward beneficial goals. It must never contradict itself; its acts must demonstrate the fundamental value of universal principles of reason. It is the idea that people, as ends in themselves, have an inherent, absolute value—that they possess "dignity" When a person has faith in the nobility of morality, he or she will consider serving as a lawmaker in the kingdom of the end to be honourable. According to this conception of a perfect community in which all citizens follow the rules of objective reason, it must result in the "kingdom of ends." No empirical standards can form the basis of morality, as they are always reliant on the perspective of the observer. In each unique case, the will is self-determining; and the principle of the action is true only in the particular situation. Kant only elaborates on the topic in Chapter 3, revealing that morality may be founded on the concept of free will.</p>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="7">But even this Kantian argument is merely a 'grounding' for the metaphysics of morals, and not a full metaphysics, or even a complete investigation of the nature of 'practical' (i.e., moral) reason and its role in our lives. According to Kant, if you expect other people to accept your objectives, you must recognise the reality that other people think of themselves as more than just a means to other objectives. Many individuals have a basic understanding of morality, thus his main concept connects effectively with the vast majority of people. Using people or taking advantage of others out of self-interest is fundamentally immoral, since doing so breaks our belief that humans are not mere objects we may use as we like. While Kant first argued that the law only becomes true if it is comprehensible to those who must obey it, democracies are more concerned with rational argument. According to Kant, even though the concepts of "autonomy" and of a "kingdom of ends" are ideal concepts, it is nevertheless unrealistic to expect these concepts to appear in the real world.</p>
<hr>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1f78ga7p0i6" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="4">Chapter 3</h2>
<p class="root-block-node dropcap" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="5">Moral behaviour is in the realm of everyone's rational thinking, not only the thoughts of humanity, and thus, we can not rely our ideas of morality on the concept of free will. If it proves this from personal experience, it would be almost tough to prove, believes the philosopher. When it comes to concepts such as reality, he asserts that everyone is different, meaning there will be variability in each person's point of view on the "sensible" world. However, to everyone, he stresses that the concepts of sense are comprehensible. "The Sensible World" is how the world seems to us on a day-to-day basis. Human beings may know about themselves by one of two possible means: through the physical senses or by logic.</p>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="6">The problem is that people don't actually live in an intelligent world and have an "independent" will, which is enslaved by the influences of society. It is, however, important to bear in mind that their acts would be governed by the laws of nature and the rules of cause and effect. It can't be denied that both ideas can not be completely described, and that the contradiction between them can't be reconciled, he says. He says that "the nature of things as appearances is ruled by necessity," and that "what things are in themselves is ruled by freedom." The categorical imperative can be paraphrased as a "ought" statement: We all know that we ought to have a pure will.</p>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="7">One could go as far as to say that the comprehensible world can't produce anything that could be used as a target for action. The greatest explanation for this phenomenon can be found in the idea that the world of appearances is controlled by causation, yet this does not mean that we can not be free as objects in ourselves. If the fact that we are free was the result of using our intellect, then that freedom would not be really free, for freedom is supposed to be unconditional. There is nothing more that we can accomplish than to acknowledge the boundaries of our understanding and accept the implications of the concept of freedom. This is the only moral and ethical justification we have: that moral ideas and the categorical imperative need to be supported by the concept of freedom.</p>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="8">This story was written by the author of "A Farewell to Man". A secular concept of reason (rather than a transcendent God) has taken the role of God in Kant's system, but the classifications remain intact: spirit is good, body is bad. If people can overcome their cravings for the physical world and follow spiritual precepts, they are truly free. In an effort to live by free will, he says that we must be able to establish our own law. "My concept of freedom offers a foundation—a basis for morality. I say this because ", he states. The demand for unconditional validity, which arose as a result of this, brought about the moral law and the Categorical Imperative, because freedom must naturally lead to freedom.</p>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="9">Though knowing that freedom gives rise to morality is not the same as knowing why we desire to be moral, one can come to see that truth in both of these approaches. According to Kant, it is impossible to prove that we are free through rational analysis. It is possible to say that every occurrence can be explained by an earlier occurrence, but this is merely a property of the world of appearances. Causal determinism is therefore not the final word for us, since we are already objects in themselves. Our sense that we are free may be correct, regardless of the circumstances.</p>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="10">However, there is no logical refutation of our concept of freedom, is there? We are in favour of maximising our freedom by adhering to the categorical imperative. In Kant's view, the ultimate test of freedom is being able to obey our own most pressing demands and desires. Kant's conception of freedom may not seem convincing to some thinkers. Since morality inherently includes restraining our selfish tendencies in ways that benefit the greater welfare of humanity, it follows that a fundamental characteristic of morality is virtue.</p>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="11">While it may be disputed whether Kant's theories are correct, there is at least some evidence to support his claim that the theory of morality fits the ordinary moral intuitions of people. Despite his strict adherence to rationalism, Kant's moral philosophy is no more restrictive than any other, notes Zafar Hussain.</p>
<hr>
<p data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="11"> </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>The origin of language summary under 300 words</title>
        <author>
            <name>Uddipan Barman</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://www.bibarud.com/the-origin-of-language-summary/"/>
        <id>https://www.bibarud.com/the-origin-of-language-summary/</id>
            <category term="Summary"/>

        <updated>2021-06-04T01:26:19+05:30</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://www.bibarud.com/media/posts/7/The-Origin-of-Language-Summary-under-300-words.jpg" alt="The origin of language summary" />
                    Key Points According to the Ding-dong hypothesis, small or pointy things are&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://www.bibarud.com/media/posts/7/The-Origin-of-Language-Summary-under-300-words.jpg" alt="The origin of language summary" />
                <h2 data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="3">Key Points</h2>
<ul>
<li class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="6">According to the Ding-dong hypothesis, small or pointy things are named with words with high front vowels, whereas large or circular things have a round vowel at the end of the word.</li>
<li class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="7">In recognition of his teacher, Noam Chomsky, Nim Chimpsky was named after him.</li>
<li class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="8">This 2009 study published in Nature appears to support the hypothesis.</li>
<li class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="9">When this gene is mutated, it disrupts language and animals can't.</li>
<li class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="10">The scientist, Dean Falk, posits that as early humans lost their fur, carrying kids became more difficult.</li>
</ul>
<p class="dropcap" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="3">Languages are a core component of human society. The Linguistic Society of Paris prohibited discourse on the topic in 1886 and did not recant it for several years. No other species has the vocal pathology needed to talk like we do. No animal has demonstrated any competence above the level of a two-year-old human. In order to talk like a person, a creature must have a person's brain, voice chords, and intelligence.</p>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="4">Theory that humans developed to copy and mimic sounds Pooh-pooh believes that humans made all of the earliest words. Primitive people used their tongues to mimic hand gestures and words then emerged from that. Another, much earlier view states that language is a God-given capacity. Genesis says that the first man and woman, Adam and Eve, were able to comprehend what God said to them and converse in the same language.</p>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="5">For many years, people spoke the same language until the uprising of Babel. Animals will never be able to speak. It appears we can communicate with human-like speech but apes can not. Project Washoe tested if a chimpanzee could learn language in the 1960s. Project Nim was less regulated than the man in charge, Herbert S Terrace.</p>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="6">He decided that they were never able to use the indicators properly. Terrace claims a genetic mutation allowed our ancestors to communicate and grasp language. Chimpanzees have an important gene for language and speech development, FOXP2, which differs from humans. Maybe this one gene's mutation caused other species to become extinct? Another hypothesis is that because human societies became larger, people required an effective grooming method to maintain friendly relationships with others. the continuity theory that it arose from pre-linguistic sounds</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Is there still potential to earn money from the internet in 2021?</title>
        <author>
            <name>Uddipan Barman</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://www.bibarud.com/is-there-still-potential-to-earn-money-from-the-internet/"/>
        <id>https://www.bibarud.com/is-there-still-potential-to-earn-money-from-the-internet/</id>

        <updated>2021-06-02T16:33:28+05:30</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://www.bibarud.com/media/posts/3/Bibarud.jpg" alt="" />
                     Recently the web hosting business has been booming in the technological&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://www.bibarud.com/media/posts/3/Bibarud.jpg" alt="" />
                <div data-mobiledoc="{&quot;version&quot;:&quot;0.3.2&quot;,&quot;atoms&quot;:[],&quot;cards&quot;:[],&quot;markups&quot;:[],&quot;sections&quot;:[[1,&quot;p&quot;,[[0,[],0,&quot;Recently the web hosting business has been booming in the technological space. New individuals and enterprises are appearing online. Everyone wants to have a name for themselves or their business in the internet world. And it">
<div>
<p>Recently the web hosting business has been booming in the technological space. New individuals and enterprises are appearing online. Everyone wants to have a name for themselves or their business in the internet world. And it's also worth being on the internet as physically, no person or brand can reach such a vast amount of audience at once.</p>
<p>Many business and individuals have profited from the internet; there is no doubt that the internet has many potentials. It can generate tons of revenue for any brand or individual.</p>
<p>The internet has been growing since the past decade, for the context. In 1995, the internet had only 16 Million users, about 0.4% of the world's population; yeah, 16 million is not a small number, but if you compare it with the users in 2020, i.e. 5,098 Million, which is around 64.7% of the worlds total population it's just unbelievable of how much the internet has gained growth.</p>
<p>And it's not the end; it's just the beginning. The remaining 40% of the world aren't still using the internet. The number of users will be increasing drastically over the upcoming years. As infants would be getting older, they would too become aware of the internet and its uses. There's a lot of potential of earning from the internet in the future.</p>
<div data-mobiledoc="{&quot;version&quot;:&quot;0.3.2&quot;,&quot;atoms&quot;:[],&quot;cards&quot;:[],&quot;markups&quot;:[],&quot;sections&quot;:[[1,&quot;h2&quot;,[[0,[],0,&quot;How easy was earning money from the internet earlier?&quot;]]],[1,&quot;p&quot;,[[0,[],0,&quot;Earning some cash has never been easy in any aspect. The internet is no exception. However, it is relatively easier than physical labour. There were many ways of how people earned from the internet; at first, people use to sell goods and earn from the internet, that">
<div>
<h2>How easy was earning money from the internet earlier?</h2>
<p>Earning some cash has never been easy in any aspect. The internet is no exception. However, it is relatively easier than physical labour. There were many ways of how people earned from the internet; at first, people use to sell goods and earn from the internet, that's how big e-commerce giants like amazon got created, because of the internet.</p>
<p>After that, many business and individuals joined the route seeing such a massive amount of profits. Every brand wanted a piece of cake on the internet. Every brand now has their website where they sell their goods.</p>
<p>But it's not only brands that have earned from the internet; many individuals have earned a lot of money throughout the period.</p>
<p>Earlier, a popular way of earning through the internet was to work or which is known as freelancing for companies and business to create their websites or provide other services.</p>
<p>As there were not many tech-savvy people available earlier, so the ones that knew coding and programming made quite good money through making websites for other individuals and brands.</p>
<p>Even early coders and programmers have the advantage of creating anything on the internet and succeeding in it. They were the first to make such a thing, and no other competition existed.</p>
<h2>How did earning on the internet became so popular?</h2>
<p>As the internet boomed, companies like Google and Facebook started gaining popularity; they introduced user behaviour tracking with the browser and Java scripts' help.</p>
<p>Being able to track the users gave them the advantage to show users ads of businesses. Slowly the tech giants began to earn a lot of revenue from ads alone, becoming prevalent.</p>
<p>Now every business wants to advertise their products not only offline but in online space too. Brands like google introduced services for individuals to show ads on their websites to get paid some revenue. This business model became very popular and is on the rise.</p>
<p>The idea of serving ads of different companies on an individual's blog was a success. It allowed the individuals to focus on their content, which, if it gets ranked on google, generates an outstanding amount of ad revenue.</p>
<p>But with it, there came many advantages and also disadvantages. Benefits were for both the individuals and the big corporates, as for individuals, it became an excellent source of income, and for companies, they could now reach more targeted customers.</p>
<p>The significant disadvantage about ads is that they are targeted to users search and intent, which means ad companies like Google and Facebook are constantly spying on their users and tracking their every search and quarries on the internet, even they have access to the most potent things like location data of users. They knew every bit of information about their users, making the privacy of the users compromised.</p>
<p>As seen recently, there were also many data breaches of users data from these companies, which makes a big concern about users' privacy on the internet.</p>
<p>This article is not focused on the privacy part, which you can find in our other articles. We will now talk about the potential of earning from the internet in today's age.</p>
<h2>How to earn money from the internet in 2021?</h2>
<p>Earning money from the internet is not a new topic; it has been covered by many publications, influencers, and other people, teaching tips and tricks on how to earn money online.</p>
<p>In my personal experience, I have tried doing many things to earn money online; I have tried hard to make pennies from the internet. I used to follow anyone guide of things that I can do to earn money online.</p>
<p>Many experts, or so-called influencers, claim to earn a lot of cash, even in millions, by just doing a simple thing or simply filling up a form or just doing a survey.</p>
<p>People claimed to have installed an app that made them a millionaire by watching ads. That's very funny and serious at the same time. Many people believe in such things and waste their time hoping that they would earn some cash.</p>
<p>These apps and surveys may earn you a tiny amount of money, but they can't make you rich or even fulfil your daily expenses.</p>
<div data-mobiledoc="{&quot;version&quot;:&quot;0.3.2&quot;,&quot;atoms&quot;:[],&quot;cards&quot;:[],&quot;markups&quot;:[],&quot;sections&quot;:[[1,&quot;h2&quot;,[[0,[],0,&quot;The bright and legal ways to earn money online:&quot;]]],[1,&quot;p&quot;,[[0,[],0,&quot;Earning money online has provided a ton of people with their livelihood and supports many businesses to operate.&quot;]]],[1,&quot;p&quot;,[[0,[],0,&quot;There are many ways that people earn from the internet. Lets first talk about the Bright or legal ways to make money online.&quot;]]],[1,&quot;h3&quot;,[[0,[],0,&quot;Blogging + Ads&quot;]]],[1,&quot;p&quot;,[[0,[],0,&quot;I have already mentioned in this article how people are earning a ton of revenue by showing or displaying ads on their blogs or websites.&quot;]]],[1,&quot;p&quot;,[[0,[],0,&quot;There are many ad providers available now on the internet; Google is one of the largest. Google has a program call Ad Sense which helps influencers and blog owners to display the ads provided by google for which they earn revenue.&quot;]]],[1,&quot;p&quot;,[[0,[],0,&quot;There are also alternatives like Media.net, which is a collab between Yahoo and Microsoft. There are options like Pop Ads or Ads Terra available too for different types of blogs.&quot;]]],[1,&quot;p&quot;,[[0,[],0,&quot;These ad companies have their policies according to which they show ads. Some might be showing ads on adult content too, but companies like google have stringent rules, and they maintain the quality of the ads making them the market leader.&quot;]]],[1,&quot;p&quot;,[[0,[],0,&quot;If your thinking of earning money online, you can start a blog and post good content on it; if any of your blog posts rank on Google and have ads enabled on them, you would be earing an outstanding amount of ad revenue.&quot;]]],[1,&quot;h3&quot;,[[0,[],0,&quot;Youtube&quot;]]],[1,&quot;p&quot;,[[0,[],0,&quot;If you are not a good content writer or don">
<div>
<h2>The bright and legal ways to earn money online:</h2>
<p>Earning money online has provided a ton of people with their livelihood and supports many businesses to operate.</p>
<p>There are many ways that people earn from the internet. Lets first talk about the Bright or legal ways to make money online.</p>
<h3>Blogging + Ads</h3>
<p>I have already mentioned in this article how people are earning a ton of revenue by showing or displaying ads on their blogs or websites.</p>
<p>There are many ad providers available now on the internet; Google is one of the largest. Google has a program call Ad Sense which helps influencers and blog owners to display the ads provided by google for which they earn revenue.</p>
<p>There are also alternatives like Media.net, which is a collab between Yahoo and Microsoft. There are options like Pop Ads or Ads Terra available too for different types of blogs.</p>
<p>These ad companies have their policies according to which they show ads. Some might be showing ads on adult content too, but companies like google have stringent rules, and they maintain the quality of the ads making them the market leader.</p>
<p>If your thinking of earning money online, you can start a blog and post good content on it; if any of your blog posts rank on Google and have ads enabled on them, you would be earing an outstanding amount of ad revenue.</p>
<h3>Youtube</h3>
<p>If you are not a good content writer or don't want to spend your time figuring out how to build a blog, choose a hosting plan and get fooled by hosting companies. Then you can try it on Youtube.</p>
<p>Suppose you enjoy your time filming yourself and want to share your thoughts, expertise, or personal life through video and earn revenue from it. Youtube is the best choice for you.</p>
<p>We all are aware of how youtube has changed the lives of many people. People are earning so much and also providing a ton of value to the consumers by their videos.</p>
<p>Youtube is owned by Google, which means it is all managed by Google; you need to create a youtube channel, which you can through your Gmail account and start posting your quality content there.</p>
<p>After you meet the criteria of views and subscribers, you can monetise your videos through google ads and earn an outstanding amount of revenue.</p>
<p>Well, it's not as simple as I make it seem, but you can definitely try it as a hobby first, and if somehow your success in it, you can always choose it over other things.</p>
<h3>Blogging + Membership</h3>
<p>Due to the increasing knowledge of people and raising awareness about tracking f their data to show ads, the Ad situation has been on a slight decline; people now are using adblocking softwares on their devices, making it hard for publishers and individuals to earn from ad revenue.</p>
<p>Still, the ads are very profitable, but there are now new ways for publishers to charge a particular amount of money for allowing users to read or access their content.</p>
<p>Users are not shown ads, and instead, they need to pay a membership fee. This is very beneficial for users as paying for the services eliminates the online ads and trackers, giving a safe and privacy-oriented experience.</p>
<p>However, this has not been so popular as not all users tend to pay for every article they read on a different website, making the internet costly for people.</p>
<p>Blogging platforms like Medium.com have gained success in this model of blogging, as the userbase of Medium.com are more reader-centric and likes to read articles.</p>
<h3>Freelancing</h3>
<p>If you are very good at something and want to earn online from those skills of yours, freelancing can be the thing to do.</p>
<p>If your very good at writing articles, many business and blog owners are looking for content writers for their blogs and publications.</p>
<p>There are websites like freelancer.com or Fiverr.com, where you can list out your skills, and people wanting them will come to you for your work; you would get paid for the job you have done for them.</p>
<p>This was very popular back in the day, it's popular now too, but the situation has changed a lot, as there are increasing in skilled people, there are many options for clients to choose from, because of the harsh competition people are offering services for significantly less amount of money.</p>
<p>They are making it hard for new people to get the opportunity to earn money. However, don't lose hope as experts verified by sites like Fiverr and Upwork tend to get many clients and make a lot of money.</p>
<p>If that's what you're looking to do, build and develop your skills first, maybe get a college degree in the field your good at; that way, you would have the advantage over other people in this field.</p>
<h3>Affiliate Marketing</h3>
<p>Another trendy way to earn money online is to market or promote products of brands, in return for which they provide commission for every product bought.</p>
<p>Affiliate marketing is the most popular way to earn without showing ads on your websites, blogs or youtube videos. You even don't need o own any blog or website or even youtube channel to earn from affiliate marketing.</p>
<p>Though having them may help you to boost your revenue. You can promote products of the brand on any platform; you can even pay for ads to promote those products on social media platforms like Facebook or Instagram and, in return, earn a commission for the purchase made.</p>
<p>That way, you would be able to campaign to a more targeted userbase for your promoted product.</p>
<p>Affiliate marketing has a lot of potentials and will be expanding vastly in the future. But, for doing it correctly, you need some good knowledge about marketing and gaining customers.</p>
<p>It would be better to build an online userbase through any platform; that way, it would be much easier to promote products.</p>
<p>There are also other ways to earn money online, by selling your good and products and much more; these were just a few examples; we would be updating the article as things get different in the future.</p>
<div translate="" data-mobiledoc="{&quot;version&quot;:&quot;0.3.2&quot;,&quot;atoms&quot;:[],&quot;cards&quot;:[],&quot;markups&quot;:[],&quot;sections&quot;:[[1,&quot;h2&quot;,[[0,[],0,&quot;Not so bright and legal ways to earn money online.&quot;]]],[1,&quot;p&quot;,[[0,[],0,&quot;There are also ways to earn money online which might earn you cash but might be not legal or suitable for your long term.&quot;]]],[1,&quot;h3&quot;,[[0,[],0,&quot;Reselling Pirated Digital goods&quot;]]],[1,&quot;p&quot;,[[0,[],0,&quot;Recently piracy has been on the rise, and it">
<div>
<h2>Not so bright and legal ways to earn money online.</h2>
<p>There are also ways to earn money online which might earn you cash but might be not legal or suitable for your long term.</p>
<h3>Reselling Pirated Digital goods</h3>
<p>Recently piracy has been on the rise, and it's now a massive problem for the internet and the people earing from it and using it.</p>
<p>Nowadays, the digital goods of business and owners are stolen, modified and then resold or redistributed on someone's other websites.</p>
<p>This makes it very hard for the product owner to earn revenue and generate cash to redistribute it without doing any hard work.</p>
<p>Stealing content from other websites and posting it on theirs is one of the types of internet piracy. Many new bloggers don't want to invest their time to research and write content for their websites. Instead, they steal or copy others content and post them as their own on which they also show ads.</p>
<p>Many websites provide download links of paid applications; the websites offer them free and even modify them to unlock more features.</p>
<p>While this may seem reasonable and beneficial to you as a user because you're getting the paid item for free, it's not good for the real owners or publishers to affect their revenue stream.</p>
<p>Not only that, these pirated or modified digital products are not at all safe for you to use. They might contain any malicious virus or may steal your data without you knowing about it.</p>
<h3>Using other's copyrighted content as your own</h3>
<p>Another not, so way to earn money is to steal other people's content and post it as your own. Recently, the trend has been rising a lot; many influencers on youtube are promoting stealing articles from news websites and publishing them by changing their synonyms.</p>
<p>There are also many softwares or bots available on the internet that can scrape the articles from any website automatically; you need to set up it once, and the tool will automatically scrape content and post it and will also replace the words with their synonyms by which it would be unique and plagiarism free.</p>
<p>Wow! that's an excellent idea. No, it's not; changing the synonyms doesn't make it your content. If something is copyrighted, you can't change anything or even translate it without the permission of the owner.</p>
<p>Doing so can be very dangerous for you as you might get in trouble for copying the content of others without taking permission.</p>
<p>I have seen these types of content ranking on google. Even I have tried it on my own and also ranked articles scraped from other websites. But this is not the way to earn as its very illegal and can get you into big trouble.</p>
<h2>Conclusion</h2>
<p>Earning money is not very easy, especially now, but it doesn't mean that it's impossible. The internet is still growing and will have more users added in the upcoming years. If you want to earn money from the internet, you would need to develop a skill or do something that will benefit those users.</p>
<p>After all, the people using the internet are constantly looking for information for themselves; they are not using the internet to make you rich. So, to get successful on the internet, you need to provide value to the users.</p>
<p>If you're starting a blog, don't focus on revenue. Try to lean on how to do it perfectly. May analyse and learn what the other people are earning from the internet are doing right.</p>
<p>If you think you can provide value to the users on the internet, you are ready to go; you can earn an unlimited amount of money. It's not only about money; you can even build an excellent image of yourself like the guru of something.</p>
<p>Show your expertise to the people, make them satisfied by whatever you are serving them. Make them come back to you without even spamming them on their inboxes.</p>
<p>That way, you would provide proper value to the internet, keeping it fair and clean for everyone.</p>
<p>I hope you enjoyed reading my blog; if you did, make sure to do something right. If you are thinking of earning something, try to provide good value.</p>
<p>Don't worry about whether there would be a success or not; if you have the patience, you will succeed. Don't expect to get rich in just a day or month. It's not possible.</p>
<p>Big brands and companies took years of expertise to get to the level they are now; if your starting something on the internet, have patience keep on growing and keep on providing value, you would be successful.</p>
<p>There is no guarantee of a particular period for anyone to get something. It might come quickly to some people and late to some, but continuing it can indeed succeed.</p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
