<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <title>Bibarud</title>
    <link href="https://www.bibarud.com/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://www.bibarud.com" />
    <updated>2021-06-06T01:33:52+05:30</updated>
    <author>
        <name>Uddipan Barman</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://www.bibarud.com</id>

    <entry>
        <title>The Portrait of a Lady Summary (Hornbill)</title>
        <author>
            <name>Uddipan Barman</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://www.bibarud.com/the-portrait-of-a-lady-summary-hornbill/"/>
        <id>https://www.bibarud.com/the-portrait-of-a-lady-summary-hornbill/</id>
            <category term="Summary"/>

        <updated>2021-06-06T01:33:52+05:30</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://www.bibarud.com/media/posts/12/Crello-Free-Graphic-Design-Software-Simple-Online-Photo-Editor.png" alt="The Portrait of a Lady Summary (Hornbill)" />
                    The Author Says: In the two decades that I had known my&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://www.bibarud.com/media/posts/12/Crello-Free-Graphic-Design-Software-Simple-Online-Photo-Editor.png" alt="The Portrait of a Lady Summary (Hornbill)" />
                <h2 data-changed="true" data-paragraphid="33">The Author Says:</h2>
<p class="dropcap" data-changed="true" data-paragraphid="33">In the two decades that I had known my grandmother, she had developed prominent wrinkles and a frailer figure. Many stated she had once been young and lovely, and there was no question that she had even had a spouse, but those claims were difficult to accept. My grandfather's photo was prominently displayed over the fireplace in the drawing room. He was wearing a large turban and loose-fitting clothing, and he was several decades older than he looked. He seemed as if he could only have as many grandkids as there were grains of sand on the beach.</p>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="true" data-paragraphid="34">I had nearly thrown up when I thought about my grandmother being young and attractive. "I got my own room one day, and it was one of the best things that had happened to me." Their bond was torn apart as their friendship shattered." The quote from The Annals of Sanness goes like this: "I would try to pass on to her English words and ideas about western science and learning, including the law of gravity, Archimedes' Principle, and the globe being round. After feeding the sparrows, she had a well-deserved rest in the afternoon. As she sat in the veranda, she would give out handfuls of nuts to the birds. She used to consider the twenty minutes from five to seven p.m. as the happiest part of her day. A significant change in her personality occurred through the evening.</p>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="true" data-paragraphid="35">She had not prayed. The next morning she was stricken with illness. She lay in bed quietly praying and telling her beads. She told us that her death was approaching even before we could stop her. She stated she wasn't going to waste any more time talking to us because she hadn't prayed just a few hours before the end of her last chapter of life.</p>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="true" data-paragraphid="36">Suspect's lips froze, and the rosary slipped from her lifeless fingers. We realised she was gone when a peaceful pallor came across her face. Thousands of sparrows sat on the verandah and in her room, straight up to where she lay dead and rigid draped in a scarlet shroud.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Grounding for the Metaphysics of Morals Summary (All Chapters)</title>
        <author>
            <name>Uddipan Barman</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://www.bibarud.com/grounding-for-the-metaphysics-of-morals-summary-all-chapters/"/>
        <id>https://www.bibarud.com/grounding-for-the-metaphysics-of-morals-summary-all-chapters/</id>
            <category term="Summary"/>

        <updated>2021-06-04T01:26:13+05:30</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://www.bibarud.com/media/posts/10/Blog-Banner-560x315-px-Custom-dimensions.jpeg" alt="Grounding for the Metaphysics of Morals Summary (All Chapters)" />
                     Key Points A good majority of our core views about the&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://www.bibarud.com/media/posts/10/Blog-Banner-560x315-px-Custom-dimensions.jpeg" alt="Grounding for the Metaphysics of Morals Summary (All Chapters)" />
                <div class="post__toc">
<h3>Table of Contents</h3>
<ul>
<li><a href="#mcetoc_1f78ga7p0i0">Key Points</a></li>
<li><a href="#mcetoc_1f78ga7p0i1">Preface</a></li>
<li><a href="#mcetoc_1f78ga7p0i2">Chapter 1</a></li>
<li><a href="#mcetoc_1f78ga7p0i3">Chapter 2</a>
<ul>
<li><a href="#mcetoc_1f78ga7p0i4">Part 1</a></li>
<li><a href="#mcetoc_1f78ga7p0i5">Part 2</a></li>
</ul>
</li>
<li><a href="#mcetoc_1f78ga7p0i6">Chapter 3</a></li>
</ul>
</div>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1f78ga7p0i0">Key Points</h2>
<ul>
<li class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="9">A good majority of our core views about the universe are previous notions that we possess a priori in the Critique of Pure Reason, which Kant referred to as a 'philosophical precept.'</li>
<li class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="10">Kant said: One of the most important arguments in Kant's Metaphysics of Morals is on the subject of theft.</li>
<li class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="11">It is a paradox in a culture where property rights exist when one steals, as one expects others to recognise one's ownership of the property they took.</li>
<li class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="12">We can not count on the concept of free will to tell us what is right and wrong. Moral behaviour is within everyone's grasp of reason, not only humanity's, and hence we must rely on rationality to decide what is moral.</li>
<li class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="13">The need for unconditional validity, which evolved as a result of this, resulted in the introduction of the moral law and the Categorical Imperative, because freedom will inevitably be accompanied by freedom.</li>
</ul>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1f78ga7p0i1">Preface</h2>
<p class="root-block-node dropcap" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="10">In the Critique of Pure Reason, Kant claimed that a great number of our basic beliefs about the world are previous concepts that we possess a priori. In this work, Kant presents an argument on moral philosophy along similar lines. In this instance, he outlines basic concepts of moral thought that occur to us even when they aren't relevant to the circumstances. In other words, Kant believes that if you want to understand morality, you must begin with "pure," a priori ideas of reason.As far as Kant is concerned, moral thoughts may be universally legitimate only if they are grounded on a prior concept of cognition.</p>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="11">The Preface to this book was published by Oxford University Press, which is priced at $19.99. According to Kant, we should not take human nature into consideration when we determine morality. Some critics of Kant have contested his claim to present a comprehensive moral philosophy that is founded solely on rational thinking. According to Kant, a morality founded on rational thinking will be embraced by everyone; it will be better than one supported by one particular group of people. Some philosophers contend that we do not act on our values because we can not understand morality in its entirety; yet, researchers who study ethics report that we use intuition instead of analysis to discern what moral courses of action are.</p>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="12">It is simply because what makes sense to us is mostly derived from beliefs and misconceptions we learn from our parents and our local communities. Kant only only presents one instance of a moral principle with universal validity; this is to say that grounding the Metaphysics of Morals is the only instance of this. Additional examples and definitions of moral concepts will be provided in the subsequent chapters. There are two terms in German that both mean "man" — one is for man in the sense of a male adult, while the other is for man in the generic sense.</p>
<hr>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1f78ga7p0i2">Chapter 1</h2>
<p class="root-block-node dropcap" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="3">Good will is one of the only things in the world that is completely unambiguous, according to Kant. Promising something that can not be kept is an example of an activity that violates this moral norm, he explains. Regardless of whether they are uneducated or unskilled, everyone exhibits this ability to follow the moral rules in their daily life, he notes. While Hegel stated that Kant's philosophy was too abstract to be of value, the Austrian philosopher and 19th-century classicist Hegel also maintained that our thinking is organised by the ideas, institutions, and traditions of the community in which we live. He also disagreed with Kant's view, which holds that you can't know whether or not someone's behaviour will appear self-contradictory until you know something about their society.</p>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="4">Kant: One of the major arguments in Kant's Metaphysics of Morals is about theft. In a society where there are property rights, it is paradoxical to steal because you expect others to accept your ownership of what you have stolen. On the other hand, we can only envisage a new family structure in which affairs would not be regarded as unethical. To begin with, morality is not something for automatons living a life of pure rational thought. The ability to overlook personal desires in order to support and maintain communal values is of relevance to human beings, who are called upon to compromise their personal interests in various circumstances. Kant's critics, however, have instead said that while Hegel is correct in believing that social institutions play a crucial part in influencing our beliefs, he neglects to recognise how entrenched established norms, values, and beliefs can be. The notions of instinct and self-preservation had been accepted by the scientific community even before Darwin presented his thesis.</p>
<hr>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1f78ga7p0i3" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="4">Chapter 2</h2>
<h3 id="mcetoc_1f78ga7p0i4" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="4">Part 1</h3>
<p class="root-block-node dropcap" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="5">It is nearly rare to identify any instances of people carrying out their tasks just out of a sense of responsibility. Nearly everything we see may be explained by some motivation other than doing the right thing because it is the right thing to do. This idea that people behave as they do for no other reason than a need for self-preservation may be accurate at first glance, but we can not ever be sure whether there is some hidden motivation influencing their actions. It is critical to have a more complete knowledge of a priori moral conceptions, especially when competing goals and motivations attempt to weaken our moral sense. All categorical imperatives incorporate only intrinsic and universal factors, such as universal validity, and do not take into consideration any situational factors. As a result, the only viable categorical imperative is that actions must follow a requirement of universal validity.</p>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="6">People who routinely disregard their duties in each and every circumstance, such as when they accept the objective validity of the law and then seek an exception to it, are involved in a contradictory state of affairs; accepting the objective validity of the law, they desire an exception to it. To conclude the discussion in chapter 2, Kant mentions his ongoing work and asserts that an enhanced comprehension of principles of morality might further bolster our moral instincts. The standard view, as argued in the Critique of Pure Reason, is that it would be impossible for us to deduce our concept of cause from our observations of the world. For Kant, causality is an a priori concept. He refers to it as a thought that comes to us as a result of mental processing that happens prior to our thinking about it. In a similar vein, we must emphasise that while causation is too fundamental an idea to be derived from experience, our moral beliefs are much more foundational.</p>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="7">In reference to concrete examples from our personal experiences However, this doesn't mean that a lack of moral motivation or pure moral acts doesn't exist, just like the notion of a lack of moral motivation or pure moral deeds. The chapter's objective is to clarify and improve our knowledge of the absolute moral requirements that the law lays on us. Insofar as one accepts Kant's theory of ethical demands, one must accept "categorical imperatives" as his definition of moral law. In order for an a priori imperative to be valid, it must be independent of any circumstantial reasons. The categorical imperative can neither dictate that you should or must do something in a certain situation nor tell you not to do it.</p>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="8">Consequently, your activity is not applicable to everyone; it is partial and hypocritical, according to Kant. The categorical imperative is substantially the same as what we discussed in Chapter 1 of moral law. When it comes to each case, each person is obligated to decide on the path of action that appears most credible. The categorical imperative is an interesting philosophical experiment that attempts to base moral judgments on the assertion that contradiction is illogical. Despite this, Kant's formula does not seem to describe the complexity of moral concerns quite well.</p>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="9">The second part of Chapter 2 is concerned with Kant's second formulation of the categorical imperative, and in it, he restates his value-theoretic account of it, with a focus on the intrinsic worth of every single unique human being. He argues that although the notions of God, free will, and immortality are natural notions of reason, they are not tangible objects of sensory experience. Kant's observation that our conception of God originates in our notion of moral perfection is more evidence of his views on religion. Kant: We can only have a concept of moral perfection, and so a thought of God, if we already have a concept of moral perfection. These concepts were perceived as controversial by many of Kant's contemporaries. It was decreed by the Prussian government that no more writings on religious topics would be published.</p>
<h3 id="mcetoc_1f78ga7p0i5" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="9">Part 2</h3>
<p class="root-block-node dropcap" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="5">Such entities have agency, and they may make decisions about their goals and the methods they will use to achieve them. Merely hypothetical imperatives will always be the basis for ending desires that are founded on physical necessities or wants. While the categorical imperative may be founded on anything that is an "end in itself" — something that serves just itself and not another goal, want, or want — there may be other possible reasons for its existence, such as providing security and confidence to its creator. To understand the context of an action is essential for rational decision-making, and to pursue aims, rational individuals must think of themselves as means and as ends as well. When rational humans engage in something purely for the sake of obligation, they must relinquish all personal interests and incentives, other than obligation. A basic principle of morality is to only act in accordance with those principles and motivations that are conducive to establishing a kingdom of goals.</p>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="6">Compassion is required to steer our intent toward beneficial goals. It must never contradict itself; its acts must demonstrate the fundamental value of universal principles of reason. It is the idea that people, as ends in themselves, have an inherent, absolute value—that they possess "dignity" When a person has faith in the nobility of morality, he or she will consider serving as a lawmaker in the kingdom of the end to be honourable. According to this conception of a perfect community in which all citizens follow the rules of objective reason, it must result in the "kingdom of ends." No empirical standards can form the basis of morality, as they are always reliant on the perspective of the observer. In each unique case, the will is self-determining; and the principle of the action is true only in the particular situation. Kant only elaborates on the topic in Chapter 3, revealing that morality may be founded on the concept of free will.</p>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="7">But even this Kantian argument is merely a 'grounding' for the metaphysics of morals, and not a full metaphysics, or even a complete investigation of the nature of 'practical' (i.e., moral) reason and its role in our lives. According to Kant, if you expect other people to accept your objectives, you must recognise the reality that other people think of themselves as more than just a means to other objectives. Many individuals have a basic understanding of morality, thus his main concept connects effectively with the vast majority of people. Using people or taking advantage of others out of self-interest is fundamentally immoral, since doing so breaks our belief that humans are not mere objects we may use as we like. While Kant first argued that the law only becomes true if it is comprehensible to those who must obey it, democracies are more concerned with rational argument. According to Kant, even though the concepts of "autonomy" and of a "kingdom of ends" are ideal concepts, it is nevertheless unrealistic to expect these concepts to appear in the real world.</p>
<hr>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1f78ga7p0i6" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="4">Chapter 3</h2>
<p class="root-block-node dropcap" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="5">Moral behaviour is in the realm of everyone's rational thinking, not only the thoughts of humanity, and thus, we can not rely our ideas of morality on the concept of free will. If it proves this from personal experience, it would be almost tough to prove, believes the philosopher. When it comes to concepts such as reality, he asserts that everyone is different, meaning there will be variability in each person's point of view on the "sensible" world. However, to everyone, he stresses that the concepts of sense are comprehensible. "The Sensible World" is how the world seems to us on a day-to-day basis. Human beings may know about themselves by one of two possible means: through the physical senses or by logic.</p>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="6">The problem is that people don't actually live in an intelligent world and have an "independent" will, which is enslaved by the influences of society. It is, however, important to bear in mind that their acts would be governed by the laws of nature and the rules of cause and effect. It can't be denied that both ideas can not be completely described, and that the contradiction between them can't be reconciled, he says. He says that "the nature of things as appearances is ruled by necessity," and that "what things are in themselves is ruled by freedom." The categorical imperative can be paraphrased as a "ought" statement: We all know that we ought to have a pure will.</p>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="7">One could go as far as to say that the comprehensible world can't produce anything that could be used as a target for action. The greatest explanation for this phenomenon can be found in the idea that the world of appearances is controlled by causation, yet this does not mean that we can not be free as objects in ourselves. If the fact that we are free was the result of using our intellect, then that freedom would not be really free, for freedom is supposed to be unconditional. There is nothing more that we can accomplish than to acknowledge the boundaries of our understanding and accept the implications of the concept of freedom. This is the only moral and ethical justification we have: that moral ideas and the categorical imperative need to be supported by the concept of freedom.</p>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="8">This story was written by the author of "A Farewell to Man". A secular concept of reason (rather than a transcendent God) has taken the role of God in Kant's system, but the classifications remain intact: spirit is good, body is bad. If people can overcome their cravings for the physical world and follow spiritual precepts, they are truly free. In an effort to live by free will, he says that we must be able to establish our own law. "My concept of freedom offers a foundation—a basis for morality. I say this because ", he states. The demand for unconditional validity, which arose as a result of this, brought about the moral law and the Categorical Imperative, because freedom must naturally lead to freedom.</p>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="9">Though knowing that freedom gives rise to morality is not the same as knowing why we desire to be moral, one can come to see that truth in both of these approaches. According to Kant, it is impossible to prove that we are free through rational analysis. It is possible to say that every occurrence can be explained by an earlier occurrence, but this is merely a property of the world of appearances. Causal determinism is therefore not the final word for us, since we are already objects in themselves. Our sense that we are free may be correct, regardless of the circumstances.</p>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="10">However, there is no logical refutation of our concept of freedom, is there? We are in favour of maximising our freedom by adhering to the categorical imperative. In Kant's view, the ultimate test of freedom is being able to obey our own most pressing demands and desires. Kant's conception of freedom may not seem convincing to some thinkers. Since morality inherently includes restraining our selfish tendencies in ways that benefit the greater welfare of humanity, it follows that a fundamental characteristic of morality is virtue.</p>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="11">While it may be disputed whether Kant's theories are correct, there is at least some evidence to support his claim that the theory of morality fits the ordinary moral intuitions of people. Despite his strict adherence to rationalism, Kant's moral philosophy is no more restrictive than any other, notes Zafar Hussain.</p>
<hr>
<p data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="11"> </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>The origin of language summary under 300 words</title>
        <author>
            <name>Uddipan Barman</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://www.bibarud.com/the-origin-of-language-summary/"/>
        <id>https://www.bibarud.com/the-origin-of-language-summary/</id>
            <category term="Summary"/>

        <updated>2021-06-04T01:26:19+05:30</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://www.bibarud.com/media/posts/7/The-Origin-of-Language-Summary-under-300-words.jpg" alt="The origin of language summary" />
                    Key Points According to the Ding-dong hypothesis, small or pointy things are&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://www.bibarud.com/media/posts/7/The-Origin-of-Language-Summary-under-300-words.jpg" alt="The origin of language summary" />
                <h2 data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="3">Key Points</h2>
<ul>
<li class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="6">According to the Ding-dong hypothesis, small or pointy things are named with words with high front vowels, whereas large or circular things have a round vowel at the end of the word.</li>
<li class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="7">In recognition of his teacher, Noam Chomsky, Nim Chimpsky was named after him.</li>
<li class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="8">This 2009 study published in Nature appears to support the hypothesis.</li>
<li class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="9">When this gene is mutated, it disrupts language and animals can't.</li>
<li class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="10">The scientist, Dean Falk, posits that as early humans lost their fur, carrying kids became more difficult.</li>
</ul>
<p class="dropcap" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="3">Languages are a core component of human society. The Linguistic Society of Paris prohibited discourse on the topic in 1886 and did not recant it for several years. No other species has the vocal pathology needed to talk like we do. No animal has demonstrated any competence above the level of a two-year-old human. In order to talk like a person, a creature must have a person's brain, voice chords, and intelligence.</p>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="4">Theory that humans developed to copy and mimic sounds Pooh-pooh believes that humans made all of the earliest words. Primitive people used their tongues to mimic hand gestures and words then emerged from that. Another, much earlier view states that language is a God-given capacity. Genesis says that the first man and woman, Adam and Eve, were able to comprehend what God said to them and converse in the same language.</p>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="5">For many years, people spoke the same language until the uprising of Babel. Animals will never be able to speak. It appears we can communicate with human-like speech but apes can not. Project Washoe tested if a chimpanzee could learn language in the 1960s. Project Nim was less regulated than the man in charge, Herbert S Terrace.</p>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="6">He decided that they were never able to use the indicators properly. Terrace claims a genetic mutation allowed our ancestors to communicate and grasp language. Chimpanzees have an important gene for language and speech development, FOXP2, which differs from humans. Maybe this one gene's mutation caused other species to become extinct? Another hypothesis is that because human societies became larger, people required an effective grooming method to maintain friendly relationships with others. the continuity theory that it arose from pre-linguistic sounds</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Is there still potential to earn money from the internet in 2021?</title>
        <author>
            <name>Uddipan Barman</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://www.bibarud.com/is-there-still-potential-to-earn-money-from-the-internet/"/>
        <id>https://www.bibarud.com/is-there-still-potential-to-earn-money-from-the-internet/</id>

        <updated>2021-06-02T16:33:28+05:30</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://www.bibarud.com/media/posts/3/Bibarud.jpg" alt="" />
                     Recently the web hosting business has been booming in the technological&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://www.bibarud.com/media/posts/3/Bibarud.jpg" alt="" />
                <div data-mobiledoc="{&quot;version&quot;:&quot;0.3.2&quot;,&quot;atoms&quot;:[],&quot;cards&quot;:[],&quot;markups&quot;:[],&quot;sections&quot;:[[1,&quot;p&quot;,[[0,[],0,&quot;Recently the web hosting business has been booming in the technological space. New individuals and enterprises are appearing online. Everyone wants to have a name for themselves or their business in the internet world. And it">
<div>
<p>Recently the web hosting business has been booming in the technological space. New individuals and enterprises are appearing online. Everyone wants to have a name for themselves or their business in the internet world. And it's also worth being on the internet as physically, no person or brand can reach such a vast amount of audience at once.</p>
<p>Many business and individuals have profited from the internet; there is no doubt that the internet has many potentials. It can generate tons of revenue for any brand or individual.</p>
<p>The internet has been growing since the past decade, for the context. In 1995, the internet had only 16 Million users, about 0.4% of the world's population; yeah, 16 million is not a small number, but if you compare it with the users in 2020, i.e. 5,098 Million, which is around 64.7% of the worlds total population it's just unbelievable of how much the internet has gained growth.</p>
<p>And it's not the end; it's just the beginning. The remaining 40% of the world aren't still using the internet. The number of users will be increasing drastically over the upcoming years. As infants would be getting older, they would too become aware of the internet and its uses. There's a lot of potential of earning from the internet in the future.</p>
<div data-mobiledoc="{&quot;version&quot;:&quot;0.3.2&quot;,&quot;atoms&quot;:[],&quot;cards&quot;:[],&quot;markups&quot;:[],&quot;sections&quot;:[[1,&quot;h2&quot;,[[0,[],0,&quot;How easy was earning money from the internet earlier?&quot;]]],[1,&quot;p&quot;,[[0,[],0,&quot;Earning some cash has never been easy in any aspect. The internet is no exception. However, it is relatively easier than physical labour. There were many ways of how people earned from the internet; at first, people use to sell goods and earn from the internet, that">
<div>
<h2>How easy was earning money from the internet earlier?</h2>
<p>Earning some cash has never been easy in any aspect. The internet is no exception. However, it is relatively easier than physical labour. There were many ways of how people earned from the internet; at first, people use to sell goods and earn from the internet, that's how big e-commerce giants like amazon got created, because of the internet.</p>
<p>After that, many business and individuals joined the route seeing such a massive amount of profits. Every brand wanted a piece of cake on the internet. Every brand now has their website where they sell their goods.</p>
<p>But it's not only brands that have earned from the internet; many individuals have earned a lot of money throughout the period.</p>
<p>Earlier, a popular way of earning through the internet was to work or which is known as freelancing for companies and business to create their websites or provide other services.</p>
<p>As there were not many tech-savvy people available earlier, so the ones that knew coding and programming made quite good money through making websites for other individuals and brands.</p>
<p>Even early coders and programmers have the advantage of creating anything on the internet and succeeding in it. They were the first to make such a thing, and no other competition existed.</p>
<h2>How did earning on the internet became so popular?</h2>
<p>As the internet boomed, companies like Google and Facebook started gaining popularity; they introduced user behaviour tracking with the browser and Java scripts' help.</p>
<p>Being able to track the users gave them the advantage to show users ads of businesses. Slowly the tech giants began to earn a lot of revenue from ads alone, becoming prevalent.</p>
<p>Now every business wants to advertise their products not only offline but in online space too. Brands like google introduced services for individuals to show ads on their websites to get paid some revenue. This business model became very popular and is on the rise.</p>
<p>The idea of serving ads of different companies on an individual's blog was a success. It allowed the individuals to focus on their content, which, if it gets ranked on google, generates an outstanding amount of ad revenue.</p>
<p>But with it, there came many advantages and also disadvantages. Benefits were for both the individuals and the big corporates, as for individuals, it became an excellent source of income, and for companies, they could now reach more targeted customers.</p>
<p>The significant disadvantage about ads is that they are targeted to users search and intent, which means ad companies like Google and Facebook are constantly spying on their users and tracking their every search and quarries on the internet, even they have access to the most potent things like location data of users. They knew every bit of information about their users, making the privacy of the users compromised.</p>
<p>As seen recently, there were also many data breaches of users data from these companies, which makes a big concern about users' privacy on the internet.</p>
<p>This article is not focused on the privacy part, which you can find in our other articles. We will now talk about the potential of earning from the internet in today's age.</p>
<h2>How to earn money from the internet in 2021?</h2>
<p>Earning money from the internet is not a new topic; it has been covered by many publications, influencers, and other people, teaching tips and tricks on how to earn money online.</p>
<p>In my personal experience, I have tried doing many things to earn money online; I have tried hard to make pennies from the internet. I used to follow anyone guide of things that I can do to earn money online.</p>
<p>Many experts, or so-called influencers, claim to earn a lot of cash, even in millions, by just doing a simple thing or simply filling up a form or just doing a survey.</p>
<p>People claimed to have installed an app that made them a millionaire by watching ads. That's very funny and serious at the same time. Many people believe in such things and waste their time hoping that they would earn some cash.</p>
<p>These apps and surveys may earn you a tiny amount of money, but they can't make you rich or even fulfil your daily expenses.</p>
<div data-mobiledoc="{&quot;version&quot;:&quot;0.3.2&quot;,&quot;atoms&quot;:[],&quot;cards&quot;:[],&quot;markups&quot;:[],&quot;sections&quot;:[[1,&quot;h2&quot;,[[0,[],0,&quot;The bright and legal ways to earn money online:&quot;]]],[1,&quot;p&quot;,[[0,[],0,&quot;Earning money online has provided a ton of people with their livelihood and supports many businesses to operate.&quot;]]],[1,&quot;p&quot;,[[0,[],0,&quot;There are many ways that people earn from the internet. Lets first talk about the Bright or legal ways to make money online.&quot;]]],[1,&quot;h3&quot;,[[0,[],0,&quot;Blogging + Ads&quot;]]],[1,&quot;p&quot;,[[0,[],0,&quot;I have already mentioned in this article how people are earning a ton of revenue by showing or displaying ads on their blogs or websites.&quot;]]],[1,&quot;p&quot;,[[0,[],0,&quot;There are many ad providers available now on the internet; Google is one of the largest. Google has a program call Ad Sense which helps influencers and blog owners to display the ads provided by google for which they earn revenue.&quot;]]],[1,&quot;p&quot;,[[0,[],0,&quot;There are also alternatives like Media.net, which is a collab between Yahoo and Microsoft. There are options like Pop Ads or Ads Terra available too for different types of blogs.&quot;]]],[1,&quot;p&quot;,[[0,[],0,&quot;These ad companies have their policies according to which they show ads. Some might be showing ads on adult content too, but companies like google have stringent rules, and they maintain the quality of the ads making them the market leader.&quot;]]],[1,&quot;p&quot;,[[0,[],0,&quot;If your thinking of earning money online, you can start a blog and post good content on it; if any of your blog posts rank on Google and have ads enabled on them, you would be earing an outstanding amount of ad revenue.&quot;]]],[1,&quot;h3&quot;,[[0,[],0,&quot;Youtube&quot;]]],[1,&quot;p&quot;,[[0,[],0,&quot;If you are not a good content writer or don">
<div>
<h2>The bright and legal ways to earn money online:</h2>
<p>Earning money online has provided a ton of people with their livelihood and supports many businesses to operate.</p>
<p>There are many ways that people earn from the internet. Lets first talk about the Bright or legal ways to make money online.</p>
<h3>Blogging + Ads</h3>
<p>I have already mentioned in this article how people are earning a ton of revenue by showing or displaying ads on their blogs or websites.</p>
<p>There are many ad providers available now on the internet; Google is one of the largest. Google has a program call Ad Sense which helps influencers and blog owners to display the ads provided by google for which they earn revenue.</p>
<p>There are also alternatives like Media.net, which is a collab between Yahoo and Microsoft. There are options like Pop Ads or Ads Terra available too for different types of blogs.</p>
<p>These ad companies have their policies according to which they show ads. Some might be showing ads on adult content too, but companies like google have stringent rules, and they maintain the quality of the ads making them the market leader.</p>
<p>If your thinking of earning money online, you can start a blog and post good content on it; if any of your blog posts rank on Google and have ads enabled on them, you would be earing an outstanding amount of ad revenue.</p>
<h3>Youtube</h3>
<p>If you are not a good content writer or don't want to spend your time figuring out how to build a blog, choose a hosting plan and get fooled by hosting companies. Then you can try it on Youtube.</p>
<p>Suppose you enjoy your time filming yourself and want to share your thoughts, expertise, or personal life through video and earn revenue from it. Youtube is the best choice for you.</p>
<p>We all are aware of how youtube has changed the lives of many people. People are earning so much and also providing a ton of value to the consumers by their videos.</p>
<p>Youtube is owned by Google, which means it is all managed by Google; you need to create a youtube channel, which you can through your Gmail account and start posting your quality content there.</p>
<p>After you meet the criteria of views and subscribers, you can monetise your videos through google ads and earn an outstanding amount of revenue.</p>
<p>Well, it's not as simple as I make it seem, but you can definitely try it as a hobby first, and if somehow your success in it, you can always choose it over other things.</p>
<h3>Blogging + Membership</h3>
<p>Due to the increasing knowledge of people and raising awareness about tracking f their data to show ads, the Ad situation has been on a slight decline; people now are using adblocking softwares on their devices, making it hard for publishers and individuals to earn from ad revenue.</p>
<p>Still, the ads are very profitable, but there are now new ways for publishers to charge a particular amount of money for allowing users to read or access their content.</p>
<p>Users are not shown ads, and instead, they need to pay a membership fee. This is very beneficial for users as paying for the services eliminates the online ads and trackers, giving a safe and privacy-oriented experience.</p>
<p>However, this has not been so popular as not all users tend to pay for every article they read on a different website, making the internet costly for people.</p>
<p>Blogging platforms like Medium.com have gained success in this model of blogging, as the userbase of Medium.com are more reader-centric and likes to read articles.</p>
<h3>Freelancing</h3>
<p>If you are very good at something and want to earn online from those skills of yours, freelancing can be the thing to do.</p>
<p>If your very good at writing articles, many business and blog owners are looking for content writers for their blogs and publications.</p>
<p>There are websites like freelancer.com or Fiverr.com, where you can list out your skills, and people wanting them will come to you for your work; you would get paid for the job you have done for them.</p>
<p>This was very popular back in the day, it's popular now too, but the situation has changed a lot, as there are increasing in skilled people, there are many options for clients to choose from, because of the harsh competition people are offering services for significantly less amount of money.</p>
<p>They are making it hard for new people to get the opportunity to earn money. However, don't lose hope as experts verified by sites like Fiverr and Upwork tend to get many clients and make a lot of money.</p>
<p>If that's what you're looking to do, build and develop your skills first, maybe get a college degree in the field your good at; that way, you would have the advantage over other people in this field.</p>
<h3>Affiliate Marketing</h3>
<p>Another trendy way to earn money online is to market or promote products of brands, in return for which they provide commission for every product bought.</p>
<p>Affiliate marketing is the most popular way to earn without showing ads on your websites, blogs or youtube videos. You even don't need o own any blog or website or even youtube channel to earn from affiliate marketing.</p>
<p>Though having them may help you to boost your revenue. You can promote products of the brand on any platform; you can even pay for ads to promote those products on social media platforms like Facebook or Instagram and, in return, earn a commission for the purchase made.</p>
<p>That way, you would be able to campaign to a more targeted userbase for your promoted product.</p>
<p>Affiliate marketing has a lot of potentials and will be expanding vastly in the future. But, for doing it correctly, you need some good knowledge about marketing and gaining customers.</p>
<p>It would be better to build an online userbase through any platform; that way, it would be much easier to promote products.</p>
<p>There are also other ways to earn money online, by selling your good and products and much more; these were just a few examples; we would be updating the article as things get different in the future.</p>
<div translate="" data-mobiledoc="{&quot;version&quot;:&quot;0.3.2&quot;,&quot;atoms&quot;:[],&quot;cards&quot;:[],&quot;markups&quot;:[],&quot;sections&quot;:[[1,&quot;h2&quot;,[[0,[],0,&quot;Not so bright and legal ways to earn money online.&quot;]]],[1,&quot;p&quot;,[[0,[],0,&quot;There are also ways to earn money online which might earn you cash but might be not legal or suitable for your long term.&quot;]]],[1,&quot;h3&quot;,[[0,[],0,&quot;Reselling Pirated Digital goods&quot;]]],[1,&quot;p&quot;,[[0,[],0,&quot;Recently piracy has been on the rise, and it">
<div>
<h2>Not so bright and legal ways to earn money online.</h2>
<p>There are also ways to earn money online which might earn you cash but might be not legal or suitable for your long term.</p>
<h3>Reselling Pirated Digital goods</h3>
<p>Recently piracy has been on the rise, and it's now a massive problem for the internet and the people earing from it and using it.</p>
<p>Nowadays, the digital goods of business and owners are stolen, modified and then resold or redistributed on someone's other websites.</p>
<p>This makes it very hard for the product owner to earn revenue and generate cash to redistribute it without doing any hard work.</p>
<p>Stealing content from other websites and posting it on theirs is one of the types of internet piracy. Many new bloggers don't want to invest their time to research and write content for their websites. Instead, they steal or copy others content and post them as their own on which they also show ads.</p>
<p>Many websites provide download links of paid applications; the websites offer them free and even modify them to unlock more features.</p>
<p>While this may seem reasonable and beneficial to you as a user because you're getting the paid item for free, it's not good for the real owners or publishers to affect their revenue stream.</p>
<p>Not only that, these pirated or modified digital products are not at all safe for you to use. They might contain any malicious virus or may steal your data without you knowing about it.</p>
<h3>Using other's copyrighted content as your own</h3>
<p>Another not, so way to earn money is to steal other people's content and post it as your own. Recently, the trend has been rising a lot; many influencers on youtube are promoting stealing articles from news websites and publishing them by changing their synonyms.</p>
<p>There are also many softwares or bots available on the internet that can scrape the articles from any website automatically; you need to set up it once, and the tool will automatically scrape content and post it and will also replace the words with their synonyms by which it would be unique and plagiarism free.</p>
<p>Wow! that's an excellent idea. No, it's not; changing the synonyms doesn't make it your content. If something is copyrighted, you can't change anything or even translate it without the permission of the owner.</p>
<p>Doing so can be very dangerous for you as you might get in trouble for copying the content of others without taking permission.</p>
<p>I have seen these types of content ranking on google. Even I have tried it on my own and also ranked articles scraped from other websites. But this is not the way to earn as its very illegal and can get you into big trouble.</p>
<h2>Conclusion</h2>
<p>Earning money is not very easy, especially now, but it doesn't mean that it's impossible. The internet is still growing and will have more users added in the upcoming years. If you want to earn money from the internet, you would need to develop a skill or do something that will benefit those users.</p>
<p>After all, the people using the internet are constantly looking for information for themselves; they are not using the internet to make you rich. So, to get successful on the internet, you need to provide value to the users.</p>
<p>If you're starting a blog, don't focus on revenue. Try to lean on how to do it perfectly. May analyse and learn what the other people are earning from the internet are doing right.</p>
<p>If you think you can provide value to the users on the internet, you are ready to go; you can earn an unlimited amount of money. It's not only about money; you can even build an excellent image of yourself like the guru of something.</p>
<p>Show your expertise to the people, make them satisfied by whatever you are serving them. Make them come back to you without even spamming them on their inboxes.</p>
<p>That way, you would provide proper value to the internet, keeping it fair and clean for everyone.</p>
<p>I hope you enjoyed reading my blog; if you did, make sure to do something right. If you are thinking of earning something, try to provide good value.</p>
<p>Don't worry about whether there would be a success or not; if you have the patience, you will succeed. Don't expect to get rich in just a day or month. It's not possible.</p>
<p>Big brands and companies took years of expertise to get to the level they are now; if your starting something on the internet, have patience keep on growing and keep on providing value, you would be successful.</p>
<p>There is no guarantee of a particular period for anyone to get something. It might come quickly to some people and late to some, but continuing it can indeed succeed.</p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Things Google is doing wrong with its search algorithms</title>
        <author>
            <name>Uddipan Barman</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://www.bibarud.com/how-google-search-is-getting-fooled-by-news-websites/"/>
        <id>https://www.bibarud.com/how-google-search-is-getting-fooled-by-news-websites/</id>
            <category term="opinions"/>

        <updated>2021-06-02T16:11:50+05:30</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://www.bibarud.com/media/posts/2/Blue-Aquarium-Photo-Facebook-Cover-min.jpg" alt="" />
                     Disclaimer: All the things said in this article are all my&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://www.bibarud.com/media/posts/2/Blue-Aquarium-Photo-Facebook-Cover-min.jpg" alt="" />
                <div data-mobiledoc="{&quot;version&quot;:&quot;0.3.2&quot;,&quot;atoms&quot;:[],&quot;cards&quot;:[[&quot;markdown&quot;,{&quot;markdown&quot;:&quot;![39fc63ca-d98a-4524-8019-9c4f8dc2d719-2](http://bibarud.com/content/images/2021/03/39fc63ca-d98a-4524-8019-9c4f8dc2d719-2.png)&quot;}]],&quot;markups&quot;:[[&quot;strong&quot;]],&quot;sections&quot;:[[1,&quot;p&quot;,[[0,[0],1,&quot;Disclaimer:&quot;],[0,[],0,&quot; All the things said in this article are all my thoughts and observances, it might not be relevant to any single user, but as a whole, it might be a big issue. None of the images or words used in this article are meant to hurt any person or firm">
<div>
<p><strong>Disclaimer:</strong> All the things said in this article are all my thoughts and observances, it might not be relevant to any single user, but as a whole, it might be a big issue. None of the images or words used in this article are meant to hurt any person or firm's feelings or reputation.</p>
<p>Google is the king of search; even google is so big that other companies can't beat it in market share and revenue. Google is a very complex and very advanced search engine; Google is the smartest search engine with its AI features. There are no close competitors of google search.</p>
<p>Since the launch of google search in 1988, Google has gained many users and is rapidly growing today at a very fast pace. Billions of quarries are searched for daily on google. Google tries to provide the exact and most relevant answer from the web to its users for each question.</p>
<p>So, far as a google user, it's been fantastic to search for something on google. We all know that the answer to anything will be on google. But, things tend to worsen when it comes to few things. Especially if your not a conventional google search user and you use google search for your business.</p>
<p>You use Google to promote your blog or your website to the users who are searching for it. Generally, it's very hard to remember every domain name on the internet. And as there are tons of domains and websites available on the internet, the user would be helpless if they need to remember them all.</p>
<p>So, google saves the user and the websites and their owners by showing or ranking websites on the google search according to the relevancy of their content, making it easier for users and websites. That way, websites could earn their revenue or serve their purpose, and the user could get the answer or find the things they are looking for.</p>
<p>But, the main problem arises with the search results that Google shows. There is no doubt that Google is very advanced and not just a simple programming or code line to search the web. Google has more than 200 factors that come into play regarding SEO and rankings for websites and blogs. Google can't be wrong here, right?</p>
<p>Well, it would be a little disappointing to hear for you as a user, but it's not right at all. See, Google search is advanced, and there is no doubt, but still, it's getting fooled by many websites. Many websites are doing black hat SEO and other things to trigger the algorithm, but I am not talking about those. The websites that I am talking about are the NEWS or so-called NEWS websites.</p>
<h2>How is Google getting fooled by News Websites?</h2>
<p>The question arises in everyone's mind after knowing how google search gets fooled by news websites. After all, they have a separate place for themselves; the news websites gain traffic from google news and not much from google searches. Right? Well, wrong, these News websites, or so-called news websites, are doing everything or writing about anything other than providing news.</p>
<p>Okay, let me explain. A user searches for something on google which is not news or is not related to it; the search appears in front of the user; if you look carefully into the domains of the websites appearing on the first page on the google search results, those are all news websites.</p>
<p>Even I have one more specific and better example to demonstrate. There's one illegal and very popular keyword called the "Tamil Rockers" (For context Tamil Rockers is a group of individuals, that used to do piracy of movies before its even released on Theatres. They later were arrested by the Police and their websites were also taken down). If you search it on google, generally, you should expect to get some illegal movies downloading websites appearing on search. But instead, what appears are the news websites.</p>
<p>If you inspect the screenshot that I have provided, These are the top 10 results on Google search for the keyword "Tamil Rockers". You can easily see all the News websites appearing. Well, yeah, I get it. It's their website, and they can write or publish anything. Who am I to say.</p>
<p>Well, I don't have any problems with what they write and what they don't, and I don't care if they are ranking for any illegal or legal keywords. All I care about is that Google search is so advanced and still gets fooled by these news websites up to the extent that these news websites take 70% of the web traffic without providing any useful, valuable content.</p>
<p>All these news websites write 300 - 400 word articles on very popular keywords that are searched in millions on google and get ranked quickly, as they are more reputed in Google's eye, and it doesn't matter what they are providing to the user. They will eventually get up ranking on the higher positions of google search.</p>
<p>Well, what's wrong with that? These are reputed news sites, so there is nothing wrong with getting ranked higher. Well, my friends, that's what is wrong.</p>
<p>See most of the websites or blogs on the internet to provide users value and generate revenue. Now, if any new or good website is providing more valuable content, giving their best to bring up fully researched articles, that contain full information for the users, but couldn't get ranked on Google search due to these reputed news sites that are providing way less valuable content to the user.</p>
<p>Eventually, the better website will not get any traffic and will not generate much revenue for their content; on the other hand, these reputed News sites would get wealthier day by day without providing any value.</p>
<p>After all, it's a very big loss for the good websites providing very good content out on the internet. But the biggest loss is faced by the users. Often, users are not satisfied by any web site's content and have to look for others and spend their valuable time searching more for what they could have found easily on those websites providing good content.</p>
<p>Due to the Google search algorithm, those good websites would never outperform these so-called News websites. Thus never reaching the userbase they should have got.</p>
<h2>What's the solution?</h2>
<p>I have repeatedly repeated that Google is very advanced uses a lot of AI and machine learning for its algorithm, and it tires that its users get the best results. If that's the case, why can't google filter these news sites' valueless content? Or are they blind when it comes to these websites?</p>
<p>Many good content creators create great content and try everything they can to improve it and still don't get ranked. Well, I don't have the solution to that. I am nobody to say something, and I am sure that there would be no changes if I say also. After all, Google is a business too.</p>
<p>Google wants its users to spend more time on their search results to show them ads and generate more revenue. Maybe that could be the reason that Google becomes blind when it comes to these news websites.</p>
<p>Because see if a user doesn't get the full answer of their quarries in a single website, they visit multiple to get the rest of the information. All these websites more or less use Google's Ads Sense or are partnered with google somehow; if any particular user visits more websites, it results in more impressions of ads, thus earning google a lot more than what it would have got if the user only visited a single website.</p>
<p>That could be the reason why Google is lazy or biased when it comes to search results. This might not be true, as this is just my assumption and not based on any evidence. This is just common sense that any company would want to earn more revenue. After all, that's what they are for, Google is not a charity, so it's not just there to help people.</p>
<h2>Verdict</h2>
<p>If the user is the main priority of any of these big corporations and businesses, they should worry about their users. After all, they are there because their users are using their service or product.</p>
<p>And when it comes to Google, one of the most technologically advanced companies on the planet, they could have filtered the web and sort the rankings easily if they are not doing it. Maybe there's some reason for that too.</p>
<p>But the thing that is hurting the most is spending hours of work to provide information and not getting ranked because of these news websites. The fault is not of these news websites; they are also doing their job to earn more revenue.</p>
<p>The main culprit is google here because it knows what's going on, but it's acting as everything's fine. The main loser here is the users and the small websites trying their best to find their way. And there is no loos of google and these news websites, as together they are earning a ton of revenue, which is their main motto.</p>
<p> </p>
</div>
</div>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Wordpress vs Static Website: Which is the best for blogging?</title>
        <author>
            <name>Uddipan Barman</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://www.bibarud.com/wordpress-vs-static-website-which-is-the-best-for-blogging/"/>
        <id>https://www.bibarud.com/wordpress-vs-static-website-which-is-the-best-for-blogging/</id>
            <category term="Explained"/>

        <updated>2021-06-02T16:12:28+05:30</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://www.bibarud.com/media/posts/1/Wordpress-vs-Static-Websites-1-.jpg" alt="" />
                     Wordpress has always been the best platform for blogging in the&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://www.bibarud.com/media/posts/1/Wordpress-vs-Static-Websites-1-.jpg" alt="" />
                <div data-mobiledoc="{&quot;version&quot;:&quot;0.3.2&quot;,&quot;atoms&quot;:[[&quot;soft-return&quot;,&quot;&quot;,{}],[&quot;soft-return&quot;,&quot;&quot;,{}],[&quot;soft-return&quot;,&quot;&quot;,{}],[&quot;soft-return&quot;,&quot;&quot;,{}],[&quot;soft-return&quot;,&quot;&quot;,{}],[&quot;soft-return&quot;,&quot;&quot;,{}],[&quot;soft-return&quot;,&quot;&quot;,{}],[&quot;soft-return&quot;,&quot;&quot;,{}],[&quot;soft-return&quot;,&quot;&quot;,{}],[&quot;soft-return&quot;,&quot;&quot;,{}],[&quot;soft-return&quot;,&quot;&quot;,{}],[&quot;soft-return&quot;,&quot;&quot;,{}],[&quot;soft-return&quot;,&quot;&quot;,{}],[&quot;soft-return&quot;,&quot;&quot;,{}],[&quot;soft-return&quot;,&quot;&quot;,{}],[&quot;soft-return&quot;,&quot;&quot;,{}],[&quot;soft-return&quot;,&quot;&quot;,{}],[&quot;soft-return&quot;,&quot;&quot;,{}],[&quot;soft-return&quot;,&quot;&quot;,{}],[&quot;soft-return&quot;,&quot;&quot;,{}],[&quot;soft-return&quot;,&quot;&quot;,{}],[&quot;soft-return&quot;,&quot;&quot;,{}],[&quot;soft-return&quot;,&quot;&quot;,{}],[&quot;soft-return&quot;,&quot;&quot;,{}],[&quot;soft-return&quot;,&quot;&quot;,{}],[&quot;soft-return&quot;,&quot;&quot;,{}],[&quot;soft-return&quot;,&quot;&quot;,{}],[&quot;soft-return&quot;,&quot;&quot;,{}],[&quot;soft-return&quot;,&quot;&quot;,{}],[&quot;soft-return&quot;,&quot;&quot;,{}],[&quot;soft-return&quot;,&quot;&quot;,{}],[&quot;soft-return&quot;,&quot;&quot;,{}],[&quot;soft-return&quot;,&quot;&quot;,{}],[&quot;soft-return&quot;,&quot;&quot;,{}],[&quot;soft-return&quot;,&quot;&quot;,{}],[&quot;soft-return&quot;,&quot;&quot;,{}],[&quot;soft-return&quot;,&quot;&quot;,{}],[&quot;soft-return&quot;,&quot;&quot;,{}],[&quot;soft-return&quot;,&quot;&quot;,{}],[&quot;soft-return&quot;,&quot;&quot;,{}],[&quot;soft-return&quot;,&quot;&quot;,{}],[&quot;soft-return&quot;,&quot;&quot;,{}],[&quot;soft-return&quot;,&quot;&quot;,{}],[&quot;soft-return&quot;,&quot;&quot;,{}],[&quot;soft-return&quot;,&quot;&quot;,{}],[&quot;soft-return&quot;,&quot;&quot;,{}],[&quot;soft-return&quot;,&quot;&quot;,{}],[&quot;soft-return&quot;,&quot;&quot;,{}],[&quot;soft-return&quot;,&quot;&quot;,{}],[&quot;soft-return&quot;,&quot;&quot;,{}],[&quot;soft-return&quot;,&quot;&quot;,{}],[&quot;soft-return&quot;,&quot;&quot;,{}],[&quot;soft-return&quot;,&quot;&quot;,{}],[&quot;soft-return&quot;,&quot;&quot;,{}],[&quot;soft-return&quot;,&quot;&quot;,{}],[&quot;soft-return&quot;,&quot;&quot;,{}],[&quot;soft-return&quot;,&quot;&quot;,{}],[&quot;soft-return&quot;,&quot;&quot;,{}],[&quot;soft-return&quot;,&quot;&quot;,{}],[&quot;soft-return&quot;,&quot;&quot;,{}],[&quot;soft-return&quot;,&quot;&quot;,{}],[&quot;soft-return&quot;,&quot;&quot;,{}],[&quot;soft-return&quot;,&quot;&quot;,{}],[&quot;soft-return&quot;,&quot;&quot;,{}],[&quot;soft-return&quot;,&quot;&quot;,{}],[&quot;soft-return&quot;,&quot;&quot;,{}],[&quot;soft-return&quot;,&quot;&quot;,{}],[&quot;soft-return&quot;,&quot;&quot;,{}],[&quot;soft-return&quot;,&quot;&quot;,{}],[&quot;soft-return&quot;,&quot;&quot;,{}],[&quot;soft-return&quot;,&quot;&quot;,{}],[&quot;soft-return&quot;,&quot;&quot;,{}],[&quot;soft-return&quot;,&quot;&quot;,{}],[&quot;soft-return&quot;,&quot;&quot;,{}],[&quot;soft-return&quot;,&quot;&quot;,{}],[&quot;soft-return&quot;,&quot;&quot;,{}],[&quot;soft-return&quot;,&quot;&quot;,{}],[&quot;soft-return&quot;,&quot;&quot;,{}],[&quot;soft-return&quot;,&quot;&quot;,{}],[&quot;soft-return&quot;,&quot;&quot;,{}],[&quot;soft-return&quot;,&quot;&quot;,{}],[&quot;soft-return&quot;,&quot;&quot;,{}],[&quot;soft-return&quot;,&quot;&quot;,{}],[&quot;soft-return&quot;,&quot;&quot;,{}],[&quot;soft-return&quot;,&quot;&quot;,{}],[&quot;soft-return&quot;,&quot;&quot;,{}],[&quot;soft-return&quot;,&quot;&quot;,{}],[&quot;soft-return&quot;,&quot;&quot;,{}],[&quot;soft-return&quot;,&quot;&quot;,{}],[&quot;soft-return&quot;,&quot;&quot;,{}],[&quot;soft-return&quot;,&quot;&quot;,{}],[&quot;soft-return&quot;,&quot;&quot;,{}],[&quot;soft-return&quot;,&quot;&quot;,{}],[&quot;soft-return&quot;,&quot;&quot;,{}],[&quot;soft-return&quot;,&quot;&quot;,{}],[&quot;soft-return&quot;,&quot;&quot;,{}],[&quot;soft-return&quot;,&quot;&quot;,{}],[&quot;soft-return&quot;,&quot;&quot;,{}],[&quot;soft-return&quot;,&quot;&quot;,{}],[&quot;soft-return&quot;,&quot;&quot;,{}],[&quot;soft-return&quot;,&quot;&quot;,{}],[&quot;soft-return&quot;,&quot;&quot;,{}]],&quot;cards&quot;:[[&quot;image&quot;,{&quot;src&quot;:&quot;https://images.unsplash.com/photo-1542831371-29b0f74f9713?crop=entropy&amp;cs=tinysrgb&amp;fit=max&amp;fm=jpg&amp;ixid=MnwxMTc3M3wwfDF8c2VhcmNofDF8fGh0bWx8ZW58MHx8fHwxNjE1ODk0MDI1&amp;ixlib=rb-1.2.1&amp;q=80&amp;w=2000&quot;,&quot;width&quot;:6000,&quot;height&quot;:4000,&quot;caption&quot;:&quot;&quot;,&quot;alt&quot;:&quot;Wordpress vs static website which is better&quot;}]],&quot;markups&quot;:[[&quot;a&quot;,[&quot;href&quot;,&quot;https://m.do.co/c/f49f0dc5b910&quot;]],[&quot;a&quot;,[&quot;href&quot;,&quot;https://www.vultr.com/&quot;]],[&quot;a&quot;,[&quot;href&quot;,&quot;https://aws.amazon.com/lightsail/&quot;]],[&quot;a&quot;,[&quot;href&quot;,&quot;https://cyberpanel.net/&quot;]],[&quot;a&quot;,[&quot;href&quot;,&quot;https://ghost.org/&quot;]],[&quot;a&quot;,[&quot;href&quot;,&quot;https://www.gatsbyjs.com/&quot;]],[&quot;a&quot;,[&quot;href&quot;,&quot;https://wix.com/&quot;]],[&quot;a&quot;,[&quot;href&quot;,&quot;https://wp-rocket.me/&quot;]],[&quot;a&quot;,[&quot;href&quot;,&quot;https://nitropack.io/&quot;]],[&quot;a&quot;,[&quot;href&quot;,&quot;https://www.cloudflare.com/en-gb/&quot;]],[&quot;a&quot;,[&quot;href&quot;,&quot;https://www.netlifycms.org/&quot;]],[&quot;strong&quot;],[&quot;a&quot;,[&quot;href&quot;,&quot;https://www.w3schools.com/&quot;]]],&quot;sections&quot;:[[1,&quot;p&quot;,[[0,[],0,&quot;Wordpress has always been the best platform for blogging in the recent few years. It">
<div>
<p>Wordpress has always been the best platform for blogging in the recent few years. It's because of its ease to use and a ton of features. Wordpress has been used by many bloggers and also by many businesses, from small to large corporations. There's no doubt that Wordpress is one of the, if not the best, platforms for blogging. But why did we choose static sites for blogging over wordpress? Let's know in this article.</p>
<h2>What is Wordpress?</h2>
<p>Wordpress is a content management system build using the language PHP. Wordpress is open source and also very user-friendly. Half of the internet sites are using wordpress for their business or personal website. Wordpress makes the job of the user very easy by just visualizing everything. Wordpress helps the users to make a website very simple and fast. You can deploy a wordpress site within hours. Wordpress had many advantages over other CMS or Static websites. Also, there are disadvantages; we will be talking about them in detail here in this article.</p>
<h2>Advantages of Wordpress</h2>
<p>As I said earlier, there are many advantages of choosing wordpress as the platform for blogging or your website creation. Let's look at the advantages here:</p>
<h3>Easy to use</h3>
<p>Wordpress is very easy to use and doesn't need any technical knowledge to set up or make a website. Even it's so easy that you can learn using it within hours of using it. It doesn't take you months or days to learn to use and configuring wordpress.</p>
<h3>Open Source and free</h3>
<p>Wordpress itself is Open Source and free, which means you don't need to pay any fee to use the CMS. However, it's not free to use as you would require a web hosting or server to install wordpress on top of it. We would be talking about it the disadvantages of hosting wordpress.</p>
<h3>Tons of customization options</h3>
<p>As wordpress is one of the most popular blogging platforms, tons of themes and plugins can be used on wordpress. You don't need to know even a single code. The Plugins and themes are pre-made templated for wordpress by different and talented developers, and you require to install them on your wordpress site.</p>
<h3>Excellent community support</h3>
<p>The wordpress support is phenomenal. There is no official support for the open-source wordpress version, but tons and tons of forums and websites talk and teach wordpress. If you get in trouble configuring anything, google it, and the answer would be easier there for you.</p>
<h3>Full Ownership</h3>
<p>Wordpress is fully yours; there are no contracts between you and wordpress. You can use it as you like. You can customize it. Even if you know to code, you can customize its source code. You can build apps out of wordpress. It all your there are no limitations in terms of ownership.</p>
<h2>Disadvantages of Wordpress</h2>
<p>Now comes the fun part. No, I am not a hater of Wordpress, even I was a hardcore user of the platform for a long time now. I have been experiencing these things for a long now. I will share the things based on my won experience and may differ from user to user.</p>
<h3>Wordpress is slow</h3>
<p>Yes, I know if you have a very fast server, or if you have enough money to pay for a very fast server, your installation of wordpress might be fast. But for a beginner, that is a very big drawback as most beginners can't or don't want o pay a huge amount of money to host wordpress on a very powerful and expensive server. Even I am one of them; I can't afford or don't want to invest a lot of money in very expensive web hosting. So, because wordpress needs a ton of power, it's very difficult to optimize it for a big amount of traffic. It automatically gets slow, and stats crashing. Well, it's not the fault of wordpress itself but the technology.</p>
<h3>Costly to operate</h3>
<p>I know there are tons of websites promoting hosting for wordpress and comparing them according to their price. Even they make the hosting plans look so good with unlimited everything and whatnot if you listen to me, it's all not that great. The cheap hosting or so-called shared hosting plans are not good at all for wordpress websites. As wordpress sites are already so heavy, and if the hosting company puts a ton of websites in a server, how can your website run fast? It's just that companies are taking advantage of the customers by paying the influencers a ton of affiliate commission so that the influencers promote the hosting plans they would never use for their own websites. If you want to make your website fast and reliable to your customers, you need good wordpress optimized hosting, which would cost a lot of money. Even the hosting plans can be such a headache because, if you choose a bad or weak hosting thinking your website is new and posting good content on it, if somehow your post gets or your website gets ranked on google. You start getting traffic, your site suddenly crashes, and it's not opening anymore. You have to pay more to upgrade, or if you want to switch hosting plans, you have to have a backup of your website. If, for some reason, you didn't have any backup, congrats! Your website is now gone, and there is no option to revive it without paying higher fees to the hosting company.</p>
<h3>Easy to get hacked</h3>
<p>As your using 3rd party hosting companies, the security of the servers and your wordpress website would be your job to look after. If you're not a very technically savvy person, you might not be able to secure the website fully. In wordpress, there are many plugins and themes used which 3rd party developers make. If somehow any developer of any plugin decides to leave a backdoor through a plugin to access your data. Congrats, your website will get hacked without you knowing it. Of course, there are options or security plugins to secure your website but, it will cost you more money to buy them, and also, more plugins will make your wordpress website slower.</p>
<h3>Misleading hosting companies and their plans</h3>
<p>I have often seen that the hosting companies have become so misleading, providing everything unlimited on their cheapest hosting plan. None of that is true, there is nothing as unlimited, and often companies don't mention the more technical terms like inode counts and other stuff. So please don't trust these hosting companies. They are not good at all.</p>
<h3>Overall Expensive</h3>
<p>Wordpress is free and open-source, and it's very good, yes we all know that, but it's not the truth. wordpress might be open source, but it does not make it cheap as wordpress needs to be hosted, and that's not the only cost. There are costs of plugins to do your SEO properly; yes, WordPress is versatile and good for SEO, but not without Plugins, even there are no options to change the meta description by default on wordpress. There is a plugin for everything, but installing more plugins results in a slower website. Well, let me finish here as this is not a rant about wordpress; I was just pointing out some of the things that bothered me a lot while using wordpress and its ecosystem. The naked wordpress software is very good, but the thing that makes it the most complicated is the hosting and plugins part. Plugins do make the work easier, but they also make the site slower and may lead to data breaches and hacking of your website, as seen in the past.</p>
<img loading="lazy" src="https://images.unsplash.com/photo-1542831371-29b0f74f9713?crop=entropy&amp;cs=tinysrgb&amp;fit=max&amp;fm=jpg&amp;ixid=MnwxMTc3M3wwfDF8c2VhcmNofDF8fGh0bWx8ZW58MHx8fHwxNjE1ODk0MDI1&amp;ixlib=rb-1.2.1&amp;q=80&amp;w=2000" data-is-external-image="true" >
<h2>What is a static website?</h2>
<p>Static websites are websites with no backend; they have the only frontend, i.e., they are only built using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript. The main advantage of static websites is speed and low hosting costs. Static websites can be very complicated as they required very technical knowledge to make. You need to know about html, CSS, and javascript to create a website.However, there are many static website visual builders available right now in the market. There's Bootstrap Studio and also Mobirise that we are using now to generate our static website. All these static website makers are using the bootstrap framework. Again there are static sites generator like the HUGO or Gatsby, which can help users do static website blogging. But they can be very technical and not beginner-friendly.</p>
<h3>Advantages of Static Website</h3>
<p>Static websites have many advantages as well as many disadvantages we will be talking about all of them here; these are based on my experience</p>
<h3>Fast Loading</h3>
<p>Static websites don't have anything to process; the browser processes all the files. There is no requesting for data from any database. So, it doesn't need any server power and processing. Even static websites can be stored on storage buckets and accessed from anywhere. Because static websites don't any processing and don't need to look up information on their database, so they load very fast and are best for performance.</p>
<h3>Low Cost of Hosting</h3>
<p>Static websites don't need processing power. So, they are very cheap to host; you can use any paid service which is very cheap, like google cloud buckets or amazon s3 buckets. There are also other better options like Netlify or Github Pages, on which you can host websites for free without paying any penny. The most impressive service that we use is the latest Cloudflare Pages. They are still in Beta, but they are very good.Cloudflare Pages are very easy to use and are also very fast and free to use. You get true unlimited hosting and bandwidth for your websites. Cloudflare pages are linked to the repositories of your Github Account.</p>
<h3>More Flexibility</h3>
<p>Static websites have a lot of flexibility because of their ability to edit from the code. You can add any custom html code or any js script. There are numerous options with static websites. Even most of the websites of the tools on google are made using only html, CSS, and js.The Js can be hosted using CDN like Cloudflare, and the website can be stored on storage buckets. Even better is the Jam stack platform like GitHub pages and Cloudflare pages.Overall, static websites are the future as internet consumption is getting vast and bigger day by day. The websites need more advanced, new, and faster technologies to operate. Front-end static website generators like HUGO, which is build using Google's Go language, or static site generators like Gatsby, which can use wordpress as a headless CMS, maybe the future.</p>
<h2>Disadvantages of Static Websites</h2>
<p>As there are numerous advantages, there are also many disadvantages over CMS like wordpress. Let's see what's better on Wordpress</p>
<h3>Limited Ease of use</h3>
<p>Static websites can be very hard and annoying to use if your not a programmer or coder. As of today, they still require some knowledge to operate or run them. Even it's not that easy customizing them and maintaining them. It would help if you had a very good idea about coding and the languages used to make these static websites.There is very little visual editing of static websites; most of the things are terminal or code-based. At the same time, wordpress is very easy in that field.</p>
<h3>A long learning curve</h3>
<p>Static websites and their maintenance have a long learning curve. Because for the maintenance of static websites, the programming languages need to be learned. Programming languages like HTML and CSS are relatively easier than others, but still, it can take someone many months to get good at it.</p>
<h3>Too Confusing</h3>
<p>The most annoying thing about static websites is the development platform. It can be too confusing. There are many types of web development languages and tools like node js, react, angular, gatsby js which is also made using node js and react. There are tons of options. It might be good to have options, but at the same time, having so many options is very annoying, especially if you're a beginner.These disadvantages can be easily gone or fulfilled as technology will keep on getting better, there would be new tools coming for more beginner-centric audiences. There would be CMS that can generate Static webpages by default.</p>
<h2>Which is better Wordpress or Static Websites?</h2>
<p>Both wordpress and static websites are good for their respective user bases. I like wordpress for its simplicity and ease of use, whereas static websites are much more complex and time-consuming to work on.But wordpress sites are usually slow as they need many resources, which can be a problem for many people, as it's not possible to take subscriptions of very expensive hosting services for everyone. There are cheap hosting services available, but they are not as good for sustainability. They often can't handle more traffic and usually tend to crash.Even something wrong on other websites can make the whole server slow, and your websites might be affected. In my experience, I have got the best results from hosting providers like <a href="https://m.do.co/c/f49f0dc5b910">Digital Ocean</a>, <a href="https://www.vultr.com/">Vultr</a>, and <a href="https://aws.amazon.com/lightsail/">Amazon Light Sail</a>. There are other cloud providers like Amazon EC2 or Google Cloud VMs, but they might end up costing more. I have used <a href="https://cyberpanel.net/">Cyberpannel</a> along with the digital ocean. I chose the $5 plan, which was enough for my usage and traffic. The Cyber panel is free for personal use and can be installed easily from the Digital Ocean Market Place.Cyberpanel can also be installed on other cloud providers. But I like the digital ocean more, as I find them more reliable and fast.And one good hosting can be Cloudways, only if you have extra money with you, as cloudways manages the servers of the digital ocean and other cloud providers and doubles the price. I wouldn't choose cloudways to manage my hosting; I can install CyberPannel for free on any VPS.In conclusion, if you have a good budget and are not tech-savvy enough, and don't want to tinker into code and languages, wordpress is for you.There are no other options than wordpress that can give you such an amount of flexibility in a CMS.There are newer CMS based on Node JS like the <a href="https://ghost.org/">Ghost Blogging</a> Platform, which is also good but not as popular as wordpress.People wanting to learn new skills and experiment can go with the static sites, as they are very cost-efficient and are faster in speed. Static Websites are also good for the environment as they don't use much power, which leads to less use of electricity. But I would not get into that.</p>
<h2>How to use static websites for blogging?</h2>
<p>Using static websites for blogging is not as easy as wordpress or any other blogger or medium platform. Those are very easy to use platforms. To use static websites as a blog, you need to have a static website generator like HUGO.There are also options to use wordpress and <a href="https://www.gatsbyjs.com/">gatsby</a> to use as a static website generator and CMS, but the tutorials would be much detailed and complex as of now.<a href="https://wix.com/">Wix</a> might be a good option for them to start their website for someone looking to build faster websites without worrying too much. Wix uses html and CSS and Wix websites faster than wordpress because Wix websites are fully hosted and managed by Wix themselves.There are also blogging options on Wix. Also, Wix has built-in SEO features, so there's no need to paying for extra plugins. But for tutorials, you can watch various youtube videos; this article was just the comparision of between wordpress and static website blogging. If you're looking into wordpress with managed wordpress hosting, Kinsta might be a good option, but it's quite expensive, and also Wordpress.com can be good if you choose the more expensive plans. There are no options to change permalinks or change the seo meta descriptions for the basic plans.</p>
<h2>How to make wordpress run faster?</h2>
<p>I have complained about wordpress not being fast. If you want to make it faster, please use a cache plugin, like <a href="https://wp-rocket.me/">WP rocket</a>, or if you have a lite speed server, you can use the lite speed cache plugin. Moreover, there are newer options like <a href="https://nitropack.io/">NitroPack</a> available, which has plans that include a CDN and also drastically improves the performance of your wordpress website.Moreover, using <a href="https://www.cloudflare.com/en-gb/">Cloudflare</a> can help your wordpress site getting faster. Cloudflare is one of the best web tools or web companies out there.Also, avoid installing a ton of plugins; use light themes with less. Don't use themes that need a lot of plugins to work.Also, try using Gutenberg block editor, which is developed by wordpress. It's faster than using elementor. But it's not as versatile as elementor is.The last thing I can suggest is to get good hosting, not only a gimmicky one but a good one, like the <a href="https://m.do.co/c/f49f0dc5b910">digital ocean</a> or <a href="https://aws.amazon.com/lightsail/">Amazon light sail</a>. These services are very reliable, and they provide very value for money.</p>
<h2>Conclusion</h2>
<p>There is nothing perfect in this world. In the case of the wordpress vs. Static site, there is no clear winner. I like static websites more because they are fast and more cost-friendly.However, wordpress might be the better option for you. The thing is that whatever you choose, your content will always be the one to judge your rankings. The platform or tools don't matter that much.Not only writing long content will help. But the content needs to be good and requires to provide value to the users. At last, content is King.</p>
<h2>Update</h2>
<p>Building a blog with static websites has been made easier now by <a href="https://www.netlifycms.org/">Netlify CMS</a>. It's a GUI based CMS that allows users to do blogging without editing code with static site generators. It supports many static website generators like Gatsby, HUGO and others.</p>
<p>Recently, we have switched to Ghost CMS, which is based on jam stack and can also be used as a headless CMS. We found that Ghost blog is a faster and modern and perfect choice for blogging.</p>
<p>We are using Digital ocean with Ghost, which makes it quite economical too.</p>
<h2>Frequently asked questions</h2>
<ul>
<li><strong>What should I choose Wordpress or Wix?</strong>Wordpress and Wix both are good platforms, Wordpress has more flexibility. But, Wix is more beginner friendly. Wix can be good for security and built in SEO tools.</li>
<li><strong>Can I create static websites with Wordpress?</strong>Yes, there are a number of plugins which can do it. One is called SIMPLY STATIC. It can convert your Wordpress blog pages to static HTML and CSS pages.</li>
<li><strong>How to learn HTML, CSS, JS Faster?</strong>There's no shortcut, just start with the basics and proceed step by step. <a href="https://www.w3schools.com/">W3 Schools</a> has the best guides if you want to learn for free.</li>
<li><strong>What is the need of a fast website? </strong>A faster website is very important, especially for ranking higher on google.</li>
<li><strong>Can I switch from Wordpress to static website?</strong>Yes, but there is no automated process, you have to manually convert your posts to html and css. You can use a Static site generator for your blog posts. But for a bigger website it's more easier to stick with Wordpress and use it with Gatsby Js as a headless CMS.</li>
</ul>
</div>
</div>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
