<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <title>Bibarud</title>
    <link href="https://www.bibarud.com/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://www.bibarud.com" />
    <updated>2021-09-18T21:33:06+05:30</updated>
    <author>
        <name>Uddipan Barman</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://www.bibarud.com</id>

    <entry>
        <title>Guide to Fix the Mad Max 0xc00007b Error on Windows 10</title>
        <author>
            <name>Uddipan Barman</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://www.bibarud.com/guide-to-fix-the-mad-max-0xc00007b-error-on-windows-10/"/>
        <id>https://www.bibarud.com/guide-to-fix-the-mad-max-0xc00007b-error-on-windows-10/</id>
            <category term="Tech"/>

        <updated>2021-09-18T21:33:06+05:30</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://www.bibarud.com/media/posts/30/Guide-to-Fix-the-Mad-Max-0xc00007b-Error-on-Windows-10.jpeg" alt="Guide to Fix the Mad Max 0xc00007b Error on Windows 10" />
                     The Mad Max 0xc00007b error is one of the most frustrating&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://www.bibarud.com/media/posts/30/Guide-to-Fix-the-Mad-Max-0xc00007b-Error-on-Windows-10.jpeg" alt="Guide to Fix the Mad Max 0xc00007b Error on Windows 10" />
                <div class="post__toc">
<h3>Table of Contents</h3>
<ul>
<li><a href="#mcetoc_1ffsq3i262f">Why does the Mad Max 0xc00007b error occur?</a></li>
<li><a href="#mcetoc_1ffsq3i262g">What are the common causes of the Mad Max 0xc00007b error?</a></li>
<li><a href="#mcetoc_1ffsq3i262h">How can I fix the Mad Max 0xc00007b error on Windows 10?</a></li>
<li><a href="#mcetoc_1ffsq3i262i">How to Fix the Mad Max 0xc0007b error manually?</a></li>
<li><a href="#mcetoc_1ffsq3i262j">Download 0xc00007b for Mad Max on Windows</a></li>
<li><a href="#mcetoc_1ffsq3i262k">Conclusion</a></li>
</ul>
</div>
<p dir="auto">The Mad Max 0xc00007b error is one of the most frustrating Windows 0x Code issues to deal with. Even if you're an IT professional, it can still take hours just to get your PC working again.</p>
<p dir="auto">But it doesn't have to be this way. With our detailed guide, you'll get possible fixes on how to deal with the Mad Max 0xc00007b error so it doesn't happen again.</p>
<p dir="auto">The guide will walk you through all the steps necessary to fix the Mad Max 0xc00007b error and get back up and running so you can resume your day without having to worry about any pesky errors from happening again.</p>
<h3 id="mcetoc_1ffsq3i262f" dir="auto">Why does the Mad Max 0xc00007b error occur?</h3>
<p dir="auto">Mad Max Game is an open world, single player game set in a post-apocalyptic world. The game is set to be released on September 1, 2015. The developer of the game is Avalanche Studios and the publisher of the game is Warner Bros Interactive Entertainment.</p>
<p dir="auto">This error occurs because of an issue with the game’s graphics card driver. It is very important to have an up-to-date graphics card driver, so be sure to regularly check for updates for your computer’s graphics card.</p>
<p dir="auto">The Mad Max 0xc00007b error is caused when there is a problem with the graphics card driver. When this happens, it can be difficult for you to resume playing the game. If you are experiencing this problem it’s important that you update your computer's graphics card driver regularly.</p>
<p dir="auto"><strong>Also Read:</strong> <a href="https://www.bibarud.com/how-to-solve-the-zero-views-problem-on-tiktok/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">How to Solve the Zero Views Problem on TikTok</a></p>
<h3 id="mcetoc_1ffsq3i262g" dir="auto">What are the common causes of the Mad Max 0xc00007b error?</h3>
<p dir="auto">The Mad Max 0xc00007b error is caused by a conflict in the registry.</p>
<p dir="auto">One of the most common causes of the Mad Max 0xc00007b error is that one or more referenced files are missing, not found, or cannot be accessed.</p>
<p dir="auto">The Mad max 0xc00007b error can also be caused by a power surge or a low battery, which can happen when a laptop’s cord is disconnected from the wall.</p>
<h3 id="mcetoc_1ffsq3i262h" dir="auto">How can I fix the Mad Max 0xc00007b error on Windows 10?</h3>
<p dir="auto">The Mad Max 0xc00007b error can be caused by a number of things. There are different ways to fix the problem, but the easiest one is to check for updates.</p>
<p dir="auto">Before you do anything else, make sure that your computer’s drivers are up-to-date. If you’re not sure how to check for updates, here is a link to our article on how to update drivers.</p>
<p dir="auto">This error is most likely to happen when the game was not installed properly. Before looking for solutions, it is best to make sure that you have installed the game correctly and that Steam is running.</p>
<p dir="auto">If the issue persists, try setting up a different user account to play the game or restarting your PC. Otherwise, you will need to contact Steam Support for further help.</p>
<p dir="auto"><strong>Also Read: </strong><a href="https://www.bibarud.com/the-complete-guide-to-protecting-pdf-files/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">The Complete Guide to Protecting PDF Files in 2022</a></p>
<h3 id="mcetoc_1ffsq3i262i" dir="auto">How to Fix the Mad Max 0xc0007b error manually?</h3>
<p dir="auto">These are the steps you can take to fix it manually:</p>
<ul>
<li>
<p dir="auto">Use the control panel or download this uninstaller (easier way).</p>
</li>
<li>
<p dir="auto">Open the uninstaller you downloaded and type "visual" into the search box in the upper right corner.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p dir="auto">Now select all of the things or apps that are showing and uninstall them. (You can also use batch uninstall).</p>
</li>
<li>
<p dir="auto">Now, one by one, choose to erase each one, and then use a strong scan to eliminate all traces!</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="auto">After you've uninstalled everything, restart your computer or laptop and reinstall it! Not just one or two, but all of them.</p>
<p dir="auto">It makes no difference if you have a 64-bit or 32-bit operating system because you must install all visuals.</p>
<h3 id="mcetoc_1ffsq3i262j" dir="auto">Download 0xc00007b for Mad Max on Windows</h3>
<p dir="auto">This is a tutorial that will help you fix the error 0xc00007b, which is one of the most common errors in Mad Max on Windows.</p>
<ul>
<li>
<p dir="auto">Download the file <a href="https://www.bibarud.com/(0xc000007b).zip" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">here</a></p>
</li>
<li>
<p dir="auto">Now, after it’s downloaded paste the file in the Mad Max root folder,</p>
</li>
<li>
<p dir="auto">After pasting the file try restarting your PC</p>
</li>
<li>
<p dir="auto">Open Mad Max, and see if it works.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<h3 id="mcetoc_1ffsq3i262k" dir="auto">Conclusion</h3>
<p dir="auto">The guide explained how to fix the Mad Max 0xc00007b error on Windows 10. By following the directions in the guide, you can easily get rid of this error and enjoy smooth gameplay.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>How to Solve the Zero Views Problem on TikTok</title>
        <author>
            <name>Uddipan Barman</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://www.bibarud.com/how-to-solve-the-zero-views-problem-on-tiktok/"/>
        <id>https://www.bibarud.com/how-to-solve-the-zero-views-problem-on-tiktok/</id>
            <category term="Explained"/>

        <updated>2021-09-16T03:14:15+05:30</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://www.bibarud.com/media/posts/29/How-to-Solve-the-Zero-Views-Problem-on-TikTok.jpg" alt="How to Solve the Zero Views Problem on TikTok" />
                     TikTok is a social media app that creators can use to&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://www.bibarud.com/media/posts/29/How-to-Solve-the-Zero-Views-Problem-on-TikTok.jpg" alt="How to Solve the Zero Views Problem on TikTok" />
                <div class="post__toc">
<h3>Table of Contents</h3>
<ul>
<li><a href="#mcetoc_1ffll53u2s">What is the "zero views problem" on TikTok?</a></li>
<li><a href="#mcetoc_1ffll53u2t">How to Fix the Zero Views Problem on TikTok</a></li>
<li><a href="#mcetoc_1ffll53u2u">What are some ways to increase views on TikTok?</a></li>
<li><a href="#mcetoc_1ffll53u2v">What should you consider when making a video for TikTok?</a></li>
<li><a href="#mcetoc_1ffll53u210">Conclusion</a></li>
</ul>
</div>
<p dir="auto">TikTok is a social media app that creators can use to share short videos. It has been a powerful platform for many creators, but many have faced difficulties when their videos have been left with zero views.</p>
<p dir="auto">When a video has zero views, it means that no one watched the video and the creator has missed out on a chance to get exposure. Creators have lamented about feeling ignored and even worse, criticized for being so niche in their topics.</p>
<p dir="auto">TikTok is such an amazing platform for creators to share their creativity and skills! But it can be quite heartbreaking when you post a video and no one watches. Learn how to get views with this easy-to-follow guide</p>
<h3 id="mcetoc_1ffll53u2s" dir="auto">What is the "zero views problem" on TikTok?</h3>
<p dir="auto">The “zero views problem” is a phrase coined by TikTok to describe the way that some creators on the platform experience a lack of engagement.</p>
<p dir="auto">It is not an issue with how many followers you have, but rather the number of views your posts get.</p>
<p dir="auto">This is problematic because it can affect how often you post content on TikTok and what kind of content you make in order to get more views. It leaves some creators feeling like they are posting things that are not their true identity or voice in order to get more attention.</p>
<p dir="auto">The concept of “zero views problem” started as a joke but has now become an important discussion topic among creators on TikTok, who are now facing issues with performing their creative work due to this phenomenon.</p>
<h3 id="mcetoc_1ffll53u2t" dir="auto">How to Fix the Zero Views Problem on TikTok</h3>
<p dir="auto">TikTok is one of the most popular social media platforms for teens. Because it’s so popular, there are over 500 million monthly users on the app. However, not all of them are active or making content. The average number of views on a video is less than 1,000 views per day and it continues to decline.</p>
<p dir="auto">There are multiple ways that content creators can fix the problem with zero views. The first way they can do this is by getting rid of sponsors in every videos in order to focus on organic content that will retain more viewers and create a better user experience. A great way to reward quality content is to also enable comments for people’s opinions.</p>
<p dir="auto">Some Fixes can be:</p>
<ul>
<li>
<p dir="auto">Using the default video editor on Tiktok</p>
</li>
<li>
<p dir="auto">Avoiding Controversial and abusive videos.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p dir="auto">Sometimes, some videos are marked as suspended by tiktok, which can also cause the issue.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p dir="auto">Don’t copy someone’s video without putting your own creativity.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<figure class="post__image"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://www.bibarud.com/media/posts/29/Tiktok-image.jpg" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" srcset="https://www.bibarud.com/media/posts/29/responsive/Tiktok-image-xs.jpg 300w ,https://www.bibarud.com/media/posts/29/responsive/Tiktok-image-sm.jpg 480w ,https://www.bibarud.com/media/posts/29/responsive/Tiktok-image-md.jpg 768w ,https://www.bibarud.com/media/posts/29/responsive/Tiktok-image-lg.jpg 1024w"  alt="How to Solve the Zero Views Problem on TikTok" width="727" height="484"></figure>
<h3 id="mcetoc_1ffll53u2u" dir="auto">What are some ways to increase views on TikTok?</h3>
<p dir="auto">In order to get more views on TikTok, there are a number of ways that can help. If you have been uploading videos for a while and you have not had a lot of success, it might be the time to try something new. There is no one way to get more views on TikTok but there are some ways that have been proven to work.</p>
<p dir="auto">Some people download popular music and edit together a video with it. This can be done in several ways such as lip-sync or with lyrics on the screen in the background. This is an effective way to get more views because the original video often has millions of views already which means when people watch your video they might click on it too. It will also show up in searches that use the same song title since they will be in the same album, which means it will often show up in charts and playlists.</p>
<p dir="auto">Here are some more tips on increasing views on tiktok:</p>
<ul>
<li>
<p dir="auto">Post to popular hashtags and share your content with people who might enjoy it.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p dir="auto">Watch other TikTokers and use their best features in your videos.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p dir="auto">Share your content outside of TikTok, like on Instagram or other social media platforms, and add the hashtag #TikTok or #Tik to make it easier for people to find you.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p dir="auto">Make sure that you tag the creator of the video if it's not you.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<h3 id="mcetoc_1ffll53u2v" dir="auto">What should you consider when making a video for TikTok?</h3>
<p dir="auto">A video on TikTok is a brief and quick-paced content that is up to 15 seconds long. A video for TikTok should be made to entertain people and generate likes, comments, and followers. Some things you should consider before making a video on TikTok is to keep it short, add captions or subtitles in different languages, add music if the context doesn't make sense without it, make the content relatable and relateable by adding in some humor.</p>
<p dir="auto">Create a list of tips for making a video for TikTok:</p>
<ul>
<li>
<p dir="auto">Pick your favorite song</p>
</li>
<li>
<p dir="auto">Make sure your video is in focus</p>
</li>
<li>
<p dir="auto">Try to make your videos in vertical orientation</p>
</li>
<li>
<p dir="auto">Be creative!</p>
</li>
</ul>
<h3 id="mcetoc_1ffll53u210" dir="auto">Conclusion</h3>
<p dir="auto">TikTok is a social media app that allows users to create short videos (15 seconds) and share them with friends. This app is popular for its short, creative videos that attract millions of followers every day.</p>
<p dir="auto">The zero-view problem is where any video uploaded to TikTok has no views, likes or dislikes after 24 hours and may be seen as a major problem for the app’s sustainability.</p>
<p dir="auto">This blog post has taken a look at this issue and explored possible solutions that can help solve this issue in the future.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Comparison of Contabo Vs DigitalOcean: Understanding the Differences &amp; Which One is Best for You</title>
        <author>
            <name>Uddipan Barman</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://www.bibarud.com/contabo-vs-digitalocean/"/>
        <id>https://www.bibarud.com/contabo-vs-digitalocean/</id>
            <category term="Tech"/>

        <updated>2021-09-13T12:06:18+05:30</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://www.bibarud.com/media/posts/28/Digital-ocean-vs-Contabo.jpg" alt="Contabo Vs DigitalOcean" />
                     As a business owner, you have two big decisions to make&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://www.bibarud.com/media/posts/28/Digital-ocean-vs-Contabo.jpg" alt="Contabo Vs DigitalOcean" />
                <div class="post__toc">
<h3>Table of Contents</h3>
<ul>
<li><a href="#mcetoc_1ffdp3qtcv1">What is Contabo?</a></li>
<li><a href="#mcetoc_1ffdp3qtcv2">What’s special about Contabo?</a></li>
<li><a href="#mcetoc_1ffdp3qtcv3">What is Digital Ocean?</a></li>
<li><a href="#mcetoc_1ffdp3qtcv4">What’s special about Digital Ocean?</a></li>
<li><a href="#mcetoc_1ffdp3qtcv5">Whats The Difference Between Contabo and DigitalOcean?</a></li>
<li><a href="#mcetoc_1ffdp3qtcv6">Comparing Pricing</a></li>
<li><a href="#mcetoc_1ffdp3qtcv7">Comparing Performance &amp; Speed</a></li>
<li><a href="#mcetoc_1ffdp3qtcv8">Compare the backup options between contabo vs digitalocean</a></li>
<li><a href="#mcetoc_1ffdp3qtcv9">Digitalocean Server Location zones</a></li>
<li><a href="#mcetoc_1ffdp3qtcva">Contabo Server Location zones</a></li>
<li><a href="#mcetoc_1ffdp3qtcvb">Conclusion : Which One to Choose for Hosting Your Business Website?</a></li>
</ul>
</div>
<p dir="auto">As a business owner, you have two big decisions to make when choosing a hosting provider: which hosting provider to use and how to go about evaluating the differences.</p>
<p dir="auto">No one wants to be at a disadvantage of having a bad hosting provider. Which is why it's so important to take the time and do your research before committing to any one company.</p>
<p dir="auto">In this article, we'll present you with a comparison of <a href="https://contabo.com/en/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Contabo </a>and <a href="https://m.do.co/c/f49f0dc5b910" target="_blank" rel="sponsored noopener noreferrer">DigitalOcean</a> as well as their benefits, drawbacks, and what sets them apart from one another. This way you can make your decision with confidence and peace of mind. By becoming informed, you will also be able to avoid costly mistakes that can prove detrimental not only for your business but for the future</p>
<figure class="post__image"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://www.bibarud.com/media/posts/28/pexels-manuel-geissinger-325229.jpg" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" srcset="https://www.bibarud.com/media/posts/28/responsive/pexels-manuel-geissinger-325229-xs.jpg 300w ,https://www.bibarud.com/media/posts/28/responsive/pexels-manuel-geissinger-325229-sm.jpg 480w ,https://www.bibarud.com/media/posts/28/responsive/pexels-manuel-geissinger-325229-md.jpg 768w ,https://www.bibarud.com/media/posts/28/responsive/pexels-manuel-geissinger-325229-lg.jpg 1024w"  alt="Contabo Vs Digital Ocean" width="706" height="247"></figure>
<h3 id="mcetoc_1ffdp3qtcv1" dir="auto">What is <a href="https://contabo.com/en/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Contabo</a>?</h3>
<p dir="auto"><a href="https://contabo.com/en/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Contabo </a>is a German hosting company which was founded in 2003. It has grown to be one of the three largest web hosting providers in Germany. Contabo is known for their competitive prices and focus on standard, business-grade hosting features.</p>
<p dir="auto">In the beginning, <a href="https://contabo.com/en/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Contabo </a>was just a small start-up, but it has since grown into a player that needs to be taken seriously. In fact, they have many data centers around the world with over 1 million customers from many different countries and industries.</p>
<h3 id="mcetoc_1ffdp3qtcv2" dir="auto">What’s special about <a href="https://contabo.com/en/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Contabo</a>?</h3>
<p dir="auto">There are a couple of things that make <a href="https://contabo.com/en/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Contabo </a>stand out from the competition. The first is the price. It’s not always easy to find a reliable, affordable hosting provider, but with <a href="https://contabo.com/en/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Contabo </a>you can rest assured that they will not overcharge you. In fact, they provide the most competitive prices in comparison to other providers. What’s more, their customer service is excellent and guarantees high-quality support 24/7/365 days a year. As for their server performance and uptime, it’s second to none with 99% up-time on all servers.</p>
<p dir="auto">They also offer SSL certificates which come at no extra cost and have a 99% uptime on all servers as well as excellent customer service 24/7/365.</p>
<figure class="post__image"><a href="https://m.do.co/c/f49f0dc5b910" target="_blank" rel="sponsored noopener noreferrer"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://www.bibarud.com/media/posts/28/digitalocean-gif.gif" alt="100$ on digital ocean" width="728" height="90"></figure></a></p>
<h3 id="mcetoc_1ffdp3qtcv3" dir="auto">What is <a href="https://m.do.co/c/f49f0dc5b910" target="_blank" rel="sponsored noopener noreferrer">Digital Ocean</a>?</h3>
<p dir="auto"><a href="https://m.do.co/c/f49f0dc5b910" target="_blank" rel="sponsored noopener noreferrer">Digital Ocean</a> is a cloud hosting service that offers a hosting platform with a simple user interface.</p>
<p dir="auto"><a href="https://m.do.co/c/f49f0dc5b910" target="_blank" rel="sponsored noopener noreferrer">Digital Ocean</a> provides a platform for developers to create and deploy code in the form of a web server, database server, and other applications. The cloud server is scalable and provides a number of features such as data backups and monitoring.</p>
<p dir="auto"><a href="https://m.do.co/c/f49f0dc5b910" target="_blank" rel="sponsored noopener noreferrer">Digital Ocean</a> is a cloud-hosted virtual computer platform used for running and managing apps, websites, and other services. It offers a computing environment for developers to create and deploy code in the form of a web server, database server, and other applications. The cloud server is scalable and provides a number of features such as load balancing, object storage, firewalls, snapshots, and more.</p>
<h3 id="mcetoc_1ffdp3qtcv4" dir="auto">What’s special about Digital Ocean?</h3>
<p dir="auto"><a href="https://m.do.co/c/f49f0dc5b910" target="_blank" rel="sponsored noopener noreferrer">DigitalOcean </a>is a cloud hosting service provider that specializes in infrastructure for application developers.</p>
<p dir="auto"><a href="https://m.do.co/c/f49f0dc5b910" target="_blank" rel="sponsored noopener noreferrer">DigitalOcean </a>offers the latest Linux operating systems and software packages through its control panel, one-click application installs, and its interface.</p>
<p dir="auto">The company has over 10 million registered customers globally with over 1 million customers using <a href="https://m.do.co/c/f49f0dc5b910" target="_blank" rel="sponsored noopener noreferrer">DigitalOcean </a>as their primary web hosting provider.</p>
<figure class="post__image"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://www.bibarud.com/media/posts/28/pexels-panumas-nikhomkhai-1148820.jpg" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" srcset="https://www.bibarud.com/media/posts/28/responsive/pexels-panumas-nikhomkhai-1148820-xs.jpg 300w ,https://www.bibarud.com/media/posts/28/responsive/pexels-panumas-nikhomkhai-1148820-sm.jpg 480w ,https://www.bibarud.com/media/posts/28/responsive/pexels-panumas-nikhomkhai-1148820-md.jpg 768w ,https://www.bibarud.com/media/posts/28/responsive/pexels-panumas-nikhomkhai-1148820-lg.jpg 1024w"  alt="Digitalocean vs Contabo" width="713" height="476"></figure>
<h3 id="mcetoc_1ffdp3qtcv5" dir="auto">Whats The Difference Between <a href="https://contabo.com/en/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Contabo </a>and <a href="https://m.do.co/c/f49f0dc5b910" target="_blank" rel="sponsored noopener noreferrer">DigitalOcean</a>?</h3>
<p dir="auto"><a href="https://contabo.com/en/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Contabo </a>and <a href="https://m.do.co/c/f49f0dc5b910" target="_blank" rel="sponsored noopener noreferrer">DigitalOcean </a>are two of the most popular cloud hosting service providers in the world. However, there is a difference between them that separates them from each other. Let’s take a closer look at what this difference is and when it might become useful to you.</p>
<p dir="auto">When we talk about cloud hosting, we’re typically referring to hosting your website in a data center in order to provide you with faster and more reliable access to your site, especially in the case of an outage, such as when your internet connection goes out.</p>
<p dir="auto"><a href="https://m.do.co/c/f49f0dc5b910" target="_blank" rel="sponsored noopener noreferrer">DigitalOcean </a>and <a href="https://contabo.com/en/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Contabo </a>both offer this type of hosting service among many other similar services for companies who want their websites hosted on the internet.</p>
<h3 id="mcetoc_1ffdp3qtcv6" dir="auto">Comparing Pricing</h3>
<ul>
<li>
<p dir="auto"><a href="https://m.do.co/c/f49f0dc5b910" target="_blank" rel="sponsored noopener noreferrer">DigitalOcean </a>offers a plan for $5 per month with 1 CPU and 1GB of RAM.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p dir="auto"><a href="https://contabo.com/en/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Contabo </a>has a monthly fee of $6.99 in which you get a server with 4 cpu cores and 8 gigabytes of RAM.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="auto"><a href="https://contabo.com/en/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Contabo’s </a>Pricing starts from $6.99/month to $299/month depending on your configuration and needs, you can choose the plans you like.</p>
<p dir="auto"><a href="https://m.do.co/c/f49f0dc5b910" target="_blank" rel="sponsored noopener noreferrer">Digital ocean’s</a> pricing starts from $5/Month and can go up to $1000+/Month depending on your selection of extras and other things.</p>
<p dir="auto">Overall, the pricing of both of the services are good. While <a href="https://contabo.com/en/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">contabo’s </a>starting price is a little bit more, but it also offers more Ram and storage on the base plan.</p>
<h3 id="mcetoc_1ffdp3qtcv7" dir="auto">Comparing Performance &amp; Speed</h3>
<p dir="auto">Both the companies have a lot of similarities and differences. For example, both the companies provide virtual private servers, but <a href="https://contabo.com/en/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Contabo </a>is a German company while <a href="https://m.do.co/c/f49f0dc5b910" target="_blank" rel="sponsored noopener noreferrer">DigitalOcean </a>is a US firm.</p>
<p dir="auto">The basic difference between the two is that <a href="https://contabo.com/en/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Contabo </a>offers only few configuration of VPS with many features while <a href="https://m.do.co/c/f49f0dc5b910" target="_blank" rel="sponsored noopener noreferrer">DigitalOcean </a>offers many different types of VPS with varied features. In our speed test we found <a href="https://m.do.co/c/f49f0dc5b910" target="_blank" rel="sponsored noopener noreferrer">Digital Ocean</a> and contabo to be relatable to each other.</p>
<p dir="auto"><a href="https://contabo.com/en/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Contabo </a>has more ram than <a href="https://m.do.co/c/f49f0dc5b910" target="_blank" rel="sponsored noopener noreferrer">Digital Ocean</a> for $2 more, but contabo doesn’t have pure SSD Speeds. Their Servers are configured as boosted HDD meaning, SSD + HDD. In contabo both HDD and SDD are used as a hybrid manner, the OS and the other importnat things are stored on SSD but the other less important things are stored on their HDD.</p>
<p dir="auto">Whereas in <a href="https://m.do.co/c/f49f0dc5b910" target="_blank" rel="sponsored noopener noreferrer">Digital Ocean</a> the default is SSD, which means better read and write speeds. But as contabo has more ram they are both similar in terms of performance and speeds.</p>
<h3 id="mcetoc_1ffdp3qtcv8" dir="auto">Compare the backup options between <a href="https://contabo.com/en/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">contabo </a>vs <a href="https://m.do.co/c/f49f0dc5b910" target="_blank" rel="sponsored noopener noreferrer">digitalocean</a></h3>
<p dir="auto"><strong><a href="https://contabo.com/en/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Contabo</a></strong></p>
<ul>
<li>
<p dir="auto">The monthly cost for an 100GB FTP Storge backup is $4.99</p>
</li>
<li>
<p dir="auto">The monthly cost for an 2TB FTP Storage backup is $39.99.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="auto">The <a href="https://m.do.co/c/f49f0dc5b910" target="_blank" rel="sponsored noopener noreferrer">digital ocean</a> backup price is $1 per month for the $5/month Plan. DigitalOcean backups cost 20% for every plan. The best thing about this backup service is that it works seamlessly with the <a href="https://m.do.co/c/f49f0dc5b910" target="_blank" rel="sponsored noopener noreferrer">digital ocean</a> account.</p>
<h3 id="mcetoc_1ffdp3qtcv9" dir="auto"><a href="https://m.do.co/c/f49f0dc5b910" target="_blank" rel="sponsored noopener noreferrer">Digitalocean </a>Server Location zones</h3>
<p dir="auto"><a href="https://m.do.co/c/f49f0dc5b910" target="_blank" rel="sponsored noopener noreferrer">DigitalOcean </a>offers a suite of hosting options to suit the needs of the individual website owner. These options include cloud hosting, droplets, and DNS as well as instant provisioning and automatic backups. The instant provisioning feature allows for a server to be started within 60 seconds from receiving an order.</p>
<p dir="auto"><a href="https://m.do.co/c/f49f0dc5b910" target="_blank" rel="sponsored noopener noreferrer">DigitalOcean </a>has a global network of data centres that means that people can choose the location of their data centre to be closest to them. The datacentres are present in USA, India, Netherlands, Singapore, United Kingdom, Germany and Canada. This gives customers more control over their experience and also means that they can get faster access to their data.</p>
<h3 id="mcetoc_1ffdp3qtcva" dir="auto"><a href="https://contabo.com/en/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Contabo </a>Server Location zones</h3>
<p dir="auto"><a href="https://contabo.com/en/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Contabo </a>is a German company. The headquarters for <a href="https://contabo.com/en/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Contabo </a>is in Munich, Germany. The data center are in Germany, and in the United States. They have data centers in Singapore too. Their servers are located in Chicago and Seattle at the United States - East Coast zone.</p>
<h3 id="mcetoc_1ffdp3qtcvb" dir="auto">Conclusion : Which One to Choose for Hosting Your Business Website?</h3>
<p dir="auto"><a href="https://m.do.co/c/f49f0dc5b910" target="_blank" rel="sponsored noopener noreferrer">Digital ocean</a>, a cloud hosting service provider, and <a href="https://contabo.com/en/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Contabo</a><a href="#INTERNAL_LINK#/post/null" rel="nofollow"></a>, a German hosting service provider, are comparable in many ways. But they also have some distinct advantages and drawbacks.</p>
<p dir="auto">For starters, both offer a wide range of services to suit the needs of small businesses. They have competitive pricing for VPS hosting and have generous free trial periods that allow you to test their services before committing to them. <a href="https://contabo.com/en/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Contabo </a>offers customer support channels including phone, chat and email. While <a href="https://m.do.co/c/f49f0dc5b910" target="_blank" rel="sponsored noopener noreferrer">digital ocean</a> has a ticket system.</p>
<p dir="auto">The biggest difference between these two providers is that <a href="https://m.do.co/c/f49f0dc5b910" target="_blank" rel="sponsored noopener noreferrer">Digital Ocean</a> has a more advanced infrastructure than <a href="https://contabo.com/en/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Contabo </a>which means that its servers are more reliable and faster.</p>
<p dir="auto">For people looking for a more reliable hosting provider that can be scaled easily in the future <a href="https://m.do.co/c/f49f0dc5b910" target="_blank" rel="sponsored noopener noreferrer">Digital Ocean</a> would be the right choice. But it doesn’t mean that <a href="https://contabo.com/en/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Contabo </a>is bad.</p>
<p dir="auto">For people on a very tight budget and want to start their website and needs more RAM and CPU power for a low price, <a href="https://contabo.com/en/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Contabo </a>is the perfect choice.</p>
<p dir="auto"><em><strong>Disclaimer</strong>: Some of the links are affliliate links, which means we would get a small comission for your purchase without cositng you any extra penny. </em></p>
<figure class="post__image"><a href="https://m.do.co/c/f49f0dc5b910https://m.do.co/c/f49f0dc5b910" target="_blank" rel="sponsored noopener noreferrer"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://www.bibarud.com/media/posts/28/digitalocean-gif-2.gif" alt="Digital ocean $100 credit Instantly" width="728" height="90"></figure></a></p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>The Complete Guide to Protecting PDF Files in 2022</title>
        <author>
            <name>Uddipan Barman</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://www.bibarud.com/the-complete-guide-to-protecting-pdf-files/"/>
        <id>https://www.bibarud.com/the-complete-guide-to-protecting-pdf-files/</id>
            <category term="Tech"/>

        <updated>2021-09-12T14:45:28+05:30</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://www.bibarud.com/media/posts/27/The-Complete-Guide-to-Protecting-PDF-Files-Cover.jpg" alt="The Complete Guide to Protecting PDF Files" />
                     Keeping your PDF files safe and secure is one of the&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://www.bibarud.com/media/posts/27/The-Complete-Guide-to-Protecting-PDF-Files-Cover.jpg" alt="The Complete Guide to Protecting PDF Files" />
                <div class="post__toc">
<h3>Table of Contents</h3>
<ul>
<li><a href="#mcetoc_1ffcjt0181b">What are PDF Files?</a></li>
<li><a href="#mcetoc_1ffcjt0181c">Why You Need to Encrypt PDF Files?</a></li>
<li><a href="#mcetoc_1ffcjt0181d">Encryption Tools for Protecting PDFs</a></li>
<li><a href="#mcetoc_1ffcjt0181e">How to protect Pdf files from copying</a></li>
<li><a href="#mcetoc_1ffcjt0181f">How do you password protect a pdf file on mac?</a></li>
<li><a href="#mcetoc_1ffcjt0181g">How to protect a pdf file from being edited</a></li>
<li><a href="#mcetoc_1ffcjt0181h">PDF Files Security Recommendations</a></li>
<li><a href="#mcetoc_1ffcjt0181i">Conclusion</a></li>
</ul>
</div>
<p dir="auto">Keeping your PDF files safe and secure is one of the most important things you can do. Today's world is full of serious cyber-threats and malware, and we know that if we don't protect our files, we will lose them.</p>
<p dir="auto">But with so much information out there about what tools we should be using to keep our PDFs safe, it can be hard to figure out which solution is best for you and your company. Every option has its benefits and drawbacks, and it's hard to know which one is the perfect fit for you.</p>
<p dir="auto">In this guide you’ll know all about protecting your PDF files:</p>
<h3 id="mcetoc_1ffcjt0181b" dir="auto">What are PDF Files?</h3>
<p dir="auto">PDF files are document files that provide a high quality and accurate reproduction of the original document. They are used widely in academic institutions, legal systems, and other organizations that require a permanent record of text or images without any changes.</p>
<p dir="auto">PDF stands for Portable Document Format. It is developed by Adobe Systems Incorporated as a subset of PostScript language for viewing text and graphics on a monitor. The PDF format is capable of not just providing access to a wide variety of fonts, colors, line art, graphics, and images but it also offers the original file's content with high effectiveness.</p>
<p dir="auto">Originally, the PDF file format was created by Adobe Systems as a way to easily share documents with other people who may or may not have access to the same software. The PDF file format was created to be universal, so that anyone with Adobe Acrobat Reader could open, view, and interact with these files no matter what device they were on.</p>
<h3 id="mcetoc_1ffcjt0181c" dir="auto">Why You Need to Encrypt PDF Files?</h3>
<p dir="auto">PDF files are widely used in many organizations for their convenience, but what most people don’t know is that they are not secure. To make sure that your PDF files are safe, you need to encrypt them.</p>
<p dir="auto">Encrypting PDF files is a great way to protect the information in these documents from unauthorized access. And it’s not just about preventing data interception through email or file transfer protocol. It also protects data from being leaked because of hacking. Encryption can be applied to the whole document or selected text or images within a document.</p>
<p dir="auto">But there are some caveats with this topic - for instance, if your PDF file is too large, encryption slows down its performance and renders it unusable at all!</p>
<p dir="auto">If you want to safely encrypt your PDF files for storage, it's a good idea to use a PDF encryption softwares.</p>
<figure class="post__image"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://www.bibarud.com/media/posts/27/The-Complete-Guide-to-Protecting-PDF-Files.jpg" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" srcset="https://www.bibarud.com/media/posts/27/responsive/The-Complete-Guide-to-Protecting-PDF-Files-xs.jpg 300w ,https://www.bibarud.com/media/posts/27/responsive/The-Complete-Guide-to-Protecting-PDF-Files-sm.jpg 480w ,https://www.bibarud.com/media/posts/27/responsive/The-Complete-Guide-to-Protecting-PDF-Files-md.jpg 768w ,https://www.bibarud.com/media/posts/27/responsive/The-Complete-Guide-to-Protecting-PDF-Files-lg.jpg 1024w"  alt="The-Complete-Guide-to-Protecting-PDF-Files" width="6912" height="3456"></figure>
<h3 id="mcetoc_1ffcjt0181d" dir="auto">Encryption Tools for Protecting PDFs</h3>
<p dir="auto">The encryption tools are in demand because of the increased awareness for security. The market is filled with different software that takes care of all your data protection needs. It is hard to choose which one to use because it can be very expensive to switch between them.</p>
<p dir="auto">Encryption tools are easy to use and provide a great level of protection for your PDFs. You can upload your document or generate a new one through the site, encrypt it so only you have access, and download the encrypted PDF which will only be readable on your computer.</p>
<p dir="auto">Below is a list of encryption tools for protecting PDFs:</p>
<ul>
<li>
<p dir="auto"><a href="https://www.adobe.com/in/acrobat/acrobat-pro.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Adobe Acrobat Pro DC</a></p>
</li>
<li>
<p dir="auto"><a href="https://www.adobe.com/in/acrobat/free-trial-download.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Adobe Acrobat XI Pro</a></p>
</li>
<li>
<p dir="auto">Adobe Reader XI</p>
</li>
<li>
<p dir="auto"><a href="https://www.foxit.com/pdf-reader/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Foxit PDF Reader</a></p>
</li>
<li>
<p dir="auto"><a href="https://www.gonitro.com/pdf-reader" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Nitro PDF Reader</a></p>
</li>
</ul>
<h3 id="mcetoc_1ffcjt0181e" dir="auto">How to protect Pdf files from copying</h3>
<p dir="auto">There are a few ways to protect your content from being copied. Most people think that digitally watermarking the content is the only way to go, but there's more.</p>
<p dir="auto">Digital watermarks can be a form of protection - if someone copies your pdf file and tries to edit it, the watermark will show up and you will be able to identify it as a copy even if they have changed some of the information.</p>
<p dir="auto">A digital lock that locks your pdf file is also good protection. You can offer their clients an opportunity to purchase a password for their product once its been downloaded from you.</p>
<p dir="auto">You can encrypt your pdf files so that they can't be opened without an encryption key.</p>
<p dir="auto">These are all forms of protection available for your PDF files.</p>
<h3 id="mcetoc_1ffcjt0181f" dir="auto">How do you password protect a pdf file on mac?</h3>
<p dir="auto">This tutorial will show you how to password protect PDF files on a Mac. If you would like to password protect your PDFs using Windows, please see the link below for more information.</p>
<p dir="auto">Password protecting a PDF file is not difficult; we just need to know the right tools and techniques. The easiest and most common technique is by using Adobe Acrobat, which has built-in features that can do this task seamlessly. Alternatively, we can also use third-party software and online websites.</p>
<p dir="auto">List Tools that you can use to protect PDF Files online:</p>
<ul>
<li>
<p dir="auto"><a href="https://smallpdf.com" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Smallpdf.com</a></p>
</li>
<li>
<p dir="auto"><a href="https://ilovepdf.com" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">ilovepdf.com</a></p>
</li>
<li>
<p dir="auto"><a href="https://sejda.com" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">sejda.com</a></p>
</li>
<li>
<p dir="auto"><a href="https://cleverpdf.com" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">cleverpdf.com</a></p>
</li>
<li>
<p dir="auto"><a href="sodapdf.com" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">sodapdf.com</a></p>
</li>
</ul>
<h3 id="mcetoc_1ffcjt0181g" dir="auto">How to protect a pdf file from being edited</h3>
<p dir="auto">There are two ways of protecting PDF files: password-protecting the document and encrypting the document. Password-protecting your PDF file is a method of preventing people from editing your document by making them enter a password before they can edit the file. Encrypting your document is another way of preventing people from editing your document by scrambling all the data in it so that only someone with the right “key” can unscramble it and access its contents.</p>
<h3 id="mcetoc_1ffcjt0181h" dir="auto">PDF Files Security Recommendations</h3>
<p dir="auto">A PDF file is a document that contains text, graphics, audio, video and interactive content. It's readable on virtually any computer platform or device since it uses Adobe's Portable Document Format.</p>
<p dir="auto">PDF files are not secure. They are prone to digital tampering by hackers and other people who want to steal information from them. The PDF file format isn't designed to be secure, but there are ways you can take precautions to keep your PDF files as safe as possible.</p>
<ul>
<li>
<p dir="auto">Don't open attachments that you don't recognize</p>
</li>
<li>
<p dir="auto">Be wary of unknown attachments that might harm your data.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p dir="auto">If you must open an attachment, scan it for viruses before opening</p>
</li>
<li>
<p dir="auto">Don't open attachments after reading an email if the email is asking for sensitive information</p>
</li>
<li>
<p dir="auto">Don't open attachments with the following extensions: .exe, .bat, .zip, .scr, .cmd, .pif, .vbs without scanning them with an antivirus.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<h3 id="mcetoc_1ffcjt0181i" dir="auto">Conclusion</h3>
<p dir="auto">We hope that you have found this guide helpful. It is important that you take the necessary precautions to protect your PDF files.</p>
<p dir="auto">PDF files are increasingly getting more popular because they are easy to share and store. They are also accessible on all devices. Unfortunately, PDFs are also at risk of getting hacked or corrupted which can make them unusable.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>The Ultimate Guide to Fixing Pubg Gameloop Keyboard Not Working</title>
        <author>
            <name>Uddipan Barman</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://www.bibarud.com/the-ultimate-guide-to-fixing-pubg-gameloop-keyboard-not-working/"/>
        <id>https://www.bibarud.com/the-ultimate-guide-to-fixing-pubg-gameloop-keyboard-not-working/</id>
            <category term="Tech"/>

        <updated>2021-09-12T02:59:27+05:30</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://www.bibarud.com/media/posts/26/The-Ultimate-Guide-to-Fixing-Pubg-Gameloop-Keyboard-Not-Working.jpg" alt="The Ultimate Guide Fixing Pubg Gameloop Keyboard Not Working" />
                     The gameloop "keyboard not working" error is one that plagues many&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://www.bibarud.com/media/posts/26/The-Ultimate-Guide-to-Fixing-Pubg-Gameloop-Keyboard-Not-Working.jpg" alt="The Ultimate Guide Fixing Pubg Gameloop Keyboard Not Working" />
                <div class="post__toc">
<h3>Table of Contents</h3>
<ul>
<li><a href="#mcetoc_1ffbbur7k17">Why You Shouldn't Panic When Your Pubg Gameloop Keyboard Doesn't Work!</a></li>
<li><a href="#mcetoc_1ffbbur7k18">What are the Reasons that Make Your Pubg Gameloop Keyboard Stop Working?</a></li>
<li><a href="#mcetoc_1ffbbur7k19">How to Fix a Pubg GameLoop Keyboard issue</a></li>
<li><a href="#mcetoc_1ffbbur7k1a">Conclusion</a></li>
</ul>
</div>
<p dir="auto">The gameloop "keyboard not working" error is one that plagues many gamers. With the PUBG game, for example, it's an issue that thousands of players are facing.</p>
<p dir="auto">As an avid gamer myself, I know the pain of encountering this problem. Fixing it takes a lot of time and effort, and the whole process can be intimidating to fix on your own. But here I am to show you how!</p>
<p dir="auto">I have compiled a list of methods to fix your keyboard not working issue in PUBG. From disabling your keyboard or turning off keyboard notifications, to resyncing your Bluetooth-these are all simple solutions that are guaranteed to fix your problem 100%.</p>
<h3 id="mcetoc_1ffbbur7k17" dir="auto">Why You Shouldn't Panic When Your Pubg Gameloop Keyboard Doesn't Work!</h3>
<p dir="auto">If you are a PUBG player, you might have an idea about how important is your keyboard if you don’t have a mouse. You need to either use the arrow keys or WASD buttons on your keyboard to move in the game.</p>
<p dir="auto">Moreover, there are many keys needed for playing the game like LMB, RMB, Q and E etc., which can be confusing for some users.</p>
<p dir="auto">However, when these keys stop working in the middle of a round then it becomes really frustrating and can ruin your experience of playing PUBG!</p>
<p dir="auto">This article will guide the user with a list of useful tips on how to fix common issues that may occur when using pubg with gameloop keyboard. You can try to change some of these settings by looking at the control panel and changing some of the settings there. If you're still having trouble, you can always try unplugging your keyboard and plugging it back in again.</p>
<p dir="auto"><strong>Also Read:</strong> <a href="https://www.bibarud.com/fix-for-key-mapping-in-gameloop-2021/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Fix for key mapping in Gameloop 2021</a></p>
<h3 id="mcetoc_1ffbbur7k18" dir="auto">What are the Reasons that Make Your Pubg Gameloop Keyboard Stop Working?</h3>
<p dir="auto">The first thing to try is unplugging the keyboard and plugging it back in. If this does not work then there is probably some issue with the keyboard driver. You can go into device manager and uninstall or rollback drivers if that has helped you in the past.</p>
<p dir="auto">The next thing to do is restart your computer. This will fix the problem 90% of the time if you are experiencing an issue with your keyboard.</p>
<p dir="auto">If you are still unable to use your keyboard, try using a different one to see if it works properly. If not, then there may be something wrong with your computer or PC set up which needs fixing by a professional expert technician.</p>
<p dir="auto">It is also advisable to restart and reinstall the gameloop software to see if it will fixes the keyboard issue.</p>
<h3 id="mcetoc_1ffbbur7k19" dir="auto">How to Fix a Pubg GameLoop Keyboard issue</h3>
<p dir="auto">If you are playing PUBG and you experience the "GameLoop Keyboard" issue, it may be because your keyboard’s display is not in sync with the game. This is a fix that most players recommend and one that has been confirmed to work:</p>
<ul>
<li>
<p dir="auto">Right click on your desktop and select "Display settings".</p>
</li>
<li>
<p dir="auto">Click on the "Advanced" tab and then under "Monitor" find what looks like a tv next to your monitor.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p dir="auto">Turn off the display sync (otherwise leave it on).</p>
</li>
<li>
<p dir="auto">Restart PUBG.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p dir="auto">Restart Gameloop and clear Cache</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="auto">After this fix, this issue should not occur again while playing PUBG.</p>
<h3 id="mcetoc_1ffbbur7k1a" dir="auto">Conclusion</h3>
<p dir="auto">The pubg game is one of the most popular games in the world. It has took place in many countries and there are over 100 million players worldwide.</p>
<p dir="auto">This game is about players fighting each other with rifles, pistols, machine guns, grenades and other weapons. The goal of the game is to eliminate all opponents or to capture certain zones on a map or fight them to the death.</p>
<p dir="auto">There are many gameloop keyboard not working that happen because of many reasons like broken keyboards or technical issues.</p>
<p dir="auto"> </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>The Road Not Taken Summary in under 300 words</title>
        <author>
            <name>Uddipan Barman</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://www.bibarud.com/the-road-not-taken-summary-in-under-300-words/"/>
        <id>https://www.bibarud.com/the-road-not-taken-summary-in-under-300-words/</id>
            <category term="Summary"/>

        <updated>2021-09-06T02:01:17+05:30</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://www.bibarud.com/media/posts/25/name-17.jpeg" alt="The Road Not Taken Summary" />
                    The Road Not Taken, a la Shmoop. I'm always second guessing my&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://www.bibarud.com/media/posts/25/name-17.jpeg" alt="The Road Not Taken Summary" />
                <p>The Road Not Taken, a la Shmoop. I'm always second guessing my choices. I almost called this poem, "The Road Taken." Then I started obsessing over all the other titles I could have picked. Would I regret not going with something grittier, like "That one time I wore new shoes on a walk and got really bad blisters?</p>
<p>" I guess the grass is always greener on the other path. Or is it brownish yellowish? Argh, this is so hard! My worst case of indecision happened when I was going for a walk in a forest, and I came to a fork in the road. I stepped over it, and there were two pathways in front of me.</p>
<p>My GPS didn't work way out here in the boonies, so I didn't have any guidance to tell me which route to take. Candidate A was a fine looking specimen, with appealing scenery, and no visible predators. Candidate B looked pretty great, too, and it seemed wilder and overgrown, like it hadn’t been landscaped for a while.</p>
<p><strong>Also Read:</strong> <a href="https://www.bibarud.com/lord-of-the-flies-chapter-1-summary/">Lord of the flies chapter 1 summary in 450 words</a></p>
<p>But now that I looked closer… Road A also seemed to be untamed by the sneakers of man. Or, at least, I couldn’t see too many Cheetos wrappers on the ground.</p>
<p>I decided to settle this in a mature, reasonable manner. I could always come back another time and take Road A. Anytime I wanted to. Although I wasn’t really doing much walking, now that I had my Fat-burnatron 2000. …and the forecast was calling for rain … …and my fantasy football league was in full swing.</p>
<p>So I didn’t really have time for another relationship. And it's not like I was going to hurt the road’s feelings or anything… Oh, well. What's done is done. And this road is great! We've had some really good times together.</p>
<p>But I can't help thinking about that other road. I know someday I'll be sitting in my armchair, boring my kids with “What Ifs?” What if I had taken that first road? Maybe I would have discovered a doorway to another dimension, or a new species of feral guinea pig! I guess I'll never know what I missed….</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>CTET Previous Year Question Papers with Answers Download in PDF format.</title>
        <author>
            <name>Uddipan Barman</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://www.bibarud.com/ctet-previous-year-question-papers-with-answers-download-in-pdf-format/"/>
        <id>https://www.bibarud.com/ctet-previous-year-question-papers-with-answers-download-in-pdf-format/</id>

        <updated>2021-08-30T02:07:57+05:30</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://www.bibarud.com/media/posts/24/name-16.jpeg" alt="CTET Previous Year Question Papers with Answers Download in PDF format." />
                    CTET Question Papers from the Past with Answers Here are links to&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://www.bibarud.com/media/posts/24/name-16.jpeg" alt="CTET Previous Year Question Papers with Answers Download in PDF format." />
                <p data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="3">CTET Question Papers from the Past with Answers Here are links to PDF downloads. This page now contains the CTET Previous Year Papers. CTET past year question paper PDFs are the most valuable resources for familiarising yourself with previous exam patterns and enhancing your exam efficiency. You'll get a fair understanding of the huge variety of questions that have been posted on the CTET test over the years.</p>
<div class="post__toc">
<h3>Table of Contents</h3>
<ul>
<li><a href="#mcetoc_1fe9np39vaa">CTET Exams in the Past</a></li>
<li><a href="#mcetoc_1fe9np39vab">CTET Previous Year Papers are available in PDF format.</a></li>
<li><a href="#mcetoc_1fe9np39vac">What Are the Benefits of Examining CTET Previous Year Papers?</a></li>
<li><a href="#mcetoc_1fe9np39vad">Syllabus and Exam Pattern for CTET</a></li>
<li><a href="#mcetoc_1fe9np39vae">What is the level of difficulty for CTET Papers I and II?</a>
<ul>
<li><a href="#mcetoc_1fe9np39vaf">In CTET, what kind of negative marking is there?</a></li>
<li><a href="#mcetoc_1fe9np39vag">Is the CTET Certificate valid for a certain amount of time?</a></li>
<li><a href="#mcetoc_1fe9np39vah">What are the types and levels of difficulty of the CTET questions?</a></li>
<li><a href="#mcetoc_1fe9np39vai">Which CTET previous year question papers, and for which years, are available for download?</a></li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
</div>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1fe9np39vaa" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="4">CTET Exams in the Past</h2>
<p data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="5">You can look at previous years' CTET question papers, which are presented with the solution key on this page. You can also take CTET Mock Tests, which comprise a database of over 200 question papers to help you enhance your overall performance.</p>
<p data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="7">You can download the CTET question papers in PDF format in Hindi and English, as well as the answers, for Paper 1 and Paper 2 for the year 2020, directly from the official website. We've also provided the previous year's CTET question papers in PDF format for your convenience, so you can get a sense of the questions and patterns for both Paper 1 and Paper 2 in the next year.</p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1fe9np39vab" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="8">CTET Previous Year Papers are available in PDF format.</h2>
<p data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="9">Previous Year Papers Answer Key PDF from Connecticut Technical Education and Training (CTET).</p>
<ul>
<li data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="11">The CTET Answer Key 2021 is the most important tool for analysing and comparing performance and scores on Paper 1 and Paper 2 of the CTET test. Take a peek at the solution key in PDF format supplied below.</li>
<li data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="12">The CTET Syllabus, which can be viewed here, is used to create previous year's papers. It's a smart idea to incorporate the papers into your exam preparation strategy.</li>
</ul>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1fe9np39vac" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="13">What Are the Benefits of Examining CTET Previous Year Papers?</h2>
<p data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="14">For a variety of reasons, solving CTET previous year papers with solutions is beneficial. For your consideration, we have listed the following benefits:</p>
<ul>
<li data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="15">Assistance in deciphering the CTET 2020 exam's exact examination pattern</li>
<li data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="16">Recognize the questions' level of difficulty.</li>
<li data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="17">Recognize how the questions are distributed based on the subject.</li>
<li data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="18">Recognize how the questions are organised within each segment.</li>
</ul>
<p data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="19">Clearing the CTET exam will qualify the applicant for the most recent government teaching posts, so make sure you use the best CTET preparation approaches and tools to assure exam success.</p>
<p data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="19"><img loading="lazy" src="https://www.bibarud.com/media/posts/24/name-15.jpeg" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" srcset="https://www.bibarud.com/media/posts/24/responsive/name-15-xs.jpeg 300w ,https://www.bibarud.com/media/posts/24/responsive/name-15-sm.jpeg 480w ,https://www.bibarud.com/media/posts/24/responsive/name-15-md.jpeg 768w ,https://www.bibarud.com/media/posts/24/responsive/name-15-lg.jpeg 1024w"  alt="CTET Previous Year Question Paper with Answers PDF download" width="900" height="470"></p>
<table style="border-collapse: collapse; width: 100%; height: 943px;" border="1">
<tbody>
<tr style="height: 48px;">
<td style="width: 50%; height: 48px;"><strong>Paper 1</strong></td>
<td style="width: 50%; height: 48px;"><strong>Paper 2</strong></td>
</tr>
<tr style="height: 48px;">
<td style="width: 50%; height: 48px;"><a href="https://ctet.nic.in/webinfo/File/GetFile?FileId=37&amp;LangId=P" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Paper 1 Main</a></td>
<td style="width: 50%; height: 48px;"><a href="https://ctet.nic.in/webinfo/File/GetFile?FileId=56&amp;LangId=P" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Paper 2 Main</a></td>
</tr>
<tr style="height: 48px;">
<td style="width: 50%; height: 48px;"><a href="https://ctet.nic.in/webinfo/File/GetFile?FileId=38&amp;LangId=P" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Paper 1  Assamese</a></td>
<td style="width: 50%; height: 48px;"><a href="https://ctet.nic.in/webinfo/File/GetFile?FileId=57&amp;LangId=P" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Paper 2  Assamese</a></td>
</tr>
<tr style="height: 45px;">
<td style="width: 50%; height: 45px;"><a href="https://ctet.nic.in/webinfo/File/GetFile?FileId=55&amp;LangId=P" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Paper 1  Bengali</a></td>
<td style="width: 50%; height: 45px;"><a href="https://ctet.nic.in/webinfo/File/GetFile?FileId=58&amp;LangId=P" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Paper 2  Bengali</a></td>
</tr>
<tr style="height: 48px;">
<td style="width: 50%; height: 48px;"><a href="https://ctet.nic.in/webinfo/File/GetFile?FileId=39&amp;LangId=P" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Paper 1  Garo</a></td>
<td style="width: 50%; height: 48px;"><a href="https://ctet.nic.in/webinfo/File/GetFile?FileId=59&amp;LangId=P" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Paper 2  Garo</a></td>
</tr>
<tr style="height: 48px;">
<td style="width: 50%; height: 48px;"><a href="https://ctet.nic.in/webinfo/File/GetFile?FileId=40&amp;LangId=P" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Paper 1  Gujarati</a></td>
<td style="width: 50%; height: 48px;"><a href="https://ctet.nic.in/webinfo/File/GetFile?FileId=60&amp;LangId=P" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Paper 2  Gujarati</a></td>
</tr>
<tr style="height: 48px;">
<td style="width: 50%; height: 48px;"><a href="https://ctet.nic.in/webinfo/File/GetFile?FileId=41&amp;LangId=P" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Paper 1  Kannada</a></td>
<td style="width: 50%; height: 48px;"><a href="https://ctet.nic.in/webinfo/File/GetFile?FileId=61&amp;LangId=P" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Paper 2  Kannada</a></td>
</tr>
<tr style="height: 48px;">
<td style="width: 50%; height: 48px;"><a href="https://ctet.nic.in/webinfo/File/GetFile?FileId=42&amp;LangId=P" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Paper 1  Khasi</a></td>
<td style="width: 50%; height: 48px;"><a href="https://ctet.nic.in/webinfo/File/GetFile?FileId=62&amp;LangId=P" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Paper 2  Khasi</a></td>
</tr>
<tr style="height: 48px;">
<td style="width: 50%; height: 48px;"><a href="https://ctet.nic.in/webinfo/File/GetFile?FileId=43&amp;LangId=P" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Paper 1  Malayalam</a></td>
<td style="width: 50%; height: 48px;"><a href="https://ctet.nic.in/webinfo/File/GetFile?FileId=63&amp;LangId=P" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Paper 2  Malayalam</a></td>
</tr>
<tr style="height: 48px;">
<td style="width: 50%; height: 48px;"><a href="https://ctet.nic.in/webinfo/File/GetFile?FileId=44&amp;LangId=P" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Paper 1  Manipuri</a></td>
<td style="width: 50%; height: 48px;"><a href="https://ctet.nic.in/webinfo/File/GetFile?FileId=64&amp;LangId=P" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Paper 2  Manipuri</a></td>
</tr>
<tr style="height: 48px;">
<td style="width: 50%; height: 48px;"><a href="https://ctet.nic.in/webinfo/File/GetFile?FileId=45&amp;LangId=P" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Paper 1  Marathi</a></td>
<td style="width: 50%; height: 48px;"><a href="https://ctet.nic.in/webinfo/File/GetFile?FileId=65&amp;LangId=P" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Paper 2  Marathi</a></td>
</tr>
<tr style="height: 48px;">
<td style="width: 50%; height: 48px;"><a href="https://ctet.nic.in/webinfo/File/GetFile?FileId=46&amp;LangId=P" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Paper 1  Mizo</a></td>
<td style="width: 50%; height: 48px;"><a href="https://ctet.nic.in/webinfo/File/GetFile?FileId=66&amp;LangId=P" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Paper 2  Mizo</a></td>
</tr>
<tr style="height: 48px;">
<td style="width: 50%; height: 48px;"><a href="https://ctet.nic.in/webinfo/File/GetFile?FileId=47&amp;LangId=P" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Paper 1  Nepali</a></td>
<td style="width: 50%; height: 48px;"><a href="https://ctet.nic.in/webinfo/File/GetFile?FileId=67&amp;LangId=P" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Paper 2  Nepali</a></td>
</tr>
<tr style="height: 48px;">
<td style="width: 50%; height: 48px;"><a href="https://ctet.nic.in/webinfo/File/GetFile?FileId=48&amp;LangId=P" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Paper 1  Odia</a></td>
<td style="width: 50%; height: 48px;"><a href="https://ctet.nic.in/webinfo/File/GetFile?FileId=68&amp;LangId=P" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Paper 2  Odia</a></td>
</tr>
<tr style="height: 48px;">
<td style="width: 50%; height: 48px;"><a href="https://ctet.nic.in/webinfo/File/GetFile?FileId=49&amp;LangId=P" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Paper 1  Punjabi</a></td>
<td style="width: 50%; height: 48px;"><a href="https://ctet.nic.in/webinfo/File/GetFile?FileId=69&amp;LangId=P" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Paper 2  Punjabi</a></td>
</tr>
<tr style="height: 48px;">
<td style="width: 50%; height: 48px;"><a href="https://ctet.nic.in/webinfo/File/GetFile?FileId=50&amp;LangId=P" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Paper 1  Sanskrit</a></td>
<td style="width: 50%; height: 48px;"><a href="https://ctet.nic.in/webinfo/File/GetFile?FileId=70&amp;LangId=P" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Paper 2  Sanskrit</a></td>
</tr>
<tr style="height: 48px;">
<td style="width: 50%; height: 48px;"><a href="https://ctet.nic.in/webinfo/File/GetFile?FileId=51&amp;LangId=P" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Paper 1 Tamil</a></td>
<td style="width: 50%; height: 48px;"><a href="https://ctet.nic.in/webinfo/File/GetFile?FileId=71&amp;LangId=P" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Paper 2 Tamil</a></td>
</tr>
<tr style="height: 48px;">
<td style="width: 50%; height: 48px;"><a href="https://ctet.nic.in/webinfo/File/GetFile?FileId=52&amp;LangId=P" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Paper 1  Telugu</a></td>
<td style="width: 50%; height: 48px;"><a href="https://ctet.nic.in/webinfo/File/GetFile?FileId=72&amp;LangId=P" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Paper 2  Telugu</a></td>
</tr>
<tr style="height: 48px;">
<td style="width: 50%; height: 48px;"><a href="https://ctet.nic.in/webinfo/File/GetFile?FileId=53&amp;LangId=P" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Paper 1  Tibetan</a></td>
<td style="width: 50%; height: 48px;"><a href="https://ctet.nic.in/webinfo/File/GetFile?FileId=73&amp;LangId=P" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Paper 2  Tibetan</a></td>
</tr>
<tr style="height: 34px;">
<td style="width: 50%; height: 34px;"><a href="https://ctet.nic.in/webinfo/File/GetFile?FileId=54&amp;LangId=P" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Paper 1  Urdu</a></td>
<td style="width: 50%; height: 34px;"><a href="https://ctet.nic.in/webinfo/File/GetFile?FileId=74&amp;LangId=P" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Paper 2  Urdu</a></td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1fe9np39vad" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="20">Syllabus and Exam Pattern for CTET</h2>
<p data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="21">Applicants should familiarise themselves with the CTET Syllabus and Exam Pattern before sitting the exam, as this will help them prepare better for the exam. When preparing for the CTET, it is a good idea to go over the curriculum thoroughly. There are five subjects that must be covered for CTET Paper-I: English Language, Hindi Language, Child Development and Pedagogy, Environmental Studies, and Mathematics.</p>
<p data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="23">Social Studies, Science, English Language (including Hindi), Child Development &amp; Pedagogy, Environmental Studies (including Mathematics), and Mathematics are among the subjects covered in the CTET Paper-II. Knowing the test pattern assists us to get a better understanding of the type and difficulty of questions that will be asked on the exam.</p>
<p data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="23">Also Read: <a href="https://www.bibarud.com/lord-of-the-flies-chapter-1-summary/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Lord of the flies chapter 1 summary in 450 words</a></p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1fe9np39vae" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="24">What is the level of difficulty for CTET Papers I and II?</h2>
<p data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="25">The difficulty level of CTET Paper I and II is moderate, making it easy to moderate. The questions in CTET Paper I will be based on the themes covered in the NCERT syllabus for classes I – V. Nevertheless, the difficulty level of the questions may be comparable to that of secondary school.</p>
<p data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="27">The key focus of CTET Paper II-Mathematics and Science and Social Studies/Social Science, respectively, will concentrate on ideas, problem-solving abilities, instructional understanding, and applications of the disciplines. For grades VI-Volume 1, the questions will be organised into different divisions of the subject's syllabus, as established by the National Council of Educational Research and Training (NCERT).</p>
<h3 id="mcetoc_1fe9np39vaf" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="28">In CTET, what kind of negative marking is there?</h3>
<p data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="30">CTET does not use a system of negative marking. It is recommended that applicants attempt all questions in the exam for the best chance of getting above-average marks.</p>
<h3 id="mcetoc_1fe9np39vag" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="32">Is the CTET Certificate valid for a certain amount of time?</h3>
<p data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="34">From the date of issue, the CTET certificate is valid for seven years.</p>
<h3 id="mcetoc_1fe9np39vah" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="36">What are the types and levels of difficulty of the CTET questions?</h3>
<p data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="38">The nature and standard of questions in CTET are linked to the topic studied; for example, Child Development and Pedagogy will focus on the educational psychology of teaching and learning that pertains to children aged six to eleven years.</p>
<p data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="40">In the future, the necessity of understanding the characteristics and requirements of various learners, as well as contact with learners and the characteristics and qualities of a competent learning facilitator, will be stressed further. The topics of Mathematics and Environmental Studies will focus on the ideas, problem-solving abilities, pedagogical knowledge, and applications prescribed by the National Council of Educational Research and Training (NCERT) for grades I through V.</p>
<p data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="40">Also Read: <a href="https://www.bibarud.com/dust-of-snow-english-summary-question-and-answers/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Dust of Snow: English Class 10 NCERT (First Flight) Summary, Question &amp; Answers</a></p>
<h3 id="mcetoc_1fe9np39vai" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="42">Which CTET previous year question papers, and for which years, are available for download?</h3>
<p data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="44">CTET previous year's question paper PDFs for Paper I and Paper II are available to download for the years 2014, 15, 16, 17, 18, and 19.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>10 Ways to Fix Vizio TV Green Screen issue</title>
        <author>
            <name>Uddipan Barman</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://www.bibarud.com/10-ways-to-fix-vizio-tv-green-screen-issue/"/>
        <id>https://www.bibarud.com/10-ways-to-fix-vizio-tv-green-screen-issue/</id>
            <category term="Explained"/>

        <updated>2021-08-11T00:54:02+05:30</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://www.bibarud.com/media/posts/23/name-13.jpeg" alt="10 Ways to Fix Vizio TV Green Screen issue" />
                     For a long time, Vizio has offered cheap displays such as&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://www.bibarud.com/media/posts/23/name-13.jpeg" alt="10 Ways to Fix Vizio TV Green Screen issue" />
                <div class="post__toc">
<h3>Table of Contents</h3>
<ul>
<li><a href="#mcetoc_1fcoo83l8d4">Why is the screen on my Vizio TV green?</a></li>
<li><a href="#mcetoc_1fcoo83l8d5">How can I solve the green screen on my Vizio television?</a>
<ul>
<li><a href="#mcetoc_1fcoo83l8d6">Method 1: Restart the television</a></li>
<li><a href="#mcetoc_1fcoo83l8d7">Method 2: Change the source of your input.</a></li>
<li><a href="#mcetoc_1fcoo83l8d8">Method 3: Adjust the tint in your image mode.</a></li>
<li><a href="#mcetoc_1fcoo83l8d9">Method 4: Restart your television.</a></li>
<li><a href="#mcetoc_1fcoo83l8da">Method 5: Cable channel with a lousy signal</a></li>
<li><a href="#mcetoc_1fcoo83l8db">Method 6: Capacitors must be replaced.</a></li>
<li><a href="#mcetoc_1fcoo83l8dc">Method 7: Video Panel Damage</a></li>
<li><a href="#mcetoc_1fcoo83l8dd">Method 8: Change the LVDS cable.</a></li>
<li><a href="#mcetoc_1fcoo83l8de">Method 9: Internal Issues</a></li>
<li><a href="#mcetoc_1fcoo83l8df">Method 10: Replace the television and file a warranty claim.</a></li>
</ul>
</li>
<li><a href="#mcetoc_1fcoo83l8dg">FAQs</a></li>
</ul>
</div>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">For a long time, Vizio has offered cheap displays such as OLEDs, LEDs, and LCDs.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">These displays are suitable for the money, but they are prone to wear and tear and production flaws.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Some people claim that their screens have turned green.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">There may be underlying issues or connectivity issues. In this essay, we'll look into them.</span></p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1fcoo83l8d4"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Why is the screen on my Vizio TV green?</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">A form of magnetic interference, probably from the speakers, is a potential cause of the screen turning green. A TV screen can turn green if an internal speaker is too close or too far away.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">A loose or damaged HDMI cable connection to or from the TV is the most typical cause of a green screen on your Vizio TV.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">It's also possible that your TV's motherboard capacitors are failing.</span></p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1fcoo83l8d5"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">How can I solve the green screen on my Vizio television?</span></h2>
<h3 id="mcetoc_1fcoo83l8d6"><span data-preserver-spaces="true"><strong>Method 1:</strong> Restart the television</span></h3>
<ul>
<li><span data-preserver-spaces="true">To return your Vizio TV to its default settings, follow the procedures outlined below.</span></li>
<li><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Press the Menu button on the VIZIO remote.</span></li>
<li><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Highlight the System using the remote's arrow buttons and click OK.</span></li>
<li><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Press OK after selecting Reset &amp; Admin.</span></li>
<li><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Highlight Press OK to return the TV to its factory defaults.</span></li>
<li><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Wait for the television to shut off.</span></li>
<li><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The TV will switch back on, and the Setup App will begin the setup procedure.</span></li>
</ul>
<h3 id="mcetoc_1fcoo83l8d7"><strong><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Method 2:</span></strong><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> Change the source of your input.</span></h3>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">An alternate input source should be used instead of the HDMI cable. Change the power source as well. A broken HDMI adapter could be the source of the problem. Make the necessary adjustments to the cable. You should also adjust it for the media device.</span></p>
<h3 id="mcetoc_1fcoo83l8d8"><strong><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Method 3:</span></strong><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> Adjust the tint in your image mode.</span></h3>
<ul>
<li><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Choose 'Picture' in the Menu after pressing the Vizio button on your remote.</span></li>
<li><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Picture Mode will be the first option, and you can also adjust the Picture settings.</span></li>
<li><span data-preserver-spaces="true">A tint or hue control on your Vizio TV is required. To suit your viewing preferences, adjust the Green in RGB.</span></li>
<li><span data-preserver-spaces="true">To make it look better, experiment with different photo settings.</span></li>
</ul>
<h3 id="mcetoc_1fcoo83l8d9"><strong><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Method 4:</span></strong><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> Restart your television.</span></h3>
<p><strong><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Step 1:</span></strong><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> Turn off the television.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">By clicking the Power Off button on the Vizio remote, you can turn off your TV.</span></p>
<p><strong><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Step 2:</span></strong><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> Turn off the television.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Disconnect the power cord from the outlet in the wall.</span></p>
<p><strong><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Step 3:</span></strong><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> Keep the power button pressed.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Press and hold the power button for 3-5 seconds after the TV has been turned off and unplugged (this is critical).</span></p>
<p><strong><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Step 4:</span></strong><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> Reconnect the television.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Reconnect the TV's power cord by finding a power outlet and waiting a few seconds before turning it on.</span></p>
<h3 id="mcetoc_1fcoo83l8da"><span data-preserver-spaces="true"><strong>Method 5:</strong> Cable channel with a lousy signal</span></h3>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Some cable channels broadcast material in a resolution that is lower than your Smart TV's native resolution. This might be problematic. Alternatively, there could be a problem with the signal that your TV receives that is creating these color issues.</span></p>
<h3 id="mcetoc_1fcoo83l8db"><strong><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Method 6:</span></strong><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> Capacitors must be replaced.</span></h3>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The motherboard's capacitors may be failing. This is a typical issue with many new televisions and displays. The TV may be taking longer than usual to set up or work. It will likely cease to function shortly.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">You can open your Vizio TV and get to the motherboard if you have a little understanding. Look for ruptured capacitors, which have a bulging top rather than a flat one. These capacitors must be replaced. From the shop, find the ones with the same voltage. For additional information, contact Vizio Support.</span></p>
<h3 id="mcetoc_1fcoo83l8dc"><span data-preserver-spaces="true"><strong>Method 7:</strong> Video Panel Damage</span></h3>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">A damaged LCD panel could be the cause of your TV's green lines or green screen. Even if your TV's internal workings are OK, they may not appear in the visual panel.</span></p>
<h3 id="mcetoc_1fcoo83l8dd"><span data-preserver-spaces="true"><strong>Method 8:</strong> Change the LVDS cable.</span></h3>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The problem could be caused by the LVDS cable or Low Voltage Differential Signaling cable. Due to quality difficulties, the connectors of this cable that connect to the display may be defective. Many users have claimed that replacing the LVDS cable restored the functionality of their televisions.</span></p>
<h3 id="mcetoc_1fcoo83l8de"><span data-preserver-spaces="true"><strong>Method 9:</strong> Internal Issues</span></h3>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">When one of the panels stops working, it usually means the drive data for all RGB information on the right side of the screen has been lost completely. In this circumstance, replacing or purchasing a new television would be an excellent alternative to explore.</span></p>
<h3 id="mcetoc_1fcoo83l8df">Method 10:<span data-preserver-spaces="true"> Replace the <strong>television</strong> and file a warranty claim.</span></h3>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Call Vizio Support and request that your TV be replaced because it is malfunctioning. Vizio TVs come with a minimum 1-year warranty, so you're covered as long as you're under them. Your television can be replaced entirely. When calling Vizio Support, make a mental note of the model number and the issues you're having.</span></p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1fcoo83l8dg"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">FAQs</span></h2>
<p><strong>Q1. What happens if the screen on your television turns green?</strong></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">A. You are unable to see colors correctly. It can also be a shaky connection between media devices. It could also be a problem with your TV's hardware, causing the entire or part of the image to turn green, making it difficult to discern between things on the screen.</span></p>
<p><strong>Q2. Why is my HDMI-connected TV screen green?</strong></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">A. It's most probable that your HDMI cable is faulty. Replace the cable if possible. If the problem persists, replace both your media device and your Vizio TV's HDMI ports, as they may be faulty.</span></p>
<p><strong>Q3. How can I solve my Vizio TV's green screen?</strong></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">A. Here are several options for repairing your green screen:</span></p>
<ul>
<li><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Restart your television.</span></li>
<li><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Capacitors on the motherboard should be replaced.</span></li>
<li><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Replace the LVDS cable with a new one.</span></li>
<li><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Switch the HDMI cord on and off. Replace it if it is defective.</span></li>
<li><span data-preserver-spaces="true">HDMI ports should be replaced.</span></li>
<li><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Wait a few moments before turning on your media device that connects to your TV. Allow the television to begin first.</span></li>
<li><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Last but not least,</span></li>
<li><span data-preserver-spaces="true">If changing all of the cords and equipment indicated above doesn't help, replacing your TV is the best solution. You can use these procedures in the order listed.</span></li>
</ul>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>App for Vizio TV&#x27;s internet browser (2021): Using a web browser, Smart TVs from Vizio</title>
        <author>
            <name>Uddipan Barman</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://www.bibarud.com/app-for-vizio-tvs-internet-browser-2021/"/>
        <id>https://www.bibarud.com/app-for-vizio-tvs-internet-browser-2021/</id>
            <category term="Explained"/>

        <updated>2021-07-25T14:27:23+05:30</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://www.bibarud.com/media/posts/22/name-8.jpeg" alt="Using a web browser, Smart TVs from Vizio" />
                     App for Vizio TV's internet browser : The browser is the&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://www.bibarud.com/media/posts/22/name-8.jpeg" alt="Using a web browser, Smart TVs from Vizio" />
                <div class="post__toc">
<h3>Table of Contents</h3>
<ul>
<li><a href="#mcetoc_1fbednk3oee">Can I use my Vizio Smart TV to access the internet?</a></li>
<li><a href="#mcetoc_1fbednk3oef">How do I get the Vizio TV browser app?</a></li>
<li><a href="#mcetoc_1fbednk3oeg">How to see if the internet connection on your Vizio Smart TV is working?</a>
<ul>
<li><a href="#mcetoc_1fbednk3oeh">Examine Other Devices' Internet Connections</a></li>
<li><a href="#mcetoc_1fbednk3oei">Double-check that you're connected properly.</a></li>
<li><a href="#mcetoc_1fbednk3oej">Restart your Vizio smart television</a></li>
<li><a href="#mcetoc_1fbednk3oek">Get in touch with the customer service team.</a></li>
<li><a href="#mcetoc_1fbednk3oel">Restart your Vizio smart television</a></li>
</ul>
</li>
<li><a href="#mcetoc_1fbednk3oem">How can I get my Vizio Smart TV to connect to the internet?</a>
<ul>
<li><a href="#mcetoc_1fbednk3oen">Using the wireless approach, connect your Vizio Smart TV.</a></li>
<li><a href="#mcetoc_1fbednk3oeo">Using the Wired option, connect your Vizio Smart TV.</a></li>
</ul>
</li>
<li><a href="#mcetoc_1fbednk3oep">Conclusion</a></li>
</ul>
</div>
<hr>
<p data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="3"><strong>App for Vizio TV's internet browser</strong> : The browser is the doorway to all kinds of media and data on your Vizio Smart TV. Therefore, this is a unique yet extremely useful topic.</p>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="4">Because of the widespread use of browsers on our cellphones, there are virtually unlimited possibilities for what may be done and achieved using a web browser. So let's get this tutorial started by going over all there is to know about the Vizio TV Internet browser software.</p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1fbednk3oee" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="4">Can I use my Vizio Smart TV to access the internet?</h2>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="6">Yes! You certainly can. We all want to be able to access the internet quickly, which is feasible with web browsers. Sure, you can receive the information you need on your Smartphone, laptop, or computer and then transmit it to the TV.</p>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="7">However, this is not always enjoyable and takes time. Not to add, if you don't have the internet, downloading data through phone hotspots, USB connections, and other methods can be difficult. This is when the Internet browser comes in handy.</p>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="8">You can always try to get an Internet browser for your Vizio TV and use it to browse and download stuff directly from the television without the use of any additional devices. The next section explains how you can try to get it.</p>
<figure class="post__image"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://www.bibarud.com/media/posts/22/name-10.jpeg" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" srcset="https://www.bibarud.com/media/posts/22/responsive/name-10-xs.jpeg 300w ,https://www.bibarud.com/media/posts/22/responsive/name-10-sm.jpeg 480w ,https://www.bibarud.com/media/posts/22/responsive/name-10-md.jpeg 768w ,https://www.bibarud.com/media/posts/22/responsive/name-10-lg.jpeg 1024w"  alt="Using a web browser, Smart TVs from Vizio" width="900" height="470"></figure>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1fbednk3oef" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="8">How do I get the Vizio TV browser app?</h2>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="10">Now that we've covered the fundamentals, it's time to deliver some terrible news. Vizio does not have native support for web browsers. You're probably thinking of doing it through the App Store, but it's not supported and will cause the app to crash.</p>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="11">If you connect your Vizio Smart TV to a computer input port or a Cat5 cable, it will support a web browser, which is very similar to casting rather than using an actual web browser.</p>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="12">Although the Vizio Smart TV can not access the Internet directly, it can access Netflix, Hulu, Peacock TV, and Roku, among other apps, for all of your video streaming needs. These, too, require an internet connection to function.</p>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="13">This raises a critical question. How does one connect a Vizio Smart TV to a network so that it can access the internet? You'll always need a way to connect to the internet, whether you're using an internet browser or video streaming apps.</p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1fbednk3oeg" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="13">How to see if the internet connection on your Vizio Smart TV is working?</h2>
<figure class="post__image"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://www.bibarud.com/media/posts/22/name-9-2.jpeg" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" srcset="https://www.bibarud.com/media/posts/22/responsive/name-9-2-xs.jpeg 300w ,https://www.bibarud.com/media/posts/22/responsive/name-9-2-sm.jpeg 480w ,https://www.bibarud.com/media/posts/22/responsive/name-9-2-md.jpeg 768w ,https://www.bibarud.com/media/posts/22/responsive/name-9-2-lg.jpeg 1024w"  alt="How to see if the internet connection on your Vizio Smart TV is working?" width="900" height="470"></figure>
<h3 id="mcetoc_1fbednk3oeh" class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="15">Examine Other Devices' Internet Connections</h3>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="16">This is a very dependable and simple way to do it. You may always connect a device to the same network as the Vizio Smart TV to see if it works well with the internet. If it still doesn't work, try turning on and off your internet connection.</p>
<h3 id="mcetoc_1fbednk3oei" class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="17">Double-check that you're connected properly.</h3>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="18">If you use Wifi to connect your Vizio device to the internet, check the settings to see if your Smart TV is connected to a network (the network name and connection status should be visible if it is).</p>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="19">If it isn't already linked, connect it by entering the correct password and try using the apps again.</p>
<h3 id="mcetoc_1fbednk3oej" class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="20">Restart your Vizio smart television</h3>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="21">If you are connected to the internet but it is not working, you may either pull out the power cable or just switch off and restart the TV. Rebooting almost always solves these kinds of problems, and hopefully it will for you as well.</p>
<h3 id="mcetoc_1fbednk3oek" class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="22">Get in touch with the customer service team.</h3>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="23">You can contact Vizio's customer service department about these concerns and inform them that your internet is not working. Take note of the variant you have, as well as the firmware and any upgrades it is running.</p>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="24">Hopefully, based on your information, the Vizio support staff will be able to give you a successful solution that will work for you!</p>
<h3 id="mcetoc_1fbednk3oel" class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="25">Restart your Vizio smart television</h3>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="26">It was a severe approach, but on the other hand, it would cure the TV of any problem it had been having that had gone undetected. This should hopefully resolve the internet problem, but remember to back up your data first.</p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1fbednk3oem" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="26">How can I get my Vizio Smart TV to connect to the internet?</h2>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="28">To connect a Vizio Smart TV to the internet, there are two main options. The first is the most common wireless connection method, and the second is a cable connection approach. Both of them are simple, so pick the one that best suits your needs.</p>
<h3 id="mcetoc_1fbednk3oen" class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="29">Using the wireless approach, connect your Vizio Smart TV.</h3>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="31"><strong>Step 1: </strong>On the remote, locate and press the menu button.</p>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="32">Each remote's design differs to some extent, but the menu button is usually found at the top of the remote, plainly labelled as MENU.</p>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="34"><strong>Step 2:</strong> Select Network from the drop-down menu.</p>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="35">This is where you can connect to a variety of wireless networks or WiFi.</p>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="37"><strong>Step 3:</strong> Select the desired WiFi network by navigating to it and clicking on it.</p>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="38">As the credentials, you will be requested to provide a password.</p>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="40"><strong>Step 4:</strong> Using the on-screen keyboard, type the correct password.</p>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="41">That concludes our discussion. The Vizio Smart TV is now connected to the WiFi network and ready to use!</p>
<h3 id="mcetoc_1fbednk3oeo" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="41">Using the Wired option, connect your Vizio Smart TV.</h3>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="45">f you don't want to use the WiFi network, you can use an Ethernet cable with a slightly modified setting to get the same effect.</p>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="47"><strong>Step 1:</strong> Plug the Ethernet cable into the Ethernet port on the WiFi router.</p>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="48">A set of ports on the rear of the wifi router are used for WAN, Ethernet, and other connections. Make certain you're connected to the correct one.</p>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="50"><strong>Step 2:</strong> Plug the other end into the TV's Ethernet port.</p>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="51"><strong>Step 3:</strong> Press the Menu Button once more.</p>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="52"><strong>Step 4:</strong> Join The New Network You've Found.</p>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="53">The new network discovered with the Ethernet cable will be noticeable. Select it and follow the directions to connect to it.</p>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="55">That's all there is to it! You can now use a wired connection to watch videos on your Vizio Smart TV!</p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1fbednk3oep" class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="57">Conclusion</h2>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="59">The methods for connecting to the internet and using the Vizio TV internet browser software were addressed in the preceding article. I hope you found it informative.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>How to FIX HBO Max Sound Problems (2021)</title>
        <author>
            <name>Uddipan Barman</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://www.bibarud.com/how-to-fix-hbo-max-sound-problems-2021/"/>
        <id>https://www.bibarud.com/how-to-fix-hbo-max-sound-problems-2021/</id>
            <category term="Explained"/>

        <updated>2021-07-17T15:40:04+05:30</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://www.bibarud.com/media/posts/21/name-7.jpeg" alt="How to FIX HBO Max Sound Problems (2021)" />
                     HBO Max is HBO's premium subscription that allows users to watch&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://www.bibarud.com/media/posts/21/name-7.jpeg" alt="How to FIX HBO Max Sound Problems (2021)" />
                <div class="post__toc">
<h3>Table of Contents</h3>
<ul>
<li><a href="#mcetoc_1fapute3ro">How do I fix HBO Max's sound problem?</a>
<ul>
<li><a href="#mcetoc_1fapute3rp">Examine the volume</a></li>
<li><a href="#mcetoc_1fapute3rq">Make sure your phone is not in do not disturb mode</a></li>
<li><a href="#mcetoc_1fapute3rr">Speakers with flaws</a></li>
<li><a href="#mcetoc_1fapute3rs">Bluetooth compatibility</a></li>
<li><a href="#mcetoc_1fapute3rt">Speakers should be checked</a></li>
<li><a href="#mcetoc_1fapute3ru">Updates</a></li>
</ul>
</li>
<li><a href="#mcetoc_1fapute3rv">Conclusion</a></li>
</ul>
</div>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="4">HBO Max is HBO's premium subscription that allows users to watch all of their favourite movies and shows. HBO Max also gives you access to exclusive HBO series. However, a variety of obstacles may hinder you from doing so. We're going to discuss one of these issues, HBO Max's lack of sound.</p>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="5">Apart from that, we'd also talk about how to correct it along the road. Because HBO Max is used by several devices, you should double-check each solution. Let's get this article started right away.</p>
<p data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="5"><strong>Read More:</strong> <a href="https://www.bibarud.com/how-to-watch-hbo-max-on-fios-tv/">How to watch HBO Max on FiOS TV - (Guide 2021)</a></p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1fapute3ro" class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="6">How do I fix HBO Max's sound problem?</h2>
<h3 id="mcetoc_1fapute3rp" class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="7">Examine the volume</h3>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="8">It may appear to be a ridiculous answer, but believe me when I say that you do not want to know how many times it has happened to me. I wasted precious seconds trying to download files again because I thought they were missing audio due to a bug. Check your device's audio levels to avoid making the same error.</p>
<h3 id="mcetoc_1fapute3rq" class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="9">Make sure your phone is not in do not disturb mode</h3>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="10">The sound profiles are fantastic. On keypad phones in the past, you might have noticed different profiles, such as Silent, Meeting, Outside, and so on. The same is renamed on Android or iPhones, and one of them is DND (or Do Not Disturb in short), which is wonderful for muting your phone but disables media sound if you don't enable it.</p>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="11">Make sure Do Not Disturb is turned off whenever you're utilising HBO Max or any other media material, including audio.</p>
<h3 id="mcetoc_1fapute3rr" class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="12">Speakers with flaws</h3>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="13">Do you have an ancient phone? Perhaps your device's speakers have finally given up the ghost. This implies you won't be able to receive clear or continuous audio from it. It's possible that you won't get any sound from it at all.</p>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="14">The best approach to seeing if the material has audio is to try a working pair of earbuds or headphones and plug them into the audio jack.</p>
<h3 id="mcetoc_1fapute3rs" class="root-block-node" data-changed="true" data-paragraphid="15">Bluetooth compatibility</h3>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="16">You would not notice if your Bluetooth was unintentionally linked to your headphones or the speakers downstairs, but you would think that the noise was not originating from the media content.</p>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="17">Always check your notification panel to see if anything is associated with your Bluetooth, which could be open and paired with another device in most circumstances.</p>
<h3 id="mcetoc_1fapute3rt" class="root-block-node" data-changed="true" data-paragraphid="18">Speakers should be checked</h3>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="19">This is computer and Smart TV advice (Samsung and Apple TVs). Always double-check your external speakers to ensure they are properly connected. Try playing another piece of material to see if it has any sounds. If it doesn't, your speaker will need to be reprogrammed.</p>
<p data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="19"><strong>Read More:</strong> <a href="https://www.bibarud.com/what-does-the-phrase-no-couriers-nearby-on-uber-eats-mean/">What does the phrase "no couriers nearby" on Uber Eats mean? (2021)</a></p>
<h3 id="mcetoc_1fapute3ru" class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="20">Updates</h3>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="21">Maintain the most recent versions of your browsers, television software, and HBO Max app. This would be really beneficial to you, not just in terms of the audio problem, but also in terms of other issues! If nothing else works, try searching for a solution on the HBO Max help website.</p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1fapute3rv" class="root-block-node" data-changed="true" data-paragraphid="22">Conclusion</h2>
<p class="root-block-node" data-changed="false" data-paragraphid="23">The steps in the above advice will show you how to effortlessly cure HBO Max no sound on various devices. I hope you find the information in this post beneficial. Try this guide if your HBO Max screen is stuck.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
